[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: 
Original Script: 
Synch Point: 1
ScriptType: v4.00+
PlayResX: 0
PlayResY: 0
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no
YCbCr Matrix: TV.601

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.50,0:00:05.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)\fs16\bord0\shad0\blur5\t(0,500,\blur0)\b1\c&HECB000&\pos(99,242)}原创翻译  双语字幕
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.00,0:00:05.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)\fn方正准圆_GBK\b1\bord0\shad0\fs17\pos(235.108,242)\K40}最新连载海外影视剧下载\N{\fs19\K30}请登陆 {\c&H26F4FF&\fn方正综艺_GBK\K30}www.YYeTs.com\N{\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs15\c&HFFFFFF&\K60}仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.22,0:00:11.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)}翻译     showeryhe  Brisingr
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.22,0:00:16.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)}翻译     胖达萌萌哒  潇然
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.22,0:00:21.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)}翻译     无序脚印  tokilltime
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.22,0:00:26.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)}校对     潇然  胡说大王
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.22,0:00:31.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(27,235)}时间轴     {\c&H9B30FF&}风吹来的那片云
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.22,0:00:36.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)}后期     灰灰是菇凉
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.22,0:00:41.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)}总监     showeryhe
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.70,0:00:02.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}联调局国际反应小组
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.64,0:00:03.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每年有超过6800万美国人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.39,0:00:05.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,离开安全的国内
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.05,0:00:07.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当危险来袭
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.84,0:00:10.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,联调局国际反应小组
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.44,0:00:12.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随时出动
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.23,0:00:13.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}弗吉尼亚州  匡提科
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.94,0:00:38.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.46,0:01:22.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰克·加勒特组长
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.19,0:01:24.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天你有权保持沉默
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.20,0:01:26.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并拒绝回答问题
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.36,0:01:28.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果放弃该权利  那你所说的所有内容
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.25,0:01:30.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都可以并将用来作为呈堂证供
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.98,0:01:32.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在讯问开始之前及进行过程中
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.61,0:01:34.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你都有权找律师咨询
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.10,0:01:36.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你无力聘请律师
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.32,0:01:41.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.90,0:01:44.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰克·加勒特组长  你明白
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.57,0:01:45.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚才解释的这些权利了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.93,0:01:48.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.77,0:01:54.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}犯罪心理  国境之外
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.62,0:01:54.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}第二季第九集
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.31,0:02:34.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}要想保守秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.21,0:02:34.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}除非其他知情者都是死人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.07,0:02:34.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}本杰明·富兰克林
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.55,0:02:40.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在是否愿意坐下回答我们的问题
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.33,0:02:43.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.20,0:02:50.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰克  你确定不要律师吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.36,0:02:51.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能会来狠的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.62,0:02:53.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不需要律师
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.22,0:02:56.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请记录国际反应小组组长杰克·加勒特
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.62,0:02:58.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此次放弃咨询律师的权利
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.99,0:03:01.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此次与会的还有
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.50,0:03:03.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来自联调局职业责任办公室的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.51,0:03:06.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,布莱恩·林奇和乔迪·雷诺兹探员
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.68,0:03:09.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥伦比亚特区的副法顾贾尼丝·赖切尔
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.29,0:03:11.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,代表司法部出席
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.34,0:03:13.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,国家情报局副主任沃尔特·阿特伍德
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.93,0:03:16.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我是联调局国家安全处的执行助理主任
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.70,0:03:18.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳达·巴恩斯
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.92,0:03:21.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿特伍德副主任和我受全权委托
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.24,0:03:23.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来负责此次联调局与国情局的联合讯问
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.59,0:03:24.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加勒特组长
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.99,0:03:26.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能否从头开始
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.29,0:03:28.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说说可吉基斯坦卡利叶
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.27,0:03:30.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,编号67-16-01的案件
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.51,0:03:33.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在里斯本给飞机加燃料
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.51,0:03:33.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}葡萄牙首都
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.20,0:03:36.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这时罗素·蒙哥马利探员通知我们
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.25,0:03:39.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美国大使及可吉基斯坦外交部
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.82,0:03:42.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要求我们参与协助
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.38,0:03:45.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是涉及一位美国公民及一位可吉基公民的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.60,0:03:47.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,双尸案
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.24,0:03:48.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克丽·洛德尔  二十九岁
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.55,0:03:50.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是罗得岛州普罗维登斯人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.48,0:03:52.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在全球策略开发
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.72,0:03:56.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家美国承包单位  做网络工程师
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.49,0:03:57.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有阿伦·萨布里
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.95,0:03:59.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三十二岁  卡利叶人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.80,0:04:01.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在全球策略开发做保安
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.83,0:04:04.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据可吉基国家警察的里法伊长官
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.83,0:04:06.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一位据称与克丽有染的同事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.98,0:04:09.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将她活活捅死
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.19,0:04:11.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个人叫爱德华·德尔加多
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.37,0:04:12.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德尔加多  四十六岁
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.92,0:04:14.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是弗吉尼亚州亚历山德里亚人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.54,0:04:15.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,担任系统分析员
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.61,0:04:17.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已婚并育有一个两岁的女儿
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.48,0:04:18.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当地保安萨布里
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.98,0:04:19.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎在与德尔加多
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.87,0:04:21.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打斗过程中身亡
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.34,0:04:23.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而德尔加多则趁机逃出居住区
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.80,0:04:24.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来都发生在
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.87,0:04:26.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡利叶的钢圈中
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.08,0:04:28.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,钢圈
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.22,0:04:30.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是一片六平方千米的严守地区
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.80,0:04:32.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}伊拉克首都
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.80,0:04:32.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,类似于巴格达的绿区
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.05,0:04:35.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰克  我认识德尔加多
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.71,0:04:36.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认识他吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.74,0:04:38.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前有过接触
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.31,0:04:40.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾在缅甸一家非政府组织共事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.45,0:04:42.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么时候的事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.10,0:04:45.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三年前  我请假离开那段时间
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.40,0:04:46.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你对他有什么印象
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.81,0:04:49.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说实话  我觉得完全说不通
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.31,0:04:49.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认识的那个人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.98,0:04:51.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪怕很生气  音量也不会提高
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.56,0:04:52.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而别提杀人了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.89,0:04:55.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不止是杀人  他现在可是逃犯
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.75,0:04:58.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塞格尔探员的工作就是分析
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.46,0:05:01.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并对犯罪嫌疑人给出客观侧写
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.30,0:05:04.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那她的判断力难道不是已经受影响了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.25,0:05:05.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全没有
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.82,0:05:06.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全没有
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.64,0:05:10.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塞格尔探员和德尔加多以前的接触
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.30,0:05:13.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认为不会以任何方式影响她的能力
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.14,0:05:15.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我不认为  正如我不相信
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.50,0:05:18.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿特伍德副主任和我的老交情
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.31,0:05:20.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能影响他在本次讯问过程中
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.60,0:05:22.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保持客观公正的能力
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.63,0:05:26.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塞格尔探员有没有向你
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.31,0:05:27.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或团队中其他成员
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.53,0:05:30.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全交代她过去和德尔加多先生的关系
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.42,0:05:33.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塞格尔探员坦言三年前
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.73,0:05:35.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们曾在缅甸共事
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.47,0:05:36.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她没有刚好提及
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.50,0:05:38.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和这个男人的私人关系吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.00,0:05:44.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她没有提及  但这不重要  因为
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.67,0:05:47.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重要的是你对团队成员的了解程度
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.74,0:05:50.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毫无疑问讯问过程中这一块十分重要
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.87,0:05:52.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我们先跳过吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.42,0:05:56.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们登陆该国后  说说有什么流程
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.06,0:05:58.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们到达卡利叶后就开始
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.87,0:06:01.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和巴希尔·里法伊长官协作
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.34,0:06:03.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是可吉基国家警察的负责人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.60,0:06:04.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惜
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.35,0:06:06.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我手下对逃犯爱德华·德尔加多的追捕
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.09,0:06:08.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一无所获
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.31,0:06:11.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们倾向于认为他或许已经逃出了钢圈
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.34,0:06:13.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也可能已经死了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.06,0:06:15.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为他作为一个在逃的西方人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.79,0:06:17.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他可能轻易地落入
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.27,0:06:19.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好战组织  信念兄弟会手中
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.25,0:06:22.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  祸害我国的恐怖组织之一
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.26,0:06:23.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有这一个
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.16,0:06:26.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是由你们前将军之一拉尚·努里领导的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.19,0:06:28.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  给我们造成了更深的伤害
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.73,0:06:30.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但德尔加多是个非常聪明的人  对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.46,0:06:32.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得他是否会在安全区外铤而走险呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.23,0:06:34.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯一让他敢这么做的原因
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.31,0:06:35.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是他确切知道哪里可以让他躲藏
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.98,0:06:36.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一小段时间
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.68,0:06:39.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许贾维斯探员是对的  但以我的经验
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.68,0:06:44.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穷途之人总会做出极端的决定
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.20,0:06:48.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我和塞格尔探员要检视案发现场了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.36,0:06:50.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西蒙斯探员会去推测嫌疑人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.88,0:06:53.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从居住区逃跑后的潜在路线
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.74,0:06:54.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.70,0:06:58.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还需要将克丽·洛德尔和阿伦·萨布里的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.19,0:07:00.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尸体运回  以便贾维斯探员
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.03,0:07:02.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能进行补充尸检
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.56,0:07:04.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会安排调度的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.99,0:07:07.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,组长  你之前提到的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.41,0:07:10.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果没记错  那个可吉基的外交部长
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.16,0:07:12.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是请国际反应小组来协助
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.37,0:07:14.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这起案件的人之一  对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.76,0:07:15.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  没错
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.68,0:07:17.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是否
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.52,0:07:20.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,承认并且尊重当地政府  里法伊长官
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.87,0:07:23.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在此次调查中的主导地位呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.99,0:07:28.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,副主任  国际反应小组的职责一直都是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.16,0:07:30.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在此双尸案的调查中
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.90,0:07:33.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为里法伊长官和国家警察提供建议和协助
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.96,0:07:36.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且追捕在逃的爱德华·德尔加多
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.98,0:07:40.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在许多建议和协助
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.20,0:07:41.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是基于你们团队
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.68,0:07:45.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,建立的犯罪嫌疑人的行为侧写
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.24,0:07:46.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是吗  -没错
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.97,0:07:50.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴恩斯助理主任指出过
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.40,0:07:52.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塞格尔探员熟悉这位
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.00,0:07:55.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者说过分熟悉这位
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.03,0:07:58.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特殊人物  德尔加多先生
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.18,0:08:00.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塞格尔探员在调查中并未表现出
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.52,0:08:01.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,任何偏袒
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.79,0:08:05.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事实上  她对德尔加多过去行为的了解
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.71,0:08:08.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是帮我们更深入地研究在克丽·洛德尔
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.55,0:08:10.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死亡现场发现的证据
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.50,0:08:20.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全球策略开发不是来帮你们部门
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.62,0:08:22.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提升技术安全的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.54,0:08:25.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  我们的一些工作人员认识受害者
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.96,0:08:27.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有德尔加多先生
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.90,0:08:29.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们有见过这两人公开在一起活动吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.92,0:08:30.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.11,0:08:34.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你的理论不是情侣争吵然后恶性发展吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.75,0:08:37.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在保安截堵到德尔加多前
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.62,0:08:38.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他还曾用无线电请求增援
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.90,0:08:42.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时是凌晨两点  他听见屋里有尖叫声
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.63,0:08:44.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随后他就从这里追着嫌疑人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.55,0:08:47.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后将他逼到了走廊尽头的阳台
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.51,0:08:50.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但德尔加多打倒了他
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.15,0:08:51.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也不能说明这两人之间
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.93,0:08:53.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-有亲密关系  -我同意
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.70,0:08:57.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这更可能像是一次性骚扰
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.56,0:08:59.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随后升级成了谋杀
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.46,0:09:01.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看这狂怒的痕迹
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.28,0:09:05.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  过度杀戮  因为一些个人原因
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.16,0:09:09.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你发现什么了吗  梅
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.27,0:09:12.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发现克丽的毒检结果非常奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.46,0:09:14.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她体内有镇静剂
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.59,0:09:16.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但没有任何医生给她开过这种药
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.70,0:09:18.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且药量非常之高
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.49,0:09:20.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她像是被迫注射了镇定剂
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.06,0:09:23.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此外  克丽身上没有任何防卫伤痕
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.29,0:09:24.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你认为克丽被下药了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.95,0:09:26.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后被刺死
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.20,0:09:28.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从我的角度看是这样的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.12,0:09:30.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那第二个受害者  阿伦·萨布里呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.73,0:09:32.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死因是钝力损伤
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.77,0:09:35.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与被抛下阳台的说法一致
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.05,0:09:36.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但遗憾的是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.49,0:09:38.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死后损伤让我很难确认
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.12,0:09:40.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪些伤痕是因为受害者
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.39,0:09:42.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与嫌疑人搏斗留下的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.38,0:09:46.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且我还不清楚他的手上为什么会有擦伤
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.43,0:09:47.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}尸检报告  阿伦·萨布里
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.84,0:09:48.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是我了解到的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.99,0:09:50.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  梅
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.32,0:09:52.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰克  这里没有什么能确认或否认
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.97,0:09:54.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这两人之间存在亲密关系
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.86,0:09:56.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也无法证明他们之间
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.43,0:09:58.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底有过怎样的关系
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.09,0:09:59.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能造成这样凄惨的变故
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.11,0:10:02.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许他的房间能给我们更多信息
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.52,0:10:04.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能吧  但我认为需要对克丽·洛德尔
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.69,0:10:06.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进行更深入的受害者分析
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.88,0:10:08.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看看她的纪念物
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.16,0:10:10.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她显然在不同的人中都很受欢迎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.93,0:10:12.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们中的任何人都能对她
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.40,0:10:14.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发展出扭曲的渴慕之情
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.16,0:10:16.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从而激发出这场暴力案件
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.21,0:10:19.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让蒙蒂跟进下
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.44,0:10:22.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说  你们调查的下一步行动
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.74,0:10:24.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是根据塞格尔探员的建议来的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.65,0:10:28.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  进行受害者分析是我们侧写的一步
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.81,0:10:31.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但根据你的描述  塞格尔探员说
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.62,0:10:34.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,深入的受害者分析能让德尔加多洗掉嫌疑
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.20,0:10:35.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才没这么说  你一直都在
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.98,0:10:37.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扭曲我说过的话
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.29,0:10:38.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只想确认清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.33,0:10:39.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在有意整我们小组
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.91,0:10:41.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是这么做的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.30,0:10:43.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-可能我们该休息一下  -我认为不用
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.78,0:10:46.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我觉得需要休息了  -阿伦和克丽
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.65,0:10:49.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是这起案件仅有的受害人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.34,0:10:51.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一位平民嫌犯也死了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.80,0:10:54.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是因为国际反应小组的莽撞行为
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.14,0:10:56.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认为我有意整国际反应小组
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.75,0:11:00.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰克·加勒特组长  我就跟你明说吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.82,0:11:02.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等今天工作完成了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.12,0:11:04.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会动用全部力量将国际反应小组
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.54,0:11:06.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彻底粉碎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.02,0:11:08.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并将灰烬四散入风
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.34,0:11:22.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实可以  更好一点
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.86,0:11:27.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-进展挺顺利  -因为你并不认为
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.27,0:11:30.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样自揭底牌后  会很难证明
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.45,0:11:32.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,存在偏见
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.56,0:11:34.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该轻声而动
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.24,0:11:35.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.27,0:11:37.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  这不仅是讯问
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.90,0:11:40.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是政治棋局
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.64,0:11:41.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你喜欢下棋吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.01,0:11:43.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢拳击
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.78,0:11:47.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看出来了  我就很喜欢下棋
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.52,0:11:51.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,需要沉得住气  擅用策略
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.30,0:11:53.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,懂得人性的弱点
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.07,0:11:55.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说总能驱王使后
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.89,0:11:57.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对你的打气鼓劲并非不感激
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.41,0:11:58.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我不想要
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.72,0:12:01.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷静  我是想保护你
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.55,0:12:04.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且如果你真的想实现公正
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.56,0:12:07.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要收集也只收集事实
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.70,0:12:10.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剩下的就交给当权者
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.03,0:12:29.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用我提醒你
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.97,0:12:32.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,房里没人被捕吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.16,0:12:33.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以如果不介意
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.17,0:12:35.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要活动下腿脚  倒杯咖啡
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.53,0:12:39.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁有想要的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.50,0:12:41.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太荒谬了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.65,0:12:44.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想现在最好还是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.10,0:12:46.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要交流
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.17,0:12:47.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们在房间装了窃听器吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.96,0:12:49.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要装窃听器呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.47,0:12:52.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为尽管我们并没有被捕
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.95,0:12:55.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我们相互之间禁止讨论
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.26,0:12:56.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,任何本案相关的事
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.82,0:12:58.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难以置信  我们能有什么打算
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.76,0:13:00.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐在这儿合伙编故事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.61,0:13:02.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这正是他们的想法
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.35,0:13:04.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使只是串供的表现
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.45,0:13:06.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也可能导致停工  甚至是起诉
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.73,0:13:17.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  凯伦和孩子们怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.45,0:13:19.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得了吧  别说废话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.81,0:13:22.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  伙计  真是粗暴
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.02,0:13:25.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你要记住  有我支持你
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.06,0:13:26.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不需要你支持
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.26,0:13:29.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰克  你自己也听到那女人的话了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.36,0:13:32.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关键不在于谁对谁错
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.51,0:13:34.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是谁来担罪
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.21,0:13:36.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沃尔特  我们所有行动都是照规定来的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.65,0:13:40.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  杰克  但有人死了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.09,0:13:43.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以不管有没有照规定来  有人犯了错
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.90,0:13:46.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只希望那个人不是你
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.00,0:13:49.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我的讯问还没结束
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.74,0:13:50.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没有
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.07,0:13:54.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你和巴恩斯需要中场休息
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.18,0:13:56.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  失陪
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.93,0:14:05.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塞格尔探员  三年前你曾请假
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.80,0:14:08.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没错  -为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.35,0:14:12.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-为什么  -没错  那是个问题
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.31,0:14:14.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我恐怕不明白你的意思
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.59,0:14:17.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你面前就是我的个人档案
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.52,0:14:19.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你十分清楚我告假的原因
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.74,0:14:22.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  我确实知道
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.87,0:14:26.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真可惜  我想自己这些审讯员的花招
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.32,0:14:29.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在你这种法医心理学专家面前
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.94,0:14:31.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根本玩不起来  是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.51,0:14:33.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请你一定要包容
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.13,0:14:36.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者你也可以选择不回答该问题
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.18,0:14:38.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那可能透露出你的心智状况
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.38,0:14:39.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.28,0:14:43.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想玩游戏  我奉陪
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.66,0:14:45.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三年前
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.26,0:14:49.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我丈夫  特别督察探员布拉德·塞格尔
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.90,0:14:52.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在执行公务时被害
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.52,0:14:56.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我因为丧夫而告假
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.74,0:15:02.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,节哀顺变
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.31,0:15:04.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.72,0:15:08.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因丧夫休假期间  你去往世界各地
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.11,0:15:10.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我想集中于三年前
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.86,0:15:12.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在缅甸那段
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.76,0:15:17.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当时你和爱德华·德尔加多十分熟络
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.32,0:15:18.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该男子后来也成为
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.78,0:15:20.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡利叶调查中的重点
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.62,0:15:22.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而他和你的复杂关系
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.81,0:15:24.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-使贵团队产生偏见  -这么说不对
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.16,0:15:27.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽管我个人了解德尔加多
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.50,0:15:30.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我们团队仍不含偏见将此人视为逃犯
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.38,0:15:31.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进行追捕
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.16,0:15:33.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且蒙哥马利探员还联系了他的妻子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.91,0:15:36.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来多加了解他可能的逃亡去向
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.25,0:15:44.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蒙哥马利探员  过去二十四小时
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.74,0:15:46.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都联系不上我丈夫
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.64,0:15:49.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-德尔加多夫人  -请叫我阿米莉娅
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.37,0:15:52.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿米莉娅  请坐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.64,0:15:59.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全球战略开发的居住区发了生意外事件
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.03,0:16:00.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有两人被害
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.29,0:16:03.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一位是你丈夫的女同事克丽·洛德尔
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.11,0:16:06.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,另一位是叫阿伦·萨布里的保安
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.76,0:16:10.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你丈夫也失踪了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.90,0:16:11.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失踪
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.00,0:16:14.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么意思  失踪
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.47,0:16:15.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿米莉娅  你最近一次
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.64,0:16:17.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和丈夫联系是什么时候
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.09,0:16:19.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他昨天早上给我发了电子邮件
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.59,0:16:20.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.55,0:16:22.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么  只是几张照片
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.55,0:16:23.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能给我看看吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.10,0:16:35.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在国外的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.92,0:16:37.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩多久联系一次
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.18,0:16:40.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每周一次  主要通过邮件
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.64,0:16:44.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定很难熬  对你们俩来说
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.51,0:16:47.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我为什么感觉你真正想问的是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.83,0:16:50.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有没有觉得丈夫跟克丽有染
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.51,0:16:53.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有这个可能吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.35,0:16:55.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  没可能
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.14,0:16:58.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他发照片给我以便我认识他的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.79,0:16:59.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仅此而已
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.94,0:17:01.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.92,0:17:05.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你丈夫最近有承受不同寻常的压力吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.12,0:17:08.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没  据我所知没有
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.57,0:17:11.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是个好人  他跟所有人都相处融洽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.55,0:17:16.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发誓  他绝对不会伤害任何人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.42,0:17:18.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德尔加多的妻子给了我权限
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.77,0:17:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,登入她丈夫的社交媒体
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.00,0:17:22.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我正在检查当中  但老实说
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.00,0:17:24.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿米莉娅似乎非常了解她的丈夫
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.09,0:17:26.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以如果他跟克丽没有婚外情
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.00,0:17:27.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那他的杀人动机是什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.74,0:17:29.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是德尔加多没有杀害克丽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.36,0:17:30.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那他为什么袭击保安
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.64,0:17:31.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他为什么逃跑
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.74,0:17:33.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这带来了一个更加迫切的问题
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.98,0:17:36.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱德华·德尔加多到底在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.42,0:17:39.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  不管犯罪与否  他并非惯犯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.42,0:17:41.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他人生地不熟
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.01,0:17:42.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像梅之前说的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.64,0:17:44.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他能够逃出钢圈
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.94,0:17:46.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因为他知道在另一边
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.94,0:17:48.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许有人能保护他
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.86,0:17:50.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好像有发现
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.43,0:17:52.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德尔加多似乎跟
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.32,0:17:54.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他第一位翻译的家人很亲近
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.41,0:17:56.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,年轻人名叫奥马尔·塔汗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.33,0:17:57.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}全球策略开发  奥马尔·塔汗  翻译
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.67,0:17:58.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  塞格尔探员
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.09,0:17:59.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个年轻人叫什么名字
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.66,0:18:00.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奥马尔·塔汗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.84,0:18:03.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他给德尔加多当了两周翻译
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.25,0:18:04.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到把职责交给了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.28,0:18:06.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可吉基国家警察的一名警官
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.08,0:18:08.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么移交工作呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.00,0:18:09.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德尔加多的工作使他
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.32,0:18:11.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接触到可吉基国家警察的保密通讯
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.80,0:18:15.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而塔汗先生没有得到权限
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.65,0:18:17.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们确认了塔汗先生的身份后
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.78,0:18:19.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和你的团队接着做了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.67,0:18:21.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们前往塔汗的家
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.54,0:18:24.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,距离钢圈西北方一千六百米的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.90,0:18:27.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们发现德尔加多先生就躲在了那里
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.72,0:18:29.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他有反抗吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.19,0:18:32.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  他没有  他毫无抵抗地接受拘留
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.44,0:18:34.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塞格尔探员  是谁决定
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.67,0:18:36.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把爱德华·德尔加多转移
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.26,0:18:37.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回国际反应小组的飞机
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.70,0:18:40.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而非直接把他带给可吉基国家警察拘留呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.99,0:18:43.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是加勒特组长的决定
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.19,0:18:46.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你记得自己质疑过那个决定吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.87,0:18:48.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不  -你不记得  还是...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.98,0:18:51.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不  我没有质疑  -你支持吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.10,0:18:53.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  当时德尔加多是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.70,0:18:55.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,国际反应小组和可吉基国家警察
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.33,0:18:57.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,联合调查中的疑犯
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.49,0:18:59.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加勒特组长有权
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.63,0:19:01.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把疑犯带到飞机中审讯
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.92,0:19:05.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谁审讯他的  -是我
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.59,0:19:20.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得告诉我  爱德
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.25,0:19:24.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得告诉我在公寓里
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.70,0:19:26.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟保安发生了什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.84,0:19:29.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么逃走
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.63,0:19:33.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟她有发生关系吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.31,0:19:36.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.55,0:19:40.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老实说  我觉得你绝对不会背叛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.78,0:19:42.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你孩子的母亲
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.98,0:19:46.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想回家
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.59,0:19:49.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对天发誓  不是我做的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.79,0:19:52.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  所以让我帮你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.51,0:19:54.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你不懂  你帮不了的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.95,0:19:59.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这太疯狂了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.12,0:20:03.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在这里  走进我的生活
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.02,0:20:04.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像你以前那样
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.57,0:20:07.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了"拯救"我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.09,0:20:18.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我认为我们拯救了彼此
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.92,0:20:20.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.30,0:20:25.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我依然清楚记得  你告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.63,0:20:27.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在一起是个错误的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.22,0:20:29.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的感情到了哪一步
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.74,0:20:32.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但不可思议的是
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.59,0:20:37.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是你没有离开我  我就不会回家
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.81,0:20:39.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就不会结婚  而且
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.37,0:20:43.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我生命里就不会有宝贝女儿  朱莉娅
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.19,0:20:47.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  我现在就不会在这里帮你
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.78,0:20:49.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得相信我  爱德
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.09,0:20:51.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事实上
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.01,0:20:55.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世界上我只相信
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.73,0:20:57.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个人  克拉拉
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.56,0:21:01.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克拉拉  杰克刚和里法伊队长通完电话
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.74,0:21:03.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他要求我们把他转送给可吉基国家警察拘留
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.88,0:21:05.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可吉基国家警察  不  慢着
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.56,0:21:08.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是被联调局逮捕的美国公民
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.44,0:21:09.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们为什么不能拘留我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.86,0:21:12.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都会没事的  爱德
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.02,0:21:14.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的团队和我会一路陪着你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.30,0:21:15.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是联合调查
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.89,0:21:17.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实  把他带到这里
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.27,0:21:19.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比把他带回钢圈更方便
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.13,0:21:21.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然我就得和里法伊队长
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.17,0:21:22.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,协调安全协议
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.22,0:21:23.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  我帮他做准备
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.02,0:21:27.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安全协议
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.95,0:21:29.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种加密通讯方式
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.92,0:21:31.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在可吉基国家警察和国际反应小组
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.98,0:21:34.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,转交犯人之前  期间和之后使用
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.57,0:21:36.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我说得对吗  -对
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.61,0:21:39.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  特别督查探员西蒙斯
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.49,0:21:41.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们能倒回去吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.77,0:21:44.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你接到里法伊队长的电话
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.25,0:21:45.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他让你把人交给他
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.25,0:21:49.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能告诉我接下来本该发生什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.73,0:21:52.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原计划是国际反应小组将犯人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.32,0:21:55.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,押送回钢圈内的可吉基国家警察总部
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.21,0:21:56.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们本来要走由里法伊长官
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.83,0:21:58.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安排的安全线路
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.44,0:22:00.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行动的首要目标
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.07,0:22:01.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是避开机场
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.73,0:22:03.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与钢圈之间的主干道
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.91,0:22:06.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  因为他们把那条路叫什么来着
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.00,0:22:07.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"诅咒之路"
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.45,0:22:08.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西蒙斯探员
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.15,0:22:09.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们知道之后本该发生什么
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.69,0:22:12.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-告诉我们实际是什么情况  -我们被
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.38,0:22:15.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忠于信念兄弟会的战士伏击了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.90,0:22:17.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道你们怎么成为攻击目标的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.17,0:22:18.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.31,0:22:21.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  这是随机的攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.90,0:22:22.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随机的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.73,0:22:25.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并不是随机的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.56,0:22:27.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们被发现是因为
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.21,0:22:29.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你用公开线路进行通讯时暴露了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.61,0:22:33.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能  我亲自加密了线路
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.94,0:22:39.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你告诉我  先生
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.80,0:22:42.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是失职  还是叛徒
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.51,0:22:47.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为电子记录显示并没有加密
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.61,0:22:53.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些日志肯定不是真的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.62,0:22:55.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些日志来自可吉基国家警察的服务器
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.42,0:22:59.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伏击过程中发生了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.76,0:23:01.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们采取了躲避策略
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.48,0:23:03.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一刻  我们被迫离开道路
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.20,0:23:05.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紧接着发生了交火
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.58,0:23:08.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,犯人在交火时中枪
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.24,0:23:10.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你害德尔加多中枪了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.88,0:23:12.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在那时我们作出决定
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.66,0:23:13.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原路返回飞机
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.96,0:23:16.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谁做的决定  -加勒特组长
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.16,0:23:19.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我们救德尔加多唯一的机会
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.34,0:23:21.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是你们组长的医疗建议
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.29,0:23:24.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是他的外勤法医  梅·贾维斯探员的建议
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.55,0:23:25.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.74,0:23:27.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当时忙着带大家脱离险境
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.69,0:23:29.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我们回飞机后发生了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.18,0:23:32.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德尔加多胸部中枪
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.00,0:23:34.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这里  -我把他从车里拉出来
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.44,0:23:36.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我正准备帮忙将他搬进会议室
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.94,0:23:38.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在那时他们试图登机
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.65,0:23:41.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"他们"就是兄弟会的人
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.92,0:23:44.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  克拉拉和梅以及其他机组成员
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.56,0:23:46.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将德尔加多带离交火区
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.04,0:23:47.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  把他放在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.72,0:23:48.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.66,0:23:51.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克拉拉  把他的防弹背心脱下来
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.75,0:23:52.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.43,0:23:54.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当时一片混乱
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.76,0:24:01.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰克和我抵挡住了他们的攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.51,0:24:03.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克拉拉和梅抢救德尔加多
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.51,0:24:05.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得给他供氧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.67,0:24:07.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再紧点
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.62,0:24:10.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他人都没受伤吗
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.49,0:24:11.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.75,0:24:14.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德尔加多是唯一一个中枪的人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.85,0:24:15.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.87,0:24:19.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们尽力关上了货舱门
Dialogue: 0,0:24:24.87,0:24:28.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你们没能保住德尔加多的命  是不是
Dialogue: 0,0:24:28.40,0:24:30.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  坚持住  拜托
Dialogue: 0,0:24:32.32,0:24:33.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梅
Dialogue: 0,0:24:33.44,0:24:34.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坚持住  爱德华
Dialogue: 0,0:24:38.64,0:24:40.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我该怎么做  该怎么做
Dialogue: 0,0:24:44.18,0:24:45.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梅
Dialogue: 0,0:24:45.61,0:24:46.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他死了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:55.16,0:24:56.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:25:02.54,0:25:04.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们好像在重新集结  杰克
Dialogue: 0,0:25:04.29,0:25:06.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能在呼叫增援
Dialogue: 0,0:25:06.04,0:25:07.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不会认为
Dialogue: 0,0:25:07.16,0:25:07.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们想要登机吧
Dialogue: 0,0:25:07.93,0:25:09.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不想发生那种事
Dialogue: 0,0:25:10.12,0:25:12.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里法伊长官  你保证的增援呢
Dialogue: 0,0:25:12.60,0:25:14.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们现在正在路上
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.66,0:25:16.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特别督查探员贾维斯  加勒特组长
Dialogue: 0,0:25:16.82,0:25:18.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,命令小组返回飞机的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:25:18.32,0:25:20.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道德尔加多先生的全部伤势状况吗
Dialogue: 0,0:25:20.63,0:25:22.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发现了一处枪伤
Dialogue: 0,0:25:22.99,0:25:24.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在他的右上侧胸部
Dialogue: 0,0:25:24.81,0:25:28.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我推测他的肺部受损
Dialogue: 0,0:25:28.25,0:25:29.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你对命令提出质疑了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:25:29.81,0:25:33.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没有  -你面前的伤者胸部中枪
Dialogue: 0,0:25:33.08,0:25:36.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你却没有坚持改道去拥有战地医院的
Dialogue: 0,0:25:36.25,0:25:37.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美军格拉纳托驻地吗
Dialogue: 0,0:25:37.86,0:25:39.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我没有  因为
Dialogue: 0,0:25:40.04,0:25:42.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事实上  我知道飞机上的设备
Dialogue: 0,0:25:42.39,0:25:45.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能够稳定他的情况  而其他选择
Dialogue: 0,0:25:45.73,0:25:47.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是未知且充满变数的
Dialogue: 0,0:25:47.36,0:25:49.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且这一切是我们被敌人攻击时发生的
Dialogue: 0,0:25:50.66,0:25:52.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  当时情况很危急
Dialogue: 0,0:25:52.13,0:25:54.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是的  -也许这就能解释为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:25:54.97,0:25:58.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从医学院毕业后  你没有做外科医生
Dialogue: 0,0:25:58.01,0:26:00.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是成为了一名法医
Dialogue: 0,0:26:01.16,0:26:02.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:26:02.91,0:26:05.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你记得一位
Dialogue: 0,0:26:05.66,0:26:08.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫迪伦·雅各布斯的年轻人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:26:09.68,0:26:12.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得  我记得迪伦
Dialogue: 0,0:26:12.77,0:26:16.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他入院的那晚  你是圣柯莱特
Dialogue: 0,0:26:16.45,0:26:17.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外伤治疗中心的住院医生
Dialogue: 0,0:26:17.50,0:26:19.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你记得他发生了什么事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:26:19.89,0:26:21.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得  他死在了手术台上
Dialogue: 0,0:26:22.25,0:26:25.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的家人认为是你和贾斯汀·怀亚特医生
Dialogue: 0,0:26:25.11,0:26:26.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及医院的疏忽大意造成他死亡
Dialogue: 0,0:26:26.84,0:26:28.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们提起了诉讼
Dialogue: 0,0:26:28.57,0:26:30.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那起诉讼庭外和解了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:31.45,0:26:33.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,签订了保密协议
Dialogue: 0,0:26:33.17,0:26:36.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意思是你无法透露你是否觉得
Dialogue: 0,0:26:36.96,0:26:39.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己应该对雅各布斯的死负责吗
Dialogue: 0,0:26:47.90,0:26:50.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰克  我很抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:26:50.99,0:26:52.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本该把一切都告诉你的
Dialogue: 0,0:26:52.38,0:26:54.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的  克拉拉
Dialogue: 0,0:26:54.05,0:26:55.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把该告诉的都告诉我了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:58.46,0:26:59.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两位  听着
Dialogue: 0,0:26:59.51,0:27:01.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道我们不该交谈
Dialogue: 0,0:27:01.75,0:27:03.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但事情有点不对劲
Dialogue: 0,0:27:03.63,0:27:06.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴恩斯和阿特伍德基本上把伏击的事
Dialogue: 0,0:27:06.48,0:27:07.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都怪在我头上
Dialogue: 0,0:27:08.06,0:27:10.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们说我没有加密通讯线路
Dialogue: 0,0:27:10.99,0:27:12.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们还提供了证据
Dialogue: 0,0:27:12.32,0:27:15.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来自可吉基国家警察指挥所的电子日志
Dialogue: 0,0:27:15.41,0:27:17.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我  那些日志肯定被篡改了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:17.65,0:27:18.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但按理来说
Dialogue: 0,0:27:18.37,0:27:20.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有可吉基国家警察内部的人
Dialogue: 0,0:27:20.01,0:27:21.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-才能做到  -没错
Dialogue: 0,0:27:21.76,0:27:23.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克拉拉  我觉得你一开始就是对的
Dialogue: 0,0:27:23.99,0:27:26.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德尔加多从来都不符合克丽凶手的侧写
Dialogue: 0,0:27:28.25,0:27:30.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问题是  他为什么要跑
Dialogue: 0,0:27:31.05,0:27:32.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许他不相信当地警方
Dialogue: 0,0:27:33.09,0:27:37.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许吧  德尔加多的工作重点是提高
Dialogue: 0,0:27:37.47,0:27:39.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可吉基国家警察的网络安全
Dialogue: 0,0:27:39.52,0:27:41.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以如果他无意中发现了一些
Dialogue: 0,0:27:41.33,0:27:42.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不该发现的东西呢
Dialogue: 0,0:27:43.00,0:27:45.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个秘密  一个如此危险的秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:27:45.42,0:27:47.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以至于可吉基国家警察内部的人
Dialogue: 0,0:27:47.25,0:27:49.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不惜将谋杀案嫁祸给他
Dialogue: 0,0:27:49.96,0:27:51.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  还有一件事
Dialogue: 0,0:27:51.75,0:27:54.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道那个保安  阿伦·萨布里吗
Dialogue: 0,0:27:54.24,0:27:57.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}阿伦·萨布里\N安保团队
Dialogue: 0,0:27:54.28,0:27:56.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在全球策略开发做保安只是他的副业
Dialogue: 0,0:27:56.29,0:27:59.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的主要工作是可吉基国家警察的巡警
Dialogue: 0,0:27:59.44,0:28:00.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得他手上的擦伤吗
Dialogue: 0,0:28:00.93,0:28:02.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些梅无法解释的擦伤
Dialogue: 0,0:28:01.09,0:28:02.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}尸检报告
Dialogue: 0,0:28:03.26,0:28:05.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果擦伤不是因为和德尔加多扭打呢
Dialogue: 0,0:28:05.46,0:28:07.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果那是在一遍又一遍
Dialogue: 0,0:28:07.44,0:28:08.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刺伤克丽时产生的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:28:08.58,0:28:11.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你认为最初的计划是保安杀死克丽
Dialogue: 0,0:28:11.81,0:28:15.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后在德尔加多企图逃跑时杀了他
Dialogue: 0,0:28:15.37,0:28:17.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过德尔加多没让他得逞
Dialogue: 0,0:28:17.66,0:28:19.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很可惜  虽然听起来很合理
Dialogue: 0,0:28:19.94,0:28:21.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这仍然只是推测
Dialogue: 0,0:28:21.43,0:28:23.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  鉴于我们现在的状态
Dialogue: 0,0:28:23.32,0:28:24.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们需要确凿的证据证明
Dialogue: 0,0:28:24.66,0:28:27.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可吉基国家警察内部的人是幕后黑手
Dialogue: 0,0:28:27.67,0:28:29.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不确定在被剥夺一切的情况下
Dialogue: 0,0:28:29.87,0:28:32.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还能证明什么
Dialogue: 0,0:28:33.20,0:28:34.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许并不是一切
Dialogue: 0,0:28:35.29,0:28:36.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果德尔加多的事我们没猜错
Dialogue: 0,0:28:36.88,0:28:38.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他确实发现了可吉基国家警察的肮脏秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:28:38.84,0:28:40.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他还是我印象中的那个人
Dialogue: 0,0:28:40.94,0:28:42.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他会将证据藏起来
Dialogue: 0,0:28:43.00,0:28:44.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:28:44.20,0:28:46.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他有可能将发现的证据
Dialogue: 0,0:28:46.21,0:28:48.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发给了这世上他唯一信任的人
Dialogue: 0,0:29:02.49,0:29:04.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你还好吗  -还好
Dialogue: 0,0:29:11.08,0:29:12.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们只是和我们玩心理游戏
Dialogue: 0,0:29:12.92,0:29:14.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要摧毁我们的意志
Dialogue: 0,0:29:15.49,0:29:17.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  那他们真的很厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:29:17.09,0:29:19.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我已经无力招架了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:20.97,0:29:22.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都会没事的
Dialogue: 0,0:29:24.06,0:29:25.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不在乎别人怎么说
Dialogue: 0,0:29:25.46,0:29:29.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但当别人的性命在你手上
Dialogue: 0,0:29:30.07,0:29:32.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就能感受到责任的重量
Dialogue: 0,0:29:34.23,0:29:37.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  你表面上能装作很坚强
Dialogue: 0,0:29:38.06,0:29:41.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我觉得我永远都学不会如何
Dialogue: 0,0:29:42.35,0:29:44.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能将自己的情感控制自如
Dialogue: 0,0:29:45.81,0:29:47.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果那个人最终没活下来
Dialogue: 0,0:29:49.92,0:29:51.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你永远都会质疑自己
Dialogue: 0,0:30:00.31,0:30:02.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蒙哥马利探员  请你回想一下
Dialogue: 0,0:30:02.92,0:30:07.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德尔加多先生死后发生的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:30:07.88,0:30:11.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你记不记得接到了前方的求救电话
Dialogue: 0,0:30:11.74,0:30:12.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得
Dialogue: 0,0:30:12.76,0:30:14.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老大  怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:14.18,0:30:15.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们有麻烦了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:15.14,0:30:16.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们被兄弟会伏击了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:16.89,0:30:18.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一人遇难  看起来
Dialogue: 0,0:30:18.85,0:30:20.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们想要登机
Dialogue: 0,0:30:20.17,0:30:21.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  我立刻联系可吉基国家警察
Dialogue: 0,0:30:21.69,0:30:23.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我试过了  他们鞭长莫及
Dialogue: 0,0:30:23.24,0:30:24.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在得立刻联系
Dialogue: 0,0:30:24.67,0:30:26.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美军格拉纳托驻地的装甲部队
Dialogue: 0,0:30:28.57,0:30:32.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么无视加勒特组长的直接命令
Dialogue: 0,0:30:32.02,0:30:34.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有无视  我评估了局势
Dialogue: 0,0:30:34.34,0:30:36.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,查看了地图  他们也太远了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:36.65,0:30:39.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许你可以告诉我们
Dialogue: 0,0:30:39.23,0:30:42.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是什么时候知道
Dialogue: 0,0:30:42.10,0:30:45.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Z-TAC夜鹰S-2的存在的
Dialogue: 0,0:30:45.64,0:30:49.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能告诉你一个不存在的项目  对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:30:49.15,0:30:50.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你肯定觉得自己聪明极了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:50.58,0:30:53.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认为夜鹰S-2是美国情报界
Dialogue: 0,0:30:53.27,0:30:54.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人尽皆知的秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:30:55.09,0:30:57.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是杰克·加勒特命令你黑进
Dialogue: 0,0:30:57.69,0:30:58.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夜鹰系统的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:30:58.98,0:31:00.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是
Dialogue: 0,0:31:00.48,0:31:02.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-现在什么情况  -他们在撞门
Dialogue: 0,0:31:02.56,0:31:03.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰克  依我看来
Dialogue: 0,0:31:03.93,0:31:06.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你唯一的选择就是立刻起飞
Dialogue: 0,0:31:06.04,0:31:07.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这我可能无法做到
Dialogue: 0,0:31:07.58,0:31:09.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他们把我们包围了  -不会很久
Dialogue: 0,0:31:15.11,0:31:16.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蒙哥马利探员
Dialogue: 0,0:31:15.23,0:31:16.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}全球无人机控制系统
Dialogue: 0,0:31:16.45,0:31:18.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道盗用并损毁
Dialogue: 0,0:31:18.95,0:31:24.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一架1.64亿美元的无人机是什么后果吗
Dialogue: 0,0:31:24.45,0:31:26.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无意冒犯  1.64亿美元
Dialogue: 0,0:31:26.19,0:31:28.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是包括项目的研发费用
Dialogue: 0,0:31:28.26,0:31:31.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一架无人机的价格是374万美元
Dialogue: 0,0:31:31.98,0:31:34.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得这是开玩笑吗
Dialogue: 0,0:31:34.13,0:31:36.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  你想知道我有没有偷无人机
Dialogue: 0,0:31:37.02,0:31:40.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我偷了  我偷无人机是因为有武装分子
Dialogue: 0,0:31:40.16,0:31:42.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,追杀我的队友  所以我黑进了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:42.61,0:31:44.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,附近正在飞行的最近的监控无人机
Dialogue: 0,0:31:44.54,0:31:48.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用其扫射了飞机场  好几遍
Dialogue: 0,0:31:51.25,0:31:52.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还好那些信念兄弟会的人
Dialogue: 0,0:31:52.24,0:31:53.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常不擅长射飞靶
Dialogue: 0,0:31:53.59,0:31:54.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这样会
Dialogue: 0,0:31:54.77,0:31:56.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把他们的注意力从飞机那里吸引过来
Dialogue: 0,0:31:56.86,0:32:01.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我则是制造了一个374万美金的灯光秀
Dialogue: 0,0:32:02.26,0:32:03.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来让我的队友驾驶飞机起飞
Dialogue: 0,0:32:03.96,0:32:05.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逃出生天
Dialogue: 0,0:32:05.12,0:32:06.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道敌方的伤亡吗
Dialogue: 0,0:32:06.96,0:32:10.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没有伤亡  -当时你并不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:32:10.33,0:32:11.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白这事到头来
Dialogue: 0,0:32:11.89,0:32:13.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须要有人来担责
Dialogue: 0,0:32:13.23,0:32:14.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是事实是
Dialogue: 0,0:32:15.31,0:32:19.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有极少数的一部分被选中的人
Dialogue: 0,0:32:19.23,0:32:20.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是有资格在前线工作的
Dialogue: 0,0:32:21.37,0:32:22.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是无可辩驳的
Dialogue: 0,0:32:23.46,0:32:26.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们有更好的直觉  判断
Dialogue: 0,0:32:27.73,0:32:29.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:32:29.80,0:32:33.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这是必需的
Dialogue: 0,0:32:34.04,0:32:35.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为在情急之下
Dialogue: 0,0:32:36.10,0:32:37.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们要做出艰难的选择
Dialogue: 0,0:32:38.77,0:32:42.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得你是那少数被选中人之一吗
Dialogue: 0,0:32:45.26,0:32:46.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是觉得
Dialogue: 0,0:32:48.00,0:32:50.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是清楚知道  所以我做了那些事
Dialogue: 0,0:32:50.17,0:32:51.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次我还会这么做
Dialogue: 0,0:32:51.22,0:32:53.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我准备接受我的行为所带来的后果
Dialogue: 0,0:32:54.39,0:32:57.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好  蒙哥马利探员  因为
Dialogue: 0,0:32:58.13,0:32:59.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你由于故意盗窃
Dialogue: 0,0:32:59.64,0:33:01.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玩忽职守
Dialogue: 0,0:33:01.94,0:33:03.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和破坏政府财物而被捕了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:04.10,0:33:05.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交出你的警徽
Dialogue: 0,0:33:21.12,0:33:22.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  阿米莉亚
Dialogue: 0,0:33:24.01,0:33:26.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你来见我
Dialogue: 0,0:33:29.72,0:33:31.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和爱德之间无所不谈  克拉拉
Dialogue: 0,0:33:32.89,0:33:34.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天我来是因为我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:33:34.81,0:33:36.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是他的生命中很重要的一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:33:36.46,0:33:39.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我真的需要有人能为他
Dialogue: 0,0:33:39.02,0:33:40.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有克丽伸张正义
Dialogue: 0,0:33:41.15,0:33:42.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这正是我想要做的
Dialogue: 0,0:33:44.59,0:33:47.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以看看他给你发的照片吗
Dialogue: 0,0:33:56.63,0:33:57.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱德有这种习惯吗
Dialogue: 0,0:33:57.89,0:34:00.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会经常给你发他偷拍的快照
Dialogue: 0,0:34:00.35,0:34:02.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有  不过还好他发了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:06.24,0:34:08.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能把这些也给我发一份吗
Dialogue: 0,0:34:09.38,0:34:10.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:34:10.79,0:34:12.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿米莉亚  我和我的队友认为
Dialogue: 0,0:34:12.40,0:34:14.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱德是因为发现了一个秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:34:14.28,0:34:16.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而被陷害谋杀了克丽
Dialogue: 0,0:34:16.30,0:34:18.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我认为这些照片能告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:34:18.93,0:34:20.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秘密到底是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:34:24.81,0:34:26.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:34:27.59,0:34:29.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没事的  杰克  -不  有事
Dialogue: 0,0:34:29.76,0:34:33.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别插手  朋友  随它去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:34:33.09,0:34:34.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是按规章走的流程
Dialogue: 0,0:34:34.33,0:34:35.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罪名是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:34:35.26,0:34:36.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这重要吗  杰克
Dialogue: 0,0:34:36.42,0:34:38.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这已经是最糟的情况了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:38.17,0:34:39.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沃尔特  听我说
Dialogue: 0,0:34:39.27,0:34:40.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德尔加多是被陷害的
Dialogue: 0,0:34:40.86,0:34:42.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我或许有办法拿到证据
Dialogue: 0,0:34:42.61,0:34:44.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西格尔和西蒙斯探员正在...
Dialogue: 0,0:34:45.70,0:34:47.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西格尔和西蒙斯不能参与任何工作
Dialogue: 0,0:34:47.75,0:34:48.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:34:49.48,0:34:50.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死的  杰克
Dialogue: 0,0:34:50.57,0:34:52.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你又把你自己陷于不利
Dialogue: 0,0:34:52.67,0:34:54.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这可是违抗命令
Dialogue: 0,0:34:54.52,0:34:56.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是是  更不用说
Dialogue: 0,0:34:56.59,0:34:59.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有失联邦政府官员身份的行为了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:59.60,0:35:01.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把他带回楼上
Dialogue: 0,0:35:17.69,0:35:20.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请坐
Dialogue: 0,0:35:22.10,0:35:23.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加勒特组长
Dialogue: 0,0:35:23.20,0:35:25.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在今天的会谈过程中
Dialogue: 0,0:35:25.15,0:35:27.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是否与你的国际反应小组成员
Dialogue: 0,0:35:27.05,0:35:28.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有过交流
Dialogue: 0,0:35:28.81,0:35:30.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是的  -你是什么时候
Dialogue: 0,0:35:30.72,0:35:33.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在什么地方与他们进行的违规交流
Dialogue: 0,0:35:33.03,0:35:34.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我小组里的其他成员一样
Dialogue: 0,0:35:34.21,0:35:37.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要对德尔加多先生的死负责
Dialogue: 0,0:35:37.05,0:35:38.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我问的不是这个
Dialogue: 0,0:35:38.09,0:35:39.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我们在这里的原因
Dialogue: 0,0:35:39.24,0:35:40.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加勒特组长
Dialogue: 0,0:35:40.03,0:35:42.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,造成德尔加多先生死亡的真正原因
Dialogue: 0,0:35:43.30,0:35:44.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是背叛
Dialogue: 0,0:35:45.73,0:35:46.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:35:47.05,0:35:48.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是个好人  尽忠职守
Dialogue: 0,0:35:48.87,0:35:51.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只不过碰巧发现了一个秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:35:51.50,0:35:53.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他发现了可吉基国家警察
Dialogue: 0,0:35:53.63,0:35:55.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和信念兄弟会首脑之间的交易
Dialogue: 0,0:35:55.56,0:35:56.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是拉尚·努里
Dialogue: 0,0:35:57.76,0:35:59.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们出卖恐怖分子的名单
Dialogue: 0,0:35:59.83,0:36:01.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为交换  可吉基国家警察向努里保证
Dialogue: 0,0:36:01.69,0:36:02.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会对他们的犯罪行为
Dialogue: 0,0:36:02.62,0:36:04.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睁一只眼闭一只眼
Dialogue: 0,0:36:04.46,0:36:07.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这其中包括买卖可吉基儿童
Dialogue: 0,0:36:08.06,0:36:10.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么知道这些的
Dialogue: 0,0:36:10.19,0:36:12.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德尔加多遵循了规章制度
Dialogue: 0,0:36:12.01,0:36:14.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在卡利叶见了美国反贪调查员
Dialogue: 0,0:36:14.28,0:36:17.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提供了证据  不过为了回答你的问题
Dialogue: 0,0:36:17.23,0:36:21.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道这一切是由于德尔加多先生
Dialogue: 0,0:36:21.26,0:36:23.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还违反了规章
Dialogue: 0,0:36:23.70,0:36:26.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他还把一份证据副本用加密信息
Dialogue: 0,0:36:26.87,0:36:29.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藏在照片里发给了他的妻子
Dialogue: 0,0:36:30.95,0:36:32.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这一份
Dialogue: 0,0:36:36.14,0:36:39.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是说爱德华·德尔加多用了隐写术吗
Dialogue: 0,0:36:39.13,0:36:43.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  他用一份电子档案作为另一份的伪装
Dialogue: 0,0:36:43.00,0:36:45.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你继续翻后面那些图片
Dialogue: 0,0:36:45.39,0:36:47.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会找到行为分析部的技术分析员
Dialogue: 0,0:36:47.72,0:36:51.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佩内洛普·加西亚提供给我的加密信息
Dialogue: 0,0:36:51.32,0:36:52.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:36:54.68,0:36:57.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抛开这份证据不谈  你的行为...
Dialogue: 0,0:36:57.31,0:36:59.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这份证据证明了国际行动小组
Dialogue: 0,0:36:59.67,0:37:01.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和德尔加多一样是被陷害的
Dialogue: 0,0:37:02.01,0:37:02.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被陷害
Dialogue: 0,0:37:02.99,0:37:05.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  因为这份与魔鬼的协议
Dialogue: 0,0:37:05.80,0:37:07.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最有损名誉的部分是
Dialogue: 0,0:37:07.50,0:37:10.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一切都是在一位美国情报部门官员的
Dialogue: 0,0:37:10.71,0:37:12.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非法批准下进行的
Dialogue: 0,0:37:12.41,0:37:14.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是必须要陷害德尔加多的原因
Dialogue: 0,0:37:14.27,0:37:16.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是必须要伏击我的团队的原因
Dialogue: 0,0:37:16.51,0:37:19.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了保护这位代号为"象"的
Dialogue: 0,0:37:20.23,0:37:21.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,官员的身份
Dialogue: 0,0:37:22.18,0:37:24.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我必须要告诉你如果你指控
Dialogue: 0,0:37:24.99,0:37:26.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一位情报部门官员
Dialogue: 0,0:37:26.85,0:37:28.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而没有足够证据的话...
Dialogue: 0,0:37:28.27,0:37:30.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这才是关键所在  对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:37:30.46,0:37:32.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你生活在一个被谎言笼罩的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:37:32.93,0:37:34.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又何从找到真相
Dialogue: 0,0:37:35.69,0:37:38.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想这就是档案派上用场的时候了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:39.24,0:37:43.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能找到行为背后的动机
Dialogue: 0,0:37:43.36,0:37:45.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谎言背后的始作俑者
Dialogue: 0,0:37:47.35,0:37:48.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你已经知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:48.88,0:37:50.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些问题的答案  杰克
Dialogue: 0,0:37:50.26,0:37:52.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的确是知道的  琳达
Dialogue: 0,0:37:52.46,0:37:55.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先要好好想想谁会从中获益
Dialogue: 0,0:37:56.53,0:37:59.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,利用像努里这样现成的资源
Dialogue: 0,0:37:59.11,0:38:00.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁是最大的受益者
Dialogue: 0,0:38:00.99,0:38:03.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更重要的是  谁有这个胆量
Dialogue: 0,0:38:03.50,0:38:05.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敢和魔鬼做交易
Dialogue: 0,0:38:07.59,0:38:09.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个人肯定是心安理得地
Dialogue: 0,0:38:09.99,0:38:13.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将必要采取的恶行合理化
Dialogue: 0,0:38:13.00,0:38:15.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来保护更大的利益
Dialogue: 0,0:38:16.34,0:38:17.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个人一定是认为
Dialogue: 0,0:38:17.79,0:38:19.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果比过程更重要
Dialogue: 0,0:38:19.36,0:38:20.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:38:21.48,0:38:22.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你明白我在说什么吧
Dialogue: 0,0:38:23.90,0:38:28.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,象  所以这个人
Dialogue: 0,0:38:28.87,0:38:30.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能也很喜欢国际象棋吧
Dialogue: 0,0:38:30.37,0:38:33.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为在国际象棋中  象这个角色
Dialogue: 0,0:38:33.26,0:38:36.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,往往被视为阴险  狡猾
Dialogue: 0,0:38:37.86,0:38:39.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且堕落
Dialogue: 0,0:38:39.52,0:38:41.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你总能驱王使后
Dialogue: 0,0:38:43.69,0:38:45.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴恩斯助理主任
Dialogue: 0,0:38:45.20,0:38:48.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是我是你  我接下来会谨言慎行的
Dialogue: 0,0:38:49.02,0:38:51.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是这么打算的
Dialogue: 0,0:38:52.26,0:38:54.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿特伍德副主任  你被捕了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:54.21,0:38:55.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有权保持沉默
Dialogue: 0,0:38:55.98,0:38:57.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是来真的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:38:58.30,0:38:59.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰克的那套心理侧写
Dialogue: 0,0:38:59.98,0:39:01.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是一派胡言  算不上证据
Dialogue: 0,0:39:01.55,0:39:03.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是加西亚探员在你的私人服务器上
Dialogue: 0,0:39:03.33,0:39:06.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发现的邮件是证据  沃尔特
Dialogue: 0,0:39:07.56,0:39:10.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你根本不知道你做了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:39:10.59,0:39:12.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:39:12.84,0:39:14.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你害死了德尔加多
Dialogue: 0,0:39:14.71,0:39:16.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你让我的团队处于险境
Dialogue: 0,0:39:16.28,0:39:17.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把我们当成牺牲品
Dialogue: 0,0:39:17.35,0:39:19.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们就是牺牲品
Dialogue: 0,0:39:19.60,0:39:22.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你们是士兵  杰克  我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:39:22.13,0:39:24.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,士兵们会牺牲自己
Dialogue: 0,0:39:24.54,0:39:26.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来保护其他人
Dialogue: 0,0:39:26.45,0:39:29.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为我喜欢和努里这种混蛋同流合污吗
Dialogue: 0,0:39:29.80,0:39:32.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说得对  这就是必须采取的恶行
Dialogue: 0,0:39:32.68,0:39:33.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道为什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:39:33.28,0:39:36.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我们正处在战争中  朋友们
Dialogue: 0,0:39:36.06,0:39:38.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别搞错了  就是因为我们告诉大家
Dialogue: 0,0:39:38.12,0:39:40.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以一如既往地安居乐业
Dialogue: 0,0:39:40.47,0:39:43.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们为了实现这些理想才进行肮脏的斗争
Dialogue: 0,0:39:43.98,0:39:45.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果没有我这种人
Dialogue: 0,0:39:45.68,0:39:48.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有我这种采取必要恶行的人
Dialogue: 0,0:39:48.78,0:39:50.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就会输
Dialogue: 0,0:39:50.61,0:39:52.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少摆出这副自以为是的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:39:52.60,0:39:55.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么好意思把自己
Dialogue: 0,0:39:55.73,0:39:57.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和那些士兵们相提并论
Dialogue: 0,0:39:58.58,0:39:59.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是个小办事员
Dialogue: 0,0:40:00.39,0:40:01.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是名罪犯
Dialogue: 0,0:40:02.30,0:40:03.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带他出去
Dialogue: 0,0:40:20.28,0:40:21.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:40:22.21,0:40:24.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好多了  毕竟现在没带着手铐了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:24.14,0:40:26.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但到底是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:40:30.63,0:40:32.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鉴于我们目前的情况
Dialogue: 0,0:40:32.31,0:40:34.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对这个结果没意见
Dialogue: 0,0:40:35.03,0:40:36.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:40:36.38,0:40:37.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,显然  我没有隐瞒自己的想法
Dialogue: 0,0:40:37.72,0:40:39.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想削弱国际反应小组的作用
Dialogue: 0,0:40:39.97,0:40:41.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想摆脱我们
Dialogue: 0,0:40:41.66,0:40:42.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要你们能负起责任
Dialogue: 0,0:40:42.84,0:40:45.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是负责的  一直如此
Dialogue: 0,0:40:45.70,0:40:47.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你叫我来干什么呢  杰克
Dialogue: 0,0:40:47.60,0:40:50.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是来要求对蒙哥马利探员宽大处理的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:40:50.55,0:40:52.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这正是我想说的
Dialogue: 0,0:40:52.05,0:40:54.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽管他意图是好的  结果也不坏
Dialogue: 0,0:40:54.97,0:40:57.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但蒙哥马利探员
Dialogue: 0,0:40:57.26,0:40:59.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须为他自己的行为负责
Dialogue: 0,0:40:59.68,0:41:01.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算我同意
Dialogue: 0,0:41:01.15,0:41:02.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不提起刑事诉讼
Dialogue: 0,0:41:03.25,0:41:06.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但最起码局里必须要辞退他
Dialogue: 0,0:41:06.90,0:41:07.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她说得对  杰克
Dialogue: 0,0:41:08.27,0:41:09.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不认同
Dialogue: 0,0:41:10.29,0:41:12.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为蒙哥马利探员的行为
Dialogue: 0,0:41:12.31,0:41:14.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我团队中任何人所做的任何行为
Dialogue: 0,0:41:15.14,0:41:16.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是基于我的命令
Dialogue: 0,0:41:16.19,0:41:18.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论是直接下达的还是暗示的
Dialogue: 0,0:41:18.58,0:41:20.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切责任都应该由我承担
Dialogue: 0,0:41:20.17,0:41:23.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算有人要被开除  那也该是我
Dialogue: 0,0:41:24.79,0:41:26.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认真的  琳达
Dialogue: 0,0:41:26.13,0:41:28.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你是认真的  杰克  但你可能
Dialogue: 0,0:41:28.47,0:41:30.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不清楚现在的情况
Dialogue: 0,0:41:30.77,0:41:31.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你刚刚扳倒了
Dialogue: 0,0:41:31.55,0:41:33.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,国家情报局的副主任
Dialogue: 0,0:41:33.32,0:41:35.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在要我来停你的职吗
Dialogue: 0,0:41:35.36,0:41:37.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错啊  因为就该如此
Dialogue: 0,0:41:37.97,0:41:39.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是责任
Dialogue: 0,0:41:44.52,0:41:47.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰克·加勒特组长  我先跟你说清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:41:47.86,0:41:50.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会盯着你和你的小组
Dialogue: 0,0:41:50.96,0:41:52.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以把这当成是第一振
Dialogue: 0,0:41:52.56,0:41:55.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这场博弈中  第二振你就会出局
Dialogue: 0,0:42:08.14,0:42:09.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:42:09.38,0:42:12.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别提我了  他们都准备把你关起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:42:12.47,0:42:14.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  但我知道你们会来救我的  对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:42:14.53,0:42:16.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也可能是和你关在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:42:16.33,0:42:17.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是彼此的坚强后盾
Dialogue: 0,0:42:18.06,0:42:22.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确  我们回家吧  休息一下
Dialogue: 0,0:42:23.45,0:42:24.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位
Dialogue: 0,0:42:28.96,0:42:31.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坏蛋们可从不休息
Dialogue: 0,0:42:34.42,0:42:35.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实
Dialogue: 0,0:42:36.94,0:42:38.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来我们又有工作了
Dialogue: 0,0:42:39.46,0:42:43.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}联邦调查局国际反应小组
