[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: 
Original Script: 
Synch Point: 1
ScriptType: v4.00+
PlayResX: 0
PlayResY: 0
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no
YCbCr Matrix: TV.601

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.50,0:00:05.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)\fs16\bord0\shad0\blur5\t(0,500,\blur0)\b1\c&HECB000&\pos(99,242)}原創翻譯  雙語字幕
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.00,0:00:05.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)\fn方正準圓_GBK\b1\bord0\shad0\fs17\pos(235.108,242)\K40}最新連載海外影視劇下載\N{\fs19\K30}請登陸 {\c&H26F4FF&\fn方正綜藝_GBK\K30}www.YYeTs.com\N{\fn方正準圓_GBK\fs15\c&HFFFFFF&\K60}僅供交流學習  禁止商用盈利
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.22,0:00:11.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)}翻譯     showeryhe  Brisingr
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.22,0:00:16.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)}翻譯     胖達萌萌噠  瀟然
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.22,0:00:21.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)}翻譯     無序腳印  tokilltime
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.22,0:00:26.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)}校對     瀟然  胡說大王
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.22,0:00:31.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(27,235)}時間軸     {\c&H9B30FF&}風吹來的那片云
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.22,0:00:36.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)}后期     灰灰是菇涼
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.22,0:00:41.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)}總監     showeryhe
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.70,0:00:02.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑體簡體\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}聯調局國際反應小組
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.64,0:00:03.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每年有超過6800萬美國人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.39,0:00:05.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,離開安全的國內
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.05,0:00:07.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當危險來襲
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.84,0:00:10.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聯調局國際反應小組
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.44,0:00:12.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隨時出動
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.23,0:00:13.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑體簡體\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}弗吉尼亞州  匡提科
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.94,0:00:38.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.46,0:01:22.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰克·加勒特組長
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.19,0:01:24.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天你有權保持沉默
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.20,0:01:26.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并拒絕回答問題
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.36,0:01:28.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果放棄該權利  那你所說的所有內容
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.25,0:01:30.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都可以并將用來作為呈堂證供
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.98,0:01:32.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在訊問開始之前及進行過程中
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.61,0:01:34.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你都有權找律師咨詢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.10,0:01:36.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你無力聘請律師
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.32,0:01:41.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.90,0:01:44.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰克·加勒特組長  你明白
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.57,0:01:45.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我剛才解釋的這些權利了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.93,0:01:48.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.77,0:01:54.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑體簡體\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}犯罪心理  國境之外
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.62,0:01:54.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑體簡體\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}第二季第九集
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.31,0:02:34.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑體簡體\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}要想保守秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.21,0:02:34.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑體簡體\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}除非其他知情者都是死人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.07,0:02:34.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑體簡體\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}本杰明·富蘭克林
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.55,0:02:40.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你現在是否愿意坐下回答我們的問題
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.33,0:02:43.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.20,0:02:50.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰克  你確定不要律師嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.36,0:02:51.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能會來狠的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.62,0:02:53.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不需要律師
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.22,0:02:56.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請記錄國際反應小組組長杰克·加勒特
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.62,0:02:58.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此次放棄咨詢律師的權利
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.99,0:03:01.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此次與會的還有
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.50,0:03:03.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來自聯調局職業責任辦公室的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.51,0:03:06.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,布萊恩·林奇和喬迪·雷諾茲探員
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.68,0:03:09.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥倫比亞特區的副法顧賈尼絲·賴切爾
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.29,0:03:11.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,代表司法部出席
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.34,0:03:13.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,國家情報局副主任沃爾特·阿特伍德
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.93,0:03:16.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我是聯調局國家安全處的執行助理主任
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.70,0:03:18.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琳達·巴恩斯
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.92,0:03:21.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿特伍德副主任和我受全權委托
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.24,0:03:23.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來負責此次聯調局與國情局的聯合訊問
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.59,0:03:24.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加勒特組長
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.99,0:03:26.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能否從頭開始
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.29,0:03:28.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說說可吉基斯坦卡利葉
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.27,0:03:30.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,編號67-16-01的案件
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.51,0:03:33.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們在里斯本給飛機加燃料
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.51,0:03:33.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑體簡體\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}葡萄牙首都
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.20,0:03:36.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這時羅素·蒙哥馬利探員通知我們
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.25,0:03:39.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美國大使及可吉基斯坦外交部
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.82,0:03:42.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要求我們參與協助
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.38,0:03:45.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是涉及一位美國公民及一位可吉基公民的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.60,0:03:47.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雙尸案
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.24,0:03:48.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克麗·洛德爾  二十九歲
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.55,0:03:50.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是羅得島州普羅維登斯人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.48,0:03:52.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在全球策略開發
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.72,0:03:56.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這家美國承包單位  做網絡工程師
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.49,0:03:57.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有阿倫·薩布里
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.95,0:03:59.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三十二歲  卡利葉人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.80,0:04:01.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在全球策略開發做保安
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.83,0:04:04.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,據可吉基國家警察的里法伊長官
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.83,0:04:06.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一位據稱與克麗有染的同事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.98,0:04:09.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,將她活活捅死
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.19,0:04:11.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個人叫愛德華·德爾加多
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.37,0:04:12.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德爾加多  四十六歲
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.92,0:04:14.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是弗吉尼亞州亞歷山德里亞人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.54,0:04:15.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,擔任系統分析員
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.61,0:04:17.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已婚并育有一個兩歲的女兒
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.48,0:04:18.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當地保安薩布里
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.98,0:04:19.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎在與德爾加多
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.87,0:04:21.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打斗過程中身亡
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.34,0:04:23.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而德爾加多則趁機逃出居住區
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.80,0:04:24.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看來都發生在
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.87,0:04:26.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡利葉的鋼圈中
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.08,0:04:28.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鋼圈
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.22,0:04:30.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是一片六平方千米的嚴守地區
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.80,0:04:32.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑體簡體\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}伊拉克首都
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.80,0:04:32.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,類似于巴格達的綠區
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.05,0:04:35.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰克  我認識德爾加多
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.71,0:04:36.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你認識他嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.74,0:04:38.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前有過接觸
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.31,0:04:40.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾在緬甸一家非政府組織共事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.45,0:04:42.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么時候的事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.10,0:04:45.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三年前  我請假離開那段時間
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.40,0:04:46.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你對他有什么印象
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.81,0:04:49.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說實話  我覺得完全說不通
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.31,0:04:49.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我認識的那個人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.98,0:04:51.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪怕很生氣  音量也不會提高
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.56,0:04:52.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而別提殺人了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.89,0:04:55.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不止是殺人  他現在可是逃犯
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.75,0:04:58.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塞格爾探員的工作就是分析
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.46,0:05:01.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并對犯罪嫌疑人給出客觀側寫
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.30,0:05:04.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那她的判斷力難道不是已經受影響了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.25,0:05:05.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.82,0:05:06.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.64,0:05:10.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塞格爾探員和德爾加多以前的接觸
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.30,0:05:13.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你認為不會以任何方式影響她的能力
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.14,0:05:15.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我不認為  正如我不相信
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.50,0:05:18.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿特伍德副主任和我的老交情
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.31,0:05:20.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能影響他在本次訊問過程中
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.60,0:05:22.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保持客觀公正的能力
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.63,0:05:26.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塞格爾探員有沒有向你
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.31,0:05:27.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或團隊中其他成員
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.53,0:05:30.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全交代她過去和德爾加多先生的關系
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.42,0:05:33.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塞格爾探員坦言三年前
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.73,0:05:35.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們曾在緬甸共事
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.47,0:05:36.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她沒有剛好提及
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.50,0:05:38.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和這個男人的私人關系嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.00,0:05:44.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她沒有提及  但這不重要  因為
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.67,0:05:47.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重要的是你對團隊成員的了解程度
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.74,0:05:50.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毫無疑問訊問過程中這一塊十分重要
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.87,0:05:52.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我們先跳過吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.42,0:05:56.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們登陸該國后  說說有什么流程
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.06,0:05:58.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們到達卡利葉后就開始
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.87,0:06:01.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和巴希爾·里法伊長官協作
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.34,0:06:03.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是可吉基國家警察的負責人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.60,0:06:04.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惜
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.35,0:06:06.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我手下對逃犯愛德華·德爾加多的追捕
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.09,0:06:08.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一無所獲
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.31,0:06:11.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們傾向于認為他或許已經逃出了鋼圈
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.34,0:06:13.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也可能已經死了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.06,0:06:15.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為他作為一個在逃的西方人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.79,0:06:17.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他可能輕易地落入
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.27,0:06:19.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好戰組織  信念兄弟會手中
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.25,0:06:22.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯  禍害我國的恐怖組織之一
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.26,0:06:23.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有這一個
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.16,0:06:26.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是由你們前將軍之一拉尚·努里領導的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.19,0:06:28.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  給我們造成了更深的傷害
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.73,0:06:30.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但德爾加多是個非常聰明的人  對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.46,0:06:32.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你覺得他是否會在安全區外鋌而走險呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.23,0:06:34.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯一讓他敢這么做的原因
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.31,0:06:35.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是他確切知道哪里可以讓他躲藏
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.98,0:06:36.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一小段時間
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.68,0:06:39.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許賈維斯探員是對的  但以我的經驗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.68,0:06:44.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,窮途之人總會做出極端的決定
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.20,0:06:48.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在我和塞格爾探員要檢視案發現場了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.36,0:06:50.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西蒙斯探員會去推測嫌疑人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.88,0:06:53.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從居住區逃跑后的潛在路線
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.74,0:06:54.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  沒問題
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.70,0:06:58.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還需要將克麗·洛德爾和阿倫·薩布里的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.19,0:07:00.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尸體運回  以便賈維斯探員
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.03,0:07:02.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能進行補充尸檢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.56,0:07:04.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會安排調度的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.99,0:07:07.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,組長  你之前提到的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.41,0:07:10.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果沒記錯  那個可吉基的外交部長
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.16,0:07:12.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是請國際反應小組來協助
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.37,0:07:14.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這起案件的人之一  對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.76,0:07:15.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  沒錯
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.68,0:07:17.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是否
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.52,0:07:20.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,承認并且尊重當地政府  里法伊長官
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.87,0:07:23.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在此次調查中的主導地位呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.99,0:07:28.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,副主任  國際反應小組的職責一直都是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.16,0:07:30.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在此雙尸案的調查中
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.90,0:07:33.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為里法伊長官和國家警察提供建議和協助
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.96,0:07:36.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且追捕在逃的愛德華·德爾加多
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.98,0:07:40.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在許多建議和協助
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.20,0:07:41.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是基于你們團隊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.68,0:07:45.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,建立的犯罪嫌疑人的行為側寫
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.24,0:07:46.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是嗎  -沒錯
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.97,0:07:50.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴恩斯助理主任指出過
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.40,0:07:52.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塞格爾探員熟悉這位
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.00,0:07:55.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者說過分熟悉這位
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.03,0:07:58.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特殊人物  德爾加多先生
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.18,0:08:00.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塞格爾探員在調查中并未表現出
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.52,0:08:01.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,任何偏袒
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.79,0:08:05.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事實上  她對德爾加多過去行為的了解
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.71,0:08:08.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是幫我們更深入地研究在克麗·洛德爾
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.55,0:08:10.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死亡現場發現的證據
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.50,0:08:20.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全球策略開發不是來幫你們部門
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.62,0:08:22.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提升技術安全的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.54,0:08:25.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  我們的一些工作人員認識受害者
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.96,0:08:27.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有德爾加多先生
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.90,0:08:29.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們有見過這兩人公開在一起活動嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.92,0:08:30.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.11,0:08:34.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你的理論不是情侶爭吵然后惡性發展嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.75,0:08:37.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在保安截堵到德爾加多前
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.62,0:08:38.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他還曾用無線電請求增援
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.90,0:08:42.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那時是凌晨兩點  他聽見屋里有尖叫聲
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.63,0:08:44.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隨后他就從這里追著嫌疑人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.55,0:08:47.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后將他逼到了走廊盡頭的陽臺
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.51,0:08:50.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但德爾加多打倒了他
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.15,0:08:51.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這也不能說明這兩人之間
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.93,0:08:53.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-有親密關系  -我同意
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.70,0:08:57.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這更可能像是一次性騷擾
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.56,0:08:59.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隨后升級成了謀殺
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.46,0:09:01.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看這狂怒的痕跡
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.28,0:09:05.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對  過度殺戮  因為一些個人原因
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.16,0:09:09.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你發現什么了嗎  梅
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.27,0:09:12.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我發現克麗的毒檢結果非常奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.46,0:09:14.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她體內有鎮靜劑
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.59,0:09:16.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但沒有任何醫生給她開過這種藥
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.70,0:09:18.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且藥量非常之高
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.49,0:09:20.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她像是被迫注射了鎮定劑
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.06,0:09:23.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此外  克麗身上沒有任何防衛傷痕
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.29,0:09:24.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你認為克麗被下藥了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.95,0:09:26.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后被刺死
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.20,0:09:28.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從我的角度看是這樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.12,0:09:30.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那第二個受害者  阿倫·薩布里呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.73,0:09:32.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死因是鈍力損傷
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.77,0:09:35.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,與被拋下陽臺的說法一致
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.05,0:09:36.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但遺憾的是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.49,0:09:38.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死后損傷讓我很難確認
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.12,0:09:40.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪些傷痕是因為受害者
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.39,0:09:42.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,與嫌疑人搏斗留下的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.38,0:09:46.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且我還不清楚他的手上為什么會有擦傷
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.43,0:09:47.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑體簡體\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}尸檢報告  阿倫·薩布里
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.84,0:09:48.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就是我了解到的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.99,0:09:50.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝  梅
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.32,0:09:52.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰克  這里沒有什么能確認或否認
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.97,0:09:54.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這兩人之間存在親密關系
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.86,0:09:56.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也無法證明他們之間
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.43,0:09:58.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底有過怎樣的關系
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.09,0:09:59.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能造成這樣凄慘的變故
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.11,0:10:02.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許他的房間能給我們更多信息
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.52,0:10:04.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能吧  但我認為需要對克麗·洛德爾
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.69,0:10:06.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,進行更深入的受害者分析
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.88,0:10:08.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看看她的紀念物
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.16,0:10:10.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她顯然在不同的人中都很受歡迎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.93,0:10:12.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們中的任何人都能對她
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.40,0:10:14.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,發展出扭曲的渴慕之情
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.16,0:10:16.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從而激發出這場暴力案件
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.21,0:10:19.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓蒙蒂跟進下
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.44,0:10:22.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這么說  你們調查的下一步行動
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.74,0:10:24.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是根據塞格爾探員的建議來的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.65,0:10:28.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  進行受害者分析是我們側寫的一步
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.81,0:10:31.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但根據你的描述  塞格爾探員說
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.62,0:10:34.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,深入的受害者分析能讓德爾加多洗掉嫌疑
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.20,0:10:35.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才沒這么說  你一直都在
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.98,0:10:37.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扭曲我說過的話
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.29,0:10:38.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只想確認清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.33,0:10:39.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在有意整我們小組
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.91,0:10:41.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是這么做的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.30,0:10:43.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-可能我們該休息一下  -我認為不用
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.78,0:10:46.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我覺得需要休息了  -阿倫和克麗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.65,0:10:49.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是這起案件僅有的受害人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.34,0:10:51.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一位平民嫌犯也死了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.80,0:10:54.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是因為國際反應小組的莽撞行為
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.14,0:10:56.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你認為我有意整國際反應小組
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.75,0:11:00.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰克·加勒特組長  我就跟你明說吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.82,0:11:02.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等今天工作完成了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.12,0:11:04.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會動用全部力量將國際反應小組
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.54,0:11:06.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徹底粉碎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.02,0:11:08.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并將灰燼四散入風
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.34,0:11:22.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其實可以  更好一點
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.86,0:11:27.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-進展挺順利  -因為你并不認為
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.27,0:11:30.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那樣自揭底牌后  會很難證明
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.45,0:11:32.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,存在偏見
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.56,0:11:34.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你應該輕聲而動
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.24,0:11:35.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那樣嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.27,0:11:37.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  這不僅是訊問
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.90,0:11:40.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是政治棋局
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.64,0:11:41.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你喜歡下棋嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.01,0:11:43.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜歡拳擊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.78,0:11:47.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看出來了  我就很喜歡下棋
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.52,0:11:51.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,需要沉得住氣  擅用策略
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.30,0:11:53.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,懂得人性的弱點
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.07,0:11:55.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再說總能驅王使后
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.89,0:11:57.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我對你的打氣鼓勁并非不感激
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.41,0:11:58.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我不想要
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.72,0:12:01.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷靜  我是想保護你
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.55,0:12:04.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且如果你真的想實現公正
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.56,0:12:07.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要收集也只收集事實
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.70,0:12:10.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剩下的就交給當權者
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.03,0:12:29.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用我提醒你
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.97,0:12:32.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,房里沒人被捕吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.16,0:12:33.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以如果不介意
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.17,0:12:35.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要活動下腿腳  倒杯咖啡
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.53,0:12:39.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰有想要的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.50,0:12:41.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太荒謬了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.65,0:12:44.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想現在最好還是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.10,0:12:46.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要交流
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.17,0:12:47.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們在房間裝了竊聽器嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.96,0:12:49.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什么要裝竊聽器呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.47,0:12:52.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為盡管我們并沒有被捕
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.95,0:12:55.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我們相互之間禁止討論
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.26,0:12:56.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,任何本案相關的事
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.82,0:12:58.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難以置信  我們能有什么打算
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.76,0:13:00.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐在這兒合伙編故事嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.61,0:13:02.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這正是他們的想法
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.35,0:13:04.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使只是串供的表現
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.45,0:13:06.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也可能導致停工  甚至是起訴
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.73,0:13:17.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  凱倫和孩子們怎么樣
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.45,0:13:19.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得了吧  別說廢話
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.81,0:13:22.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  伙計  真是粗暴
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.02,0:13:25.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你要記住  有我支持你
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.06,0:13:26.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不需要你支持
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.26,0:13:29.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰克  你自己也聽到那女人的話了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.36,0:13:32.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,關鍵不在于誰對誰錯
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.51,0:13:34.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是誰來擔罪
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.21,0:13:36.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沃爾特  我們所有行動都是照規定來的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.65,0:13:40.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  杰克  但有人死了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.09,0:13:43.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以不管有沒有照規定來  有人犯了錯
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.90,0:13:46.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只希望那個人不是你
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.00,0:13:49.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對我的訊問還沒結束
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.74,0:13:50.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.07,0:13:54.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你和巴恩斯需要中場休息
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.18,0:13:56.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  失陪
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.93,0:14:05.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塞格爾探員  三年前你曾請假
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.80,0:14:08.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-沒錯  -為什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.35,0:14:12.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-為什么  -沒錯  那是個問題
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.31,0:14:14.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我恐怕不明白你的意思
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.59,0:14:17.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你面前就是我的個人檔案
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.52,0:14:19.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你十分清楚我告假的原因
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.74,0:14:22.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯  我確實知道
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.87,0:14:26.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真可惜  我想自己這些審訊員的花招
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.32,0:14:29.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在你這種法醫心理學專家面前
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.94,0:14:31.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根本玩不起來  是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.51,0:14:33.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請你一定要包容
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.13,0:14:36.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者你也可以選擇不回答該問題
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.18,0:14:38.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那可能透露出你的心智狀況
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.38,0:14:39.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.28,0:14:43.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想玩游戲  我奉陪
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.66,0:14:45.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三年前
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.26,0:14:49.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我丈夫  特別督察探員布拉德·塞格爾
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.90,0:14:52.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在執行公務時被害
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.52,0:14:56.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我因為喪夫而告假
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.74,0:15:02.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,節哀順變
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.31,0:15:04.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.72,0:15:08.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因喪夫休假期間  你去往世界各地
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.11,0:15:10.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我想集中于三年前
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.86,0:15:12.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在緬甸那段
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.76,0:15:17.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當時你和愛德華·德爾加多十分熟絡
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.32,0:15:18.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,該男子后來也成為
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.78,0:15:20.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡利葉調查中的重點
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.62,0:15:22.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而他和你的復雜關系
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.81,0:15:24.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-使貴團隊產生偏見  -這么說不對
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.16,0:15:27.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盡管我個人了解德爾加多
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.50,0:15:30.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我們團隊仍不含偏見將此人視為逃犯
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.38,0:15:31.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,進行追捕
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.16,0:15:33.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且蒙哥馬利探員還聯系了他的妻子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.91,0:15:36.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來多加了解他可能的逃亡去向
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.25,0:15:44.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蒙哥馬利探員  過去二十四小時
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.74,0:15:46.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都聯系不上我丈夫
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.64,0:15:49.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-德爾加多夫人  -請叫我阿米莉婭
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.37,0:15:52.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿米莉婭  請坐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.64,0:15:59.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全球戰略開發的居住區發了生意外事件
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.03,0:16:00.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有兩人被害
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.29,0:16:03.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一位是你丈夫的女同事克麗·洛德爾
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.11,0:16:06.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,另一位是叫阿倫·薩布里的保安
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.76,0:16:10.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你丈夫也失蹤了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.90,0:16:11.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失蹤
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.00,0:16:14.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么意思  失蹤
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.47,0:16:15.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿米莉婭  你最近一次
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.64,0:16:17.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和丈夫聯系是什么時候
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.09,0:16:19.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他昨天早上給我發了電子郵件
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.59,0:16:20.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.55,0:16:22.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒什么  只是幾張照片
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.55,0:16:23.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能給我看看嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.10,0:16:35.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在國外的時候
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.92,0:16:37.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們倆多久聯系一次
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.18,0:16:40.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每周一次  主要通過郵件
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.64,0:16:44.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定很難熬  對你們倆來說
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.51,0:16:47.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我為什么感覺你真正想問的是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.83,0:16:50.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有沒有覺得丈夫跟克麗有染
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.51,0:16:53.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有這個可能嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.35,0:16:55.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  沒可能
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.14,0:16:58.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他發照片給我以便我認識他的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.79,0:16:59.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,僅此而已
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.94,0:17:01.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.92,0:17:05.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你丈夫最近有承受不同尋常的壓力嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.12,0:17:08.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒  據我所知沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.57,0:17:11.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是個好人  他跟所有人都相處融洽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.55,0:17:16.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我發誓  他絕對不會傷害任何人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.42,0:17:18.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德爾加多的妻子給了我權限
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.77,0:17:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,登入她丈夫的社交媒體
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.00,0:17:22.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我正在檢查當中  但老實說
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.00,0:17:24.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿米莉婭似乎非常了解她的丈夫
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.09,0:17:26.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以如果他跟克麗沒有婚外情
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.00,0:17:27.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那他的殺人動機是什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.74,0:17:29.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是德爾加多沒有殺害克麗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.36,0:17:30.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那他為什么襲擊保安
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.64,0:17:31.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他為什么逃跑
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.74,0:17:33.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這帶來了一個更加迫切的問題
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.98,0:17:36.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛德華·德爾加多到底在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.42,0:17:39.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽著  不管犯罪與否  他并非慣犯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.42,0:17:41.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他人生地不熟
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.01,0:17:42.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像梅之前說的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.64,0:17:44.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他能夠逃出鋼圈
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.94,0:17:46.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因為他知道在另一邊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.94,0:17:48.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許有人能保護他
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.86,0:17:50.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好像有發現
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.43,0:17:52.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德爾加多似乎跟
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.32,0:17:54.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他第一位翻譯的家人很親近
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.41,0:17:56.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,年輕人名叫奧馬爾·塔汗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.33,0:17:57.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑體簡體\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}全球策略開發  奧馬爾·塔汗  翻譯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.67,0:17:58.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  塞格爾探員
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.09,0:17:59.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個年輕人叫什么名字
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.66,0:18:00.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奧馬爾·塔汗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.84,0:18:03.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他給德爾加多當了兩周翻譯
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.25,0:18:04.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到把職責交給了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.28,0:18:06.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可吉基國家警察的一名警官
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.08,0:18:08.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什么移交工作呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.00,0:18:09.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德爾加多的工作使他
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.32,0:18:11.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接觸到可吉基國家警察的保密通訊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.80,0:18:15.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而塔汗先生沒有得到權限
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.65,0:18:17.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們確認了塔汗先生的身份后
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.78,0:18:19.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和你的團隊接著做了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.67,0:18:21.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們前往塔汗的家
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.54,0:18:24.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,距離鋼圈西北方一千六百米的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.90,0:18:27.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們發現德爾加多先生就躲在了那里
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.72,0:18:29.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他有反抗嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.19,0:18:32.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  他沒有  他毫無抵抗地接受拘留
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.44,0:18:34.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塞格爾探員  是誰決定
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.67,0:18:36.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把愛德華·德爾加多轉移
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.26,0:18:37.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回國際反應小組的飛機
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.70,0:18:40.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而非直接把他帶給可吉基國家警察拘留呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.99,0:18:43.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是加勒特組長的決定
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.19,0:18:46.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你記得自己質疑過那個決定嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.87,0:18:48.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不  -你不記得  還是...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.98,0:18:51.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不  我沒有質疑  -你支持嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.10,0:18:53.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽著  當時德爾加多是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.70,0:18:55.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,國際反應小組和可吉基國家警察
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.33,0:18:57.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聯合調查中的疑犯
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.49,0:18:59.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加勒特組長有權
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.63,0:19:01.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把疑犯帶到飛機中審訊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.92,0:19:05.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-誰審訊他的  -是我
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.59,0:19:20.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得告訴我  愛德
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.25,0:19:24.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得告訴我在公寓里
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.70,0:19:26.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟保安發生了什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.84,0:19:29.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你為什么逃走
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.63,0:19:33.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟她有發生關系嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.31,0:19:36.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你覺得呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.55,0:19:40.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老實說  我覺得你絕對不會背叛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.78,0:19:42.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你孩子的母親
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.98,0:19:46.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想回家
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.59,0:19:49.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我對天發誓  不是我做的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.79,0:19:52.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  所以讓我幫你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.51,0:19:54.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你不懂  你幫不了的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.95,0:19:59.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這太瘋狂了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.12,0:20:03.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在這里  走進我的生活
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.02,0:20:04.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像你以前那樣
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.57,0:20:07.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了"拯救"我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.09,0:20:18.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我認為我們拯救了彼此
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.92,0:20:20.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.30,0:20:25.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我依然清楚記得  你告訴我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.63,0:20:27.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們在一起是個錯誤的時候
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.22,0:20:29.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們的感情到了哪一步
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.74,0:20:32.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但不可思議的是
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.59,0:20:37.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是你沒有離開我  我就不會回家
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.81,0:20:39.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就不會結婚  而且
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.37,0:20:43.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我生命里就不會有寶貝女兒  朱莉婭
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.19,0:20:47.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對  我現在就不會在這里幫你
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.78,0:20:49.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得相信我  愛德
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.09,0:20:51.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事實上
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.01,0:20:55.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世界上我只相信
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.73,0:20:57.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一個人  克拉拉
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.56,0:21:01.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克拉拉  杰克剛和里法伊隊長通完電話
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.74,0:21:03.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他要求我們把他轉送給可吉基國家警察拘留
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.88,0:21:05.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可吉基國家警察  不  慢著
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.56,0:21:08.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是被聯調局逮捕的美國公民
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.44,0:21:09.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們為什么不能拘留我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.86,0:21:12.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都會沒事的  愛德
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.02,0:21:14.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的團隊和我會一路陪著你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.30,0:21:15.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是聯合調查
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.89,0:21:17.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其實  把他帶到這里
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.27,0:21:19.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比把他帶回鋼圈更方便
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.13,0:21:21.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然我就得和里法伊隊長
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.17,0:21:22.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,協調安全協議
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.22,0:21:23.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  我幫他做準備
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.02,0:21:27.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安全協議
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.95,0:21:29.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種加密通訊方式
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.92,0:21:31.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在可吉基國家警察和國際反應小組
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.98,0:21:34.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轉交犯人之前  期間和之后使用
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.57,0:21:36.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我說得對嗎  -對
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.61,0:21:39.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  特別督查探員西蒙斯
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.49,0:21:41.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們能倒回去嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.77,0:21:44.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你接到里法伊隊長的電話
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.25,0:21:45.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他讓你把人交給他
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.25,0:21:49.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能告訴我接下來本該發生什么嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.73,0:21:52.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原計劃是國際反應小組將犯人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.32,0:21:55.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,押送回鋼圈內的可吉基國家警察總部
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.21,0:21:56.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們本來要走由里法伊長官
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.83,0:21:58.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安排的安全線路
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.44,0:22:00.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行動的首要目標
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.07,0:22:01.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是避開機場
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.73,0:22:03.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,與鋼圈之間的主干道
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.91,0:22:06.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  因為他們把那條路叫什么來著
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.00,0:22:07.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"詛咒之路"
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.45,0:22:08.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西蒙斯探員
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.15,0:22:09.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們知道之后本該發生什么
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.69,0:22:12.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-告訴我們實際是什么情況  -我們被
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.38,0:22:15.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忠于信念兄弟會的戰士伏擊了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.90,0:22:17.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道你們怎么成為攻擊目標的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.17,0:22:18.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.31,0:22:21.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  這是隨機的攻擊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.90,0:22:22.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隨機的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.73,0:22:25.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并不是隨機的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.56,0:22:27.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們被發現是因為
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.21,0:22:29.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你用公開線路進行通訊時暴露了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.61,0:22:33.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能  我親自加密了線路
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.94,0:22:39.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你告訴我  先生
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.80,0:22:42.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是失職  還是叛徒
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.51,0:22:47.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為電子記錄顯示并沒有加密
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.61,0:22:53.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這些日志肯定不是真的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.62,0:22:55.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這些日志來自可吉基國家警察的服務器
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.42,0:22:59.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伏擊過程中發生了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.76,0:23:01.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們采取了躲避策略
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.48,0:23:03.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一刻  我們被迫離開道路
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.20,0:23:05.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緊接著發生了交火
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.58,0:23:08.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,犯人在交火時中槍
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.24,0:23:10.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你害德爾加多中槍了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.88,0:23:12.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在那時我們作出決定
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.66,0:23:13.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原路返回飛機
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.96,0:23:16.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-誰做的決定  -加勒特組長
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.16,0:23:19.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我們救德爾加多唯一的機會
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.34,0:23:21.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是你們組長的醫療建議
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.29,0:23:24.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是他的外勤法醫  梅·賈維斯探員的建議
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.55,0:23:25.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.74,0:23:27.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我當時忙著帶大家脫離險境
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.69,0:23:29.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告訴我們回飛機后發生了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.18,0:23:32.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德爾加多胸部中槍
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.00,0:23:34.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-這里  -我把他從車里拉出來
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.44,0:23:36.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我正準備幫忙將他搬進會議室
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.94,0:23:38.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在那時他們試圖登機
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.65,0:23:41.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"他們"就是兄弟會的人
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.92,0:23:44.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯  克拉拉和梅以及其他機組成員
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.56,0:23:46.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,將德爾加多帶離交火區
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.04,0:23:47.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  把他放在這里
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.72,0:23:48.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.66,0:23:51.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克拉拉  把他的防彈背心脫下來
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.75,0:23:52.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.43,0:23:54.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當時一片混亂
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.76,0:24:01.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰克和我抵擋住了他們的攻擊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.51,0:24:03.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克拉拉和梅搶救德爾加多
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.51,0:24:05.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們得給他供氧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.67,0:24:07.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再緊點
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.62,0:24:10.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他人都沒受傷嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.49,0:24:11.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.75,0:24:14.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德爾加多是唯一一個中槍的人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.85,0:24:15.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.87,0:24:19.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們盡力關上了貨艙門
Dialogue: 0,0:24:24.87,0:24:28.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你們沒能保住德爾加多的命  是不是
Dialogue: 0,0:24:28.40,0:24:30.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  堅持住  拜托
Dialogue: 0,0:24:32.32,0:24:33.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梅
Dialogue: 0,0:24:33.44,0:24:34.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,堅持住  愛德華
Dialogue: 0,0:24:38.64,0:24:40.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告訴我該怎么做  該怎么做
Dialogue: 0,0:24:44.18,0:24:45.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梅
Dialogue: 0,0:24:45.61,0:24:46.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他死了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:55.16,0:24:56.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:25:02.54,0:25:04.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們好像在重新集結  杰克
Dialogue: 0,0:25:04.29,0:25:06.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能在呼叫增援
Dialogue: 0,0:25:06.04,0:25:07.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不會認為
Dialogue: 0,0:25:07.16,0:25:07.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們想要登機吧
Dialogue: 0,0:25:07.93,0:25:09.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不想發生那種事
Dialogue: 0,0:25:10.12,0:25:12.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里法伊長官  你保證的增援呢
Dialogue: 0,0:25:12.60,0:25:14.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們現在正在路上
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.66,0:25:16.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特別督查探員賈維斯  加勒特組長
Dialogue: 0,0:25:16.82,0:25:18.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,命令小組返回飛機的時候
Dialogue: 0,0:25:18.32,0:25:20.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道德爾加多先生的全部傷勢狀況嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:25:20.63,0:25:22.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我發現了一處槍傷
Dialogue: 0,0:25:22.99,0:25:24.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在他的右上側胸部
Dialogue: 0,0:25:24.81,0:25:28.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我推測他的肺部受損
Dialogue: 0,0:25:28.25,0:25:29.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你對命令提出質疑了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:25:29.81,0:25:33.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-沒有  -你面前的傷者胸部中槍
Dialogue: 0,0:25:33.08,0:25:36.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你卻沒有堅持改道去擁有戰地醫院的
Dialogue: 0,0:25:36.25,0:25:37.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美軍格拉納托駐地嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:25:37.86,0:25:39.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我沒有  因為
Dialogue: 0,0:25:40.04,0:25:42.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事實上  我知道飛機上的設備
Dialogue: 0,0:25:42.39,0:25:45.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能夠穩定他的情況  而其他選擇
Dialogue: 0,0:25:45.73,0:25:47.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是未知且充滿變數的
Dialogue: 0,0:25:47.36,0:25:49.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且這一切是我們被敵人攻擊時發生的
Dialogue: 0,0:25:50.66,0:25:52.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  當時情況很危急
Dialogue: 0,0:25:52.13,0:25:54.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是的  -也許這就能解釋為什么
Dialogue: 0,0:25:54.97,0:25:58.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從醫學院畢業后  你沒有做外科醫生
Dialogue: 0,0:25:58.01,0:26:00.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是成為了一名法醫
Dialogue: 0,0:26:01.16,0:26:02.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:26:02.91,0:26:05.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你記得一位
Dialogue: 0,0:26:05.66,0:26:08.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫迪倫·雅各布斯的年輕人嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:26:09.68,0:26:12.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,記得  我記得迪倫
Dialogue: 0,0:26:12.77,0:26:16.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他入院的那晚  你是圣柯萊特
Dialogue: 0,0:26:16.45,0:26:17.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外傷治療中心的住院醫生
Dialogue: 0,0:26:17.50,0:26:19.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你記得他發生了什么事嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:26:19.89,0:26:21.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,記得  他死在了手術臺上
Dialogue: 0,0:26:22.25,0:26:25.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的家人認為是你和賈斯汀·懷亞特醫生
Dialogue: 0,0:26:25.11,0:26:26.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及醫院的疏忽大意造成他死亡
Dialogue: 0,0:26:26.84,0:26:28.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們提起了訴訟
Dialogue: 0,0:26:28.57,0:26:30.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那起訴訟庭外和解了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:31.45,0:26:33.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,簽訂了保密協議
Dialogue: 0,0:26:33.17,0:26:36.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意思是你無法透露你是否覺得
Dialogue: 0,0:26:36.96,0:26:39.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己應該對雅各布斯的死負責嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:26:47.90,0:26:50.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰克  我很抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:26:50.99,0:26:52.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本該把一切都告訴你的
Dialogue: 0,0:26:52.38,0:26:54.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事的  克拉拉
Dialogue: 0,0:26:54.05,0:26:55.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把該告訴的都告訴我了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:58.46,0:26:59.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兩位  聽著
Dialogue: 0,0:26:59.51,0:27:01.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道我們不該交談
Dialogue: 0,0:27:01.75,0:27:03.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但事情有點不對勁
Dialogue: 0,0:27:03.63,0:27:06.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴恩斯和阿特伍德基本上把伏擊的事
Dialogue: 0,0:27:06.48,0:27:07.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都怪在我頭上
Dialogue: 0,0:27:08.06,0:27:10.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們說我沒有加密通訊線路
Dialogue: 0,0:27:10.99,0:27:12.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們還提供了證據
Dialogue: 0,0:27:12.32,0:27:15.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來自可吉基國家警察指揮所的電子日志
Dialogue: 0,0:27:15.41,0:27:17.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我  那些日志肯定被篡改了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:17.65,0:27:18.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但按理來說
Dialogue: 0,0:27:18.37,0:27:20.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有可吉基國家警察內部的人
Dialogue: 0,0:27:20.01,0:27:21.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-才能做到  -沒錯
Dialogue: 0,0:27:21.76,0:27:23.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克拉拉  我覺得你一開始就是對的
Dialogue: 0,0:27:23.99,0:27:26.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德爾加多從來都不符合克麗兇手的側寫
Dialogue: 0,0:27:28.25,0:27:30.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,問題是  他為什么要跑
Dialogue: 0,0:27:31.05,0:27:32.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許他不相信當地警方
Dialogue: 0,0:27:33.09,0:27:37.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許吧  德爾加多的工作重點是提高
Dialogue: 0,0:27:37.47,0:27:39.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可吉基國家警察的網絡安全
Dialogue: 0,0:27:39.52,0:27:41.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以如果他無意中發現了一些
Dialogue: 0,0:27:41.33,0:27:42.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不該發現的東西呢
Dialogue: 0,0:27:43.00,0:27:45.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一個秘密  一個如此危險的秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:27:45.42,0:27:47.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以至于可吉基國家警察內部的人
Dialogue: 0,0:27:47.25,0:27:49.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不惜將謀殺案嫁禍給他
Dialogue: 0,0:27:49.96,0:27:51.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  還有一件事
Dialogue: 0,0:27:51.75,0:27:54.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道那個保安  阿倫·薩布里嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:27:54.24,0:27:57.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑體簡體\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}阿倫·薩布里\N安保團隊
Dialogue: 0,0:27:54.28,0:27:56.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在全球策略開發做保安只是他的副業
Dialogue: 0,0:27:56.29,0:27:59.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的主要工作是可吉基國家警察的巡警
Dialogue: 0,0:27:59.44,0:28:00.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,記得他手上的擦傷嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:28:00.93,0:28:02.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些梅無法解釋的擦傷
Dialogue: 0,0:28:01.09,0:28:02.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑體簡體\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}尸檢報告
Dialogue: 0,0:28:03.26,0:28:05.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果擦傷不是因為和德爾加多扭打呢
Dialogue: 0,0:28:05.46,0:28:07.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果那是在一遍又一遍
Dialogue: 0,0:28:07.44,0:28:08.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刺傷克麗時產生的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:28:08.58,0:28:11.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你認為最初的計劃是保安殺死克麗
Dialogue: 0,0:28:11.81,0:28:15.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后在德爾加多企圖逃跑時殺了他
Dialogue: 0,0:28:15.37,0:28:17.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過德爾加多沒讓他得逞
Dialogue: 0,0:28:17.66,0:28:19.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很可惜  雖然聽起來很合理
Dialogue: 0,0:28:19.94,0:28:21.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這仍然只是推測
Dialogue: 0,0:28:21.43,0:28:23.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  鑒于我們現在的狀態
Dialogue: 0,0:28:23.32,0:28:24.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們需要確鑿的證據證明
Dialogue: 0,0:28:24.66,0:28:27.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可吉基國家警察內部的人是幕后黑手
Dialogue: 0,0:28:27.67,0:28:29.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不確定在被剝奪一切的情況下
Dialogue: 0,0:28:29.87,0:28:32.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們還能證明什么
Dialogue: 0,0:28:33.20,0:28:34.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許并不是一切
Dialogue: 0,0:28:35.29,0:28:36.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果德爾加多的事我們沒猜錯
Dialogue: 0,0:28:36.88,0:28:38.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他確實發現了可吉基國家警察的骯臟秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:28:38.84,0:28:40.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他還是我印象中的那個人
Dialogue: 0,0:28:40.94,0:28:42.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他會將證據藏起來
Dialogue: 0,0:28:43.00,0:28:44.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:28:44.20,0:28:46.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他有可能將發現的證據
Dialogue: 0,0:28:46.21,0:28:48.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,發給了這世上他唯一信任的人
Dialogue: 0,0:29:02.49,0:29:04.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你還好嗎  -還好
Dialogue: 0,0:29:11.08,0:29:12.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們只是和我們玩心理游戲
Dialogue: 0,0:29:12.92,0:29:14.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要摧毀我們的意志
Dialogue: 0,0:29:15.49,0:29:17.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  那他們真的很厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:29:17.09,0:29:19.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為我已經無力招架了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:20.97,0:29:22.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都會沒事的
Dialogue: 0,0:29:24.06,0:29:25.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不在乎別人怎么說
Dialogue: 0,0:29:25.46,0:29:29.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但當別人的性命在你手上
Dialogue: 0,0:29:30.07,0:29:32.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就能感受到責任的重量
Dialogue: 0,0:29:34.23,0:29:37.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當然  你表面上能裝作很堅強
Dialogue: 0,0:29:38.06,0:29:41.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我覺得我永遠都學不會如何
Dialogue: 0,0:29:42.35,0:29:44.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能將自己的情感控制自如
Dialogue: 0,0:29:45.81,0:29:47.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果那個人最終沒活下來
Dialogue: 0,0:29:49.92,0:29:51.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你永遠都會質疑自己
Dialogue: 0,0:30:00.31,0:30:02.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蒙哥馬利探員  請你回想一下
Dialogue: 0,0:30:02.92,0:30:07.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德爾加多先生死后發生的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:30:07.88,0:30:11.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你記不記得接到了前方的求救電話
Dialogue: 0,0:30:11.74,0:30:12.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,記得
Dialogue: 0,0:30:12.76,0:30:14.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老大  怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:14.18,0:30:15.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們有麻煩了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:15.14,0:30:16.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們被兄弟會伏擊了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:16.89,0:30:18.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一人遇難  看起來
Dialogue: 0,0:30:18.85,0:30:20.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們想要登機
Dialogue: 0,0:30:20.17,0:30:21.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  我立刻聯系可吉基國家警察
Dialogue: 0,0:30:21.69,0:30:23.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我試過了  他們鞭長莫及
Dialogue: 0,0:30:23.24,0:30:24.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你現在得立刻聯系
Dialogue: 0,0:30:24.67,0:30:26.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美軍格拉納托駐地的裝甲部隊
Dialogue: 0,0:30:28.57,0:30:32.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你為什么無視加勒特組長的直接命令
Dialogue: 0,0:30:32.02,0:30:34.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我沒有無視  我評估了局勢
Dialogue: 0,0:30:34.34,0:30:36.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,查看了地圖  他們也太遠了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:36.65,0:30:39.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許你可以告訴我們
Dialogue: 0,0:30:39.23,0:30:42.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是什么時候知道
Dialogue: 0,0:30:42.10,0:30:45.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Z-TAC夜鷹S-2的存在的
Dialogue: 0,0:30:45.64,0:30:49.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能告訴你一個不存在的項目  對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:30:49.15,0:30:50.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你肯定覺得自己聰明極了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:50.58,0:30:53.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我認為夜鷹S-2是美國情報界
Dialogue: 0,0:30:53.27,0:30:54.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人盡皆知的秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:30:55.09,0:30:57.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是杰克·加勒特命令你黑進
Dialogue: 0,0:30:57.69,0:30:58.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夜鷹系統的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:30:58.98,0:31:00.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是
Dialogue: 0,0:31:00.48,0:31:02.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-現在什么情況  -他們在撞門
Dialogue: 0,0:31:02.56,0:31:03.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰克  依我看來
Dialogue: 0,0:31:03.93,0:31:06.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你唯一的選擇就是立刻起飛
Dialogue: 0,0:31:06.04,0:31:07.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這我可能無法做到
Dialogue: 0,0:31:07.58,0:31:09.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他們把我們包圍了  -不會很久
Dialogue: 0,0:31:15.11,0:31:16.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蒙哥馬利探員
Dialogue: 0,0:31:15.23,0:31:16.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑體簡體\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}全球無人機控制系統
Dialogue: 0,0:31:16.45,0:31:18.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道盜用并損毀
Dialogue: 0,0:31:18.95,0:31:24.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一架1.64億美元的無人機是什么后果嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:31:24.45,0:31:26.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無意冒犯  1.64億美元
Dialogue: 0,0:31:26.19,0:31:28.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是包括項目的研發費用
Dialogue: 0,0:31:28.26,0:31:31.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一架無人機的價格是374萬美元
Dialogue: 0,0:31:31.98,0:31:34.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你覺得這是開玩笑嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:31:34.13,0:31:36.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  你想知道我有沒有偷無人機
Dialogue: 0,0:31:37.02,0:31:40.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我偷了  我偷無人機是因為有武裝分子
Dialogue: 0,0:31:40.16,0:31:42.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,追殺我的隊友  所以我黑進了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:42.61,0:31:44.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,附近正在飛行的最近的監控無人機
Dialogue: 0,0:31:44.54,0:31:48.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用其掃射了飛機場  好幾遍
Dialogue: 0,0:31:51.25,0:31:52.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還好那些信念兄弟會的人
Dialogue: 0,0:31:52.24,0:31:53.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常不擅長射飛靶
Dialogue: 0,0:31:53.59,0:31:54.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為這樣會
Dialogue: 0,0:31:54.77,0:31:56.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把他們的注意力從飛機那里吸引過來
Dialogue: 0,0:31:56.86,0:32:01.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我則是制造了一個374萬美金的燈光秀
Dialogue: 0,0:32:02.26,0:32:03.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來讓我的隊友駕駛飛機起飛
Dialogue: 0,0:32:03.96,0:32:05.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逃出生天
Dialogue: 0,0:32:05.12,0:32:06.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道敵方的傷亡嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:32:06.96,0:32:10.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-沒有傷亡  -當時你并不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:32:10.33,0:32:11.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白這事到頭來
Dialogue: 0,0:32:11.89,0:32:13.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必須要有人來擔責
Dialogue: 0,0:32:13.23,0:32:14.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是事實是
Dialogue: 0,0:32:15.31,0:32:19.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有極少數的一部分被選中的人
Dialogue: 0,0:32:19.23,0:32:20.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是有資格在前線工作的
Dialogue: 0,0:32:21.37,0:32:22.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是無可辯駁的
Dialogue: 0,0:32:23.46,0:32:26.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們有更好的直覺  判斷
Dialogue: 0,0:32:27.73,0:32:29.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勇氣
Dialogue: 0,0:32:29.80,0:32:33.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為這是必需的
Dialogue: 0,0:32:34.04,0:32:35.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為在情急之下
Dialogue: 0,0:32:36.10,0:32:37.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們要做出艱難的選擇
Dialogue: 0,0:32:38.77,0:32:42.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你覺得你是那少數被選中人之一嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:32:45.26,0:32:46.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是覺得
Dialogue: 0,0:32:48.00,0:32:50.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是清楚知道  所以我做了那些事
Dialogue: 0,0:32:50.17,0:32:51.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次我還會這么做
Dialogue: 0,0:32:51.22,0:32:53.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在我準備接受我的行為所帶來的后果
Dialogue: 0,0:32:54.39,0:32:57.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好  蒙哥馬利探員  因為
Dialogue: 0,0:32:58.13,0:32:59.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你由于故意盜竊
Dialogue: 0,0:32:59.64,0:33:01.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玩忽職守
Dialogue: 0,0:33:01.94,0:33:03.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和破壞政府財物而被捕了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:04.10,0:33:05.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交出你的警徽
Dialogue: 0,0:33:21.12,0:33:22.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  阿米莉亞
Dialogue: 0,0:33:24.01,0:33:26.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你來見我
Dialogue: 0,0:33:29.72,0:33:31.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和愛德之間無所不談  克拉拉
Dialogue: 0,0:33:32.89,0:33:34.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天我來是因為我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:33:34.81,0:33:36.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是他的生命中很重要的一個人
Dialogue: 0,0:33:36.46,0:33:39.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我真的需要有人能為他
Dialogue: 0,0:33:39.02,0:33:40.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有克麗伸張正義
Dialogue: 0,0:33:41.15,0:33:42.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這正是我想要做的
Dialogue: 0,0:33:44.59,0:33:47.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以看看他給你發的照片嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:33:56.63,0:33:57.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛德有這種習慣嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:33:57.89,0:34:00.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會經常給你發他偷拍的快照
Dialogue: 0,0:34:00.35,0:34:02.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有  不過還好他發了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:06.24,0:34:08.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能把這些也給我發一份嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:34:09.38,0:34:10.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什么
Dialogue: 0,0:34:10.79,0:34:12.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿米莉亞  我和我的隊友認為
Dialogue: 0,0:34:12.40,0:34:14.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛德是因為發現了一個秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:34:14.28,0:34:16.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而被陷害謀殺了克麗
Dialogue: 0,0:34:16.30,0:34:18.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我認為這些照片能告訴我
Dialogue: 0,0:34:18.93,0:34:20.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秘密到底是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:34:24.81,0:34:26.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:34:27.59,0:34:29.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-沒事的  杰克  -不  有事
Dialogue: 0,0:34:29.76,0:34:33.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別插手  朋友  隨它去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:34:33.09,0:34:34.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是按規章走的流程
Dialogue: 0,0:34:34.33,0:34:35.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罪名是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:34:35.26,0:34:36.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這重要嗎  杰克
Dialogue: 0,0:34:36.42,0:34:38.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這已經是最糟的情況了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:38.17,0:34:39.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沃爾特  聽我說
Dialogue: 0,0:34:39.27,0:34:40.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德爾加多是被陷害的
Dialogue: 0,0:34:40.86,0:34:42.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我或許有辦法拿到證據
Dialogue: 0,0:34:42.61,0:34:44.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西格爾和西蒙斯探員正在...
Dialogue: 0,0:34:45.70,0:34:47.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西格爾和西蒙斯不能參與任何工作
Dialogue: 0,0:34:47.75,0:34:48.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:34:49.48,0:34:50.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,該死的  杰克
Dialogue: 0,0:34:50.57,0:34:52.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你又把你自己陷于不利
Dialogue: 0,0:34:52.67,0:34:54.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這可是違抗命令
Dialogue: 0,0:34:54.52,0:34:56.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是是  更不用說
Dialogue: 0,0:34:56.59,0:34:59.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有失聯邦政府官員身份的行為了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:59.60,0:35:01.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把他帶回樓上
Dialogue: 0,0:35:17.69,0:35:20.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請坐
Dialogue: 0,0:35:22.10,0:35:23.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加勒特組長
Dialogue: 0,0:35:23.20,0:35:25.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在今天的會談過程中
Dialogue: 0,0:35:25.15,0:35:27.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是否與你的國際反應小組成員
Dialogue: 0,0:35:27.05,0:35:28.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有過交流
Dialogue: 0,0:35:28.81,0:35:30.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是的  -你是什么時候
Dialogue: 0,0:35:30.72,0:35:33.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在什么地方與他們進行的違規交流
Dialogue: 0,0:35:33.03,0:35:34.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我小組里的其他成員一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:35:34.21,0:35:37.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要對德爾加多先生的死負責
Dialogue: 0,0:35:37.05,0:35:38.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我問的不是這個
Dialogue: 0,0:35:38.09,0:35:39.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是我們在這里的原因
Dialogue: 0,0:35:39.24,0:35:40.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加勒特組長
Dialogue: 0,0:35:40.03,0:35:42.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,造成德爾加多先生死亡的真正原因
Dialogue: 0,0:35:43.30,0:35:44.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是背叛
Dialogue: 0,0:35:45.73,0:35:46.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在說什么
Dialogue: 0,0:35:47.05,0:35:48.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是個好人  盡忠職守
Dialogue: 0,0:35:48.87,0:35:51.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只不過碰巧發現了一個秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:35:51.50,0:35:53.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他發現了可吉基國家警察
Dialogue: 0,0:35:53.63,0:35:55.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和信念兄弟會首腦之間的交易
Dialogue: 0,0:35:55.56,0:35:56.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是拉尚·努里
Dialogue: 0,0:35:57.76,0:35:59.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們出賣恐怖分子的名單
Dialogue: 0,0:35:59.83,0:36:01.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作為交換  可吉基國家警察向努里保證
Dialogue: 0,0:36:01.69,0:36:02.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會對他們的犯罪行為
Dialogue: 0,0:36:02.62,0:36:04.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睜一只眼閉一只眼
Dialogue: 0,0:36:04.46,0:36:07.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這其中包括買賣可吉基兒童
Dialogue: 0,0:36:08.06,0:36:10.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么知道這些的
Dialogue: 0,0:36:10.19,0:36:12.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德爾加多遵循了規章制度
Dialogue: 0,0:36:12.01,0:36:14.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在卡利葉見了美國反貪調查員
Dialogue: 0,0:36:14.28,0:36:17.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提供了證據  不過為了回答你的問題
Dialogue: 0,0:36:17.23,0:36:21.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道這一切是由于德爾加多先生
Dialogue: 0,0:36:21.26,0:36:23.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還違反了規章
Dialogue: 0,0:36:23.70,0:36:26.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他還把一份證據副本用加密信息
Dialogue: 0,0:36:26.87,0:36:29.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藏在照片里發給了他的妻子
Dialogue: 0,0:36:30.95,0:36:32.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是這一份
Dialogue: 0,0:36:36.14,0:36:39.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是說愛德華·德爾加多用了隱寫術嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:36:39.13,0:36:43.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對  他用一份電子檔案作為另一份的偽裝
Dialogue: 0,0:36:43.00,0:36:45.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你繼續翻后面那些圖片
Dialogue: 0,0:36:45.39,0:36:47.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你會找到行為分析部的技術分析員
Dialogue: 0,0:36:47.72,0:36:51.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佩內洛普·加西亞提供給我的加密信息
Dialogue: 0,0:36:51.32,0:36:52.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:36:54.68,0:36:57.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拋開這份證據不談  你的行為...
Dialogue: 0,0:36:57.31,0:36:59.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這份證據證明了國際行動小組
Dialogue: 0,0:36:59.67,0:37:01.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和德爾加多一樣是被陷害的
Dialogue: 0,0:37:02.01,0:37:02.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被陷害
Dialogue: 0,0:37:02.99,0:37:05.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對  因為這份與魔鬼的協議
Dialogue: 0,0:37:05.80,0:37:07.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最有損名譽的部分是
Dialogue: 0,0:37:07.50,0:37:10.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這一切都是在一位美國情報部門官員的
Dialogue: 0,0:37:10.71,0:37:12.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非法批準下進行的
Dialogue: 0,0:37:12.41,0:37:14.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就是必須要陷害德爾加多的原因
Dialogue: 0,0:37:14.27,0:37:16.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就是必須要伏擊我的團隊的原因
Dialogue: 0,0:37:16.51,0:37:19.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了保護這位代號為"象"的
Dialogue: 0,0:37:20.23,0:37:21.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,官員的身份
Dialogue: 0,0:37:22.18,0:37:24.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我必須要告訴你如果你指控
Dialogue: 0,0:37:24.99,0:37:26.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一位情報部門官員
Dialogue: 0,0:37:26.85,0:37:28.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而沒有足夠證據的話...
Dialogue: 0,0:37:28.27,0:37:30.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這才是關鍵所在  對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:37:30.46,0:37:32.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你生活在一個被謊言籠罩的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:37:32.93,0:37:34.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又何從找到真相
Dialogue: 0,0:37:35.69,0:37:38.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想這就是檔案派上用場的時候了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:39.24,0:37:43.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能找到行為背后的動機
Dialogue: 0,0:37:43.36,0:37:45.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謊言背后的始作俑者
Dialogue: 0,0:37:47.35,0:37:48.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得你已經知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:48.88,0:37:50.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這些問題的答案  杰克
Dialogue: 0,0:37:50.26,0:37:52.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的確是知道的  琳達
Dialogue: 0,0:37:52.46,0:37:55.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先要好好想想誰會從中獲益
Dialogue: 0,0:37:56.53,0:37:59.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,利用像努里這樣現成的資源
Dialogue: 0,0:37:59.11,0:38:00.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰是最大的受益者
Dialogue: 0,0:38:00.99,0:38:03.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更重要的是  誰有這個膽量
Dialogue: 0,0:38:03.50,0:38:05.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敢和魔鬼做交易
Dialogue: 0,0:38:07.59,0:38:09.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個人肯定是心安理得地
Dialogue: 0,0:38:09.99,0:38:13.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,將必要采取的惡行合理化
Dialogue: 0,0:38:13.00,0:38:15.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來保護更大的利益
Dialogue: 0,0:38:16.34,0:38:17.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個人一定是認為
Dialogue: 0,0:38:17.79,0:38:19.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結果比過程更重要
Dialogue: 0,0:38:19.36,0:38:20.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯
Dialogue: 0,0:38:21.48,0:38:22.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你明白我在說什么吧
Dialogue: 0,0:38:23.90,0:38:28.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,象  所以這個人
Dialogue: 0,0:38:28.87,0:38:30.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能也很喜歡國際象棋吧
Dialogue: 0,0:38:30.37,0:38:33.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為在國際象棋中  象這個角色
Dialogue: 0,0:38:33.26,0:38:36.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,往往被視為陰險  狡猾
Dialogue: 0,0:38:37.86,0:38:39.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且墮落
Dialogue: 0,0:38:39.52,0:38:41.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你總能驅王使后
Dialogue: 0,0:38:43.69,0:38:45.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴恩斯助理主任
Dialogue: 0,0:38:45.20,0:38:48.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是我是你  我接下來會謹言慎行的
Dialogue: 0,0:38:49.02,0:38:51.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是這么打算的
Dialogue: 0,0:38:52.26,0:38:54.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿特伍德副主任  你被捕了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:54.21,0:38:55.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有權保持沉默
Dialogue: 0,0:38:55.98,0:38:57.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是來真的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:38:58.30,0:38:59.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰克的那套心理側寫
Dialogue: 0,0:38:59.98,0:39:01.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是一派胡言  算不上證據
Dialogue: 0,0:39:01.55,0:39:03.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是加西亞探員在你的私人服務器上
Dialogue: 0,0:39:03.33,0:39:06.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,發現的郵件是證據  沃爾特
Dialogue: 0,0:39:07.56,0:39:10.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你根本不知道你做了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:39:10.59,0:39:12.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這個混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:39:12.84,0:39:14.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你害死了德爾加多
Dialogue: 0,0:39:14.71,0:39:16.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你讓我的團隊處于險境
Dialogue: 0,0:39:16.28,0:39:17.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把我們當成犧牲品
Dialogue: 0,0:39:17.35,0:39:19.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們就是犧牲品
Dialogue: 0,0:39:19.60,0:39:22.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為你們是士兵  杰克  我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:39:22.13,0:39:24.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,士兵們會犧牲自己
Dialogue: 0,0:39:24.54,0:39:26.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來保護其他人
Dialogue: 0,0:39:26.45,0:39:29.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以為我喜歡和努里這種混蛋同流合污嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:39:29.80,0:39:32.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說得對  這就是必須采取的惡行
Dialogue: 0,0:39:32.68,0:39:33.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道為什么嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:39:33.28,0:39:36.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為我們正處在戰爭中  朋友們
Dialogue: 0,0:39:36.06,0:39:38.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別搞錯了  就是因為我們告訴大家
Dialogue: 0,0:39:38.12,0:39:40.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以一如既往地安居樂業
Dialogue: 0,0:39:40.47,0:39:43.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們為了實現這些理想才進行骯臟的斗爭
Dialogue: 0,0:39:43.98,0:39:45.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果沒有我這種人
Dialogue: 0,0:39:45.68,0:39:48.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有我這種采取必要惡行的人
Dialogue: 0,0:39:48.78,0:39:50.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們就會輸
Dialogue: 0,0:39:50.61,0:39:52.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少擺出這副自以為是的樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:39:52.60,0:39:55.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么好意思把自己
Dialogue: 0,0:39:55.73,0:39:57.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和那些士兵們相提并論
Dialogue: 0,0:39:58.58,0:39:59.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是個小辦事員
Dialogue: 0,0:40:00.39,0:40:01.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是名罪犯
Dialogue: 0,0:40:02.30,0:40:03.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帶他出去
Dialogue: 0,0:40:20.28,0:40:21.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么樣
Dialogue: 0,0:40:22.21,0:40:24.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好多了  畢竟現在沒帶著手銬了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:24.14,0:40:26.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但到底是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:40:30.63,0:40:32.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鑒于我們目前的情況
Dialogue: 0,0:40:32.31,0:40:34.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我對這個結果沒意見
Dialogue: 0,0:40:35.03,0:40:36.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:40:36.38,0:40:37.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顯然  我沒有隱瞞自己的想法
Dialogue: 0,0:40:37.72,0:40:39.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想削弱國際反應小組的作用
Dialogue: 0,0:40:39.97,0:40:41.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想擺脫我們
Dialogue: 0,0:40:41.66,0:40:42.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要你們能負起責任
Dialogue: 0,0:40:42.84,0:40:45.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們是負責的  一直如此
Dialogue: 0,0:40:45.70,0:40:47.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你叫我來干什么呢  杰克
Dialogue: 0,0:40:47.60,0:40:50.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是來要求對蒙哥馬利探員寬大處理的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:40:50.55,0:40:52.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這正是我想說的
Dialogue: 0,0:40:52.05,0:40:54.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盡管他意圖是好的  結果也不壞
Dialogue: 0,0:40:54.97,0:40:57.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但蒙哥馬利探員
Dialogue: 0,0:40:57.26,0:40:59.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必須為他自己的行為負責
Dialogue: 0,0:40:59.68,0:41:01.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算我同意
Dialogue: 0,0:41:01.15,0:41:02.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不提起刑事訴訟
Dialogue: 0,0:41:03.25,0:41:06.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但最起碼局里必須要辭退他
Dialogue: 0,0:41:06.90,0:41:07.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她說得對  杰克
Dialogue: 0,0:41:08.27,0:41:09.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不認同
Dialogue: 0,0:41:10.29,0:41:12.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為蒙哥馬利探員的行為
Dialogue: 0,0:41:12.31,0:41:14.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我團隊中任何人所做的任何行為
Dialogue: 0,0:41:15.14,0:41:16.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是基于我的命令
Dialogue: 0,0:41:16.19,0:41:18.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無論是直接下達的還是暗示的
Dialogue: 0,0:41:18.58,0:41:20.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切責任都應該由我承擔
Dialogue: 0,0:41:20.17,0:41:23.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算有人要被開除  那也該是我
Dialogue: 0,0:41:24.79,0:41:26.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我認真的  琳達
Dialogue: 0,0:41:26.13,0:41:28.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你是認真的  杰克  但你可能
Dialogue: 0,0:41:28.47,0:41:30.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還不清楚現在的情況
Dialogue: 0,0:41:30.77,0:41:31.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你剛剛扳倒了
Dialogue: 0,0:41:31.55,0:41:33.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,國家情報局的副主任
Dialogue: 0,0:41:33.32,0:41:35.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在要我來停你的職嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:41:35.36,0:41:37.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯啊  因為就該如此
Dialogue: 0,0:41:37.97,0:41:39.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就是責任
Dialogue: 0,0:41:44.52,0:41:47.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰克·加勒特組長  我先跟你說清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:41:47.86,0:41:50.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會盯著你和你的小組
Dialogue: 0,0:41:50.96,0:41:52.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以把這當成是第一振
Dialogue: 0,0:41:52.56,0:41:55.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在這場博弈中  第二振你就會出局
Dialogue: 0,0:42:08.14,0:42:09.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你還好嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:42:09.38,0:42:12.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別提我了  他們都準備把你關起來了
Dialogue: 0,0:42:12.47,0:42:14.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  但我知道你們會來救我的  對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:42:14.53,0:42:16.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也可能是和你關在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:42:16.33,0:42:17.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們是彼此的堅強后盾
Dialogue: 0,0:42:18.06,0:42:22.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的確  我們回家吧  休息一下
Dialogue: 0,0:42:23.45,0:42:24.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位
Dialogue: 0,0:42:28.96,0:42:31.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,壞蛋們可從不休息
Dialogue: 0,0:42:34.42,0:42:35.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,確實
Dialogue: 0,0:42:36.94,0:42:38.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看來我們又有工作了
Dialogue: 0,0:42:39.46,0:42:43.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}聯邦調查局國際反應小組
