1
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:05,000
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

2
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:05,000
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

3
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:05,000
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

4
00:00:00,500 --> 00:00:05,000
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

5
00:00:00,500 --> 00:00:05,000
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35

6
00:00:00,500 --> 00:00:05,000
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

7
00:00:00,500 --> 00:00:05,000
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

8
00:00:00,500 --> 00:00:05,000
原创翻译  双语字幕

9
00:00:01,000 --> 00:00:05,000
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利

10
00:00:06,220 --> 00:00:41,220
m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

11
00:00:05,720 --> 00:00:41,220
m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

12
00:00:06,220 --> 00:00:11,220
翻译     showeryhe  Brisingr

13
00:00:11,220 --> 00:00:16,220
翻译     胖达萌萌哒  潇然

14
00:00:16,220 --> 00:00:21,220
翻译     无序脚印  tokilltime

15
00:00:21,220 --> 00:00:26,220
校对     潇然  胡说大王

16
00:00:26,220 --> 00:00:31,220
时间轴     风吹来的那片云

17
00:00:31,220 --> 00:00:36,220
后期     灰灰是菇凉

18
00:00:36,220 --> 00:00:41,220
总监     showeryhe

19
00:00:00,700 --> 00:00:02,530
联调局国际反应小组

20
00:00:01,640 --> 00:00:03,390
每年有超过6800万美国人
Over 68 million Americans

21
00:00:03,390 --> 00:00:05,880
离开安全的国内
leave the safety of our borders every year.

22
00:00:06,050 --> 00:00:07,610
当危险来袭
If danger strikes,

23
00:00:07,840 --> 00:00:10,440
联调局国际反应小组
the FBI's International Response Team

24
00:00:10,440 --> 00:00:12,010
随时出动
is called into action.

25
00:00:11,230 --> 00:00:13,740
弗吉尼亚州  匡提科

26
00:00:37,940 --> 00:00:38,960
没事的
We got you.

27
00:01:20,460 --> 00:01:22,180
杰克·加勒特组长
Unit Chief Jack Garrett,

28
00:01:22,190 --> 00:01:24,200
今天你有权保持沉默
you have the right to remain silent

29
00:01:24,200 --> 00:01:26,230
并拒绝回答问题
and refuse to answer questions today.

30
00:01:26,360 --> 00:01:28,250
如果放弃该权利  那你所说的所有内容
If you give up that right, anything you say

31
00:01:28,250 --> 00:01:30,760
都可以并将用来作为呈堂证供
can and will be used against you in a court of law.

32
00:01:30,980 --> 00:01:32,610
在讯问开始之前及进行过程中
You have the right to consult with an attorney

33
00:01:32,610 --> 00:01:34,730
你都有权找律师咨询
before and during this questioning.

34
00:01:35,100 --> 00:01:36,660
如果你无力聘请律师
If you cannot afford an attorney...

35
00:01:40,320 --> 00:01:41,230
对不起
I'm sorry.

36
00:01:42,900 --> 00:01:44,570
杰克·加勒特组长  你明白
Unit Chief Garrett, do you understand these rights

37
00:01:44,570 --> 00:01:45,850
我刚才解释的这些权利了吗
as I've explained them to you?

38
00:01:47,930 --> 00:01:48,760
明白
Yes.

39
00:01:51,770 --> 00:01:54,300
犯罪心理  国境之外

40
00:01:52,620 --> 00:01:54,300
第二季第九集

41
00:02:29,310 --> 00:02:34,990
要想保守秘密

42
00:02:31,210 --> 00:02:34,990
除非其他知情者都是死人

43
00:02:33,070 --> 00:02:34,990
本杰明·富兰克林

44
00:02:38,550 --> 00:02:40,800
你现在是否愿意坐下回答我们的问题
Are you willing to sit down now and answer our questions?

45
00:02:42,330 --> 00:02:43,180
是的
Yes.

46
00:02:47,200 --> 00:02:50,110
杰克  你确定不要律师吗
Jack, are you sure you don't want your lawyer?

47
00:02:50,360 --> 00:02:51,530
可能会来狠的
It could get rough.

48
00:02:52,620 --> 00:02:53,880
我不需要律师
I don't need a lawyer.

49
00:02:54,220 --> 00:02:56,620
请记录国际反应小组组长杰克·加勒特
Let the record reflect that IRT Unit Chief Jack Garrett

50
00:02:56,620 --> 00:02:58,860
此次放弃咨询律师的权利
has waived his right to counsel at this time.

51
00:02:58,990 --> 00:03:01,500
此次与会的还有
Let us identify those also present for this session --

52
00:03:01,500 --> 00:03:03,510
来自联调局职业责任办公室的
Agents Brian Lynch and Jody Reynolds

53
00:03:03,510 --> 00:03:06,410
布莱恩·林奇和乔迪·雷诺兹探员
with the FBI's Office of Professional Responsibility.

54
00:03:06,680 --> 00:03:09,290
哥伦比亚特区的副法顾贾尼丝·赖切尔
Janice Reichel, Deputy Counsel, District of Columbia,

55
00:03:09,290 --> 00:03:11,320
代表司法部出席
representing the Department of Justice.

56
00:03:11,340 --> 00:03:13,930
国家情报局副主任沃尔特·阿特伍德
Walter Atwood, Deputy Director of National Intelligence,

57
00:03:13,930 --> 00:03:16,700
而我是联调局国家安全处的执行助理主任
and I am Linda Barnes, Executive Assistant Director

58
00:03:16,700 --> 00:03:18,760
琳达·巴恩斯
of the FBI's National Security Branch.

59
00:03:18,920 --> 00:03:21,240
阿特伍德副主任和我受全权委托
Deputy Director Atwood and I have been authorized

60
00:03:21,240 --> 00:03:23,590
来负责此次联调局与国情局的联合讯问
to conduct this joint inquiry for the FBI and DNI.

61
00:03:23,590 --> 00:03:24,990
加勒特组长
Now, Unit Chief Garrett,

62
00:03:24,990 --> 00:03:26,280
你能否从头开始
can you walk us through the beginnings

63
00:03:26,290 --> 00:03:28,270
说说可吉基斯坦卡利叶
of Case Number 67-16-01

64
00:03:28,270 --> 00:03:30,270
编号67-16-01的案件
in Qalea, Kurjikistan?

65
00:03:30,510 --> 00:03:33,020
我们在里斯本给飞机加燃料
We were refueling in Lisbon,

66
00:03:30,510 --> 00:03:33,020
葡萄牙首都

67
00:03:33,200 --> 00:03:36,250
这时罗素·蒙哥马利探员通知我们
when Agent Russell Montgomery gave notification

68
00:03:36,250 --> 00:03:39,600
美国大使及可吉基斯坦外交部
about a request from the U.S. Ambassador

69
00:03:39,820 --> 00:03:42,250
要求我们参与协助
and the Kurjikistan Foreign Minister.

70
00:03:42,380 --> 00:03:45,600
是涉及一位美国公民及一位可吉基公民的
It was a double homicide involving a U.S. Citizen

71
00:03:45,600 --> 00:03:47,210
双尸案
and a Kurjik national.

72
00:03:47,240 --> 00:03:48,550
克丽·洛德尔  二十九岁
Keri Lodel, 29.

73
00:03:48,550 --> 00:03:50,470
是罗得岛州普罗维登斯人
She's from Providence, Rhode Island,

74
00:03:50,480 --> 00:03:52,710
她在全球策略开发
and she worked as a network engineer

75
00:03:52,720 --> 00:03:56,490
这家美国承包单位  做网络工程师
for a U.S. Contractor called Global Strategem Development.

76
00:03:56,490 --> 00:03:57,950
还有阿伦·萨布里
Also, Aron Sabri,

77
00:03:57,950 --> 00:03:59,800
三十二岁  卡利叶人
32, from Qalea.

78
00:03:59,800 --> 00:04:01,820
他在全球策略开发做保安
He worked as a security guard for GSD.

79
00:04:01,830 --> 00:04:04,830
据可吉基国家警察的里法伊长官
Now according to Captain Rifai of the Kurjik National Police,

80
00:04:04,830 --> 00:04:06,980
一位据称与克丽有染的同事
Keri was stabbed to death by by a co-worker

81
00:04:06,980 --> 00:04:09,110
将她活活捅死
who she was allegedly having an affair with.

82
00:04:09,190 --> 00:04:11,370
那个人叫爱德华·德尔加多
That man's name is Edward Delgado.

83
00:04:11,370 --> 00:04:12,920
德尔加多  四十六岁
Delgado is 46 years old,

84
00:04:12,920 --> 00:04:14,530
是弗吉尼亚州亚历山德里亚人
from Alexandria, Virginia.

85
00:04:14,540 --> 00:04:15,610
担任系统分析员
He's a systems analyst,

86
00:04:15,610 --> 00:04:17,480
已婚并育有一个两岁的女儿
and he's married with a 2-year-old daughter.

87
00:04:17,480 --> 00:04:18,980
当地保安萨布里
Sabri, the local security guard,

88
00:04:18,980 --> 00:04:19,870
似乎在与德尔加多
appears to have died

89
00:04:19,870 --> 00:04:21,340
打斗过程中身亡
during the struggle with Delgado

90
00:04:21,340 --> 00:04:23,740
而德尔加多则趁机逃出居住区
as he fled the GSD housing compound.

91
00:04:23,800 --> 00:04:24,870
看来都发生在
So it looks like all this took place

92
00:04:24,870 --> 00:04:26,520
卡利叶的钢圈中
inside of Qalea's Steel Ring.

93
00:04:27,080 --> 00:04:28,120
钢圈
Steel Ring?

94
00:04:28,220 --> 00:04:30,800
是一片六平方千米的严守地区
It's a heavily fortified 4-square-mile area

95
00:04:30,800 --> 00:04:32,720
伊拉克首都

96
00:04:30,800 --> 00:04:32,720
类似于巴格达的绿区
much like Baghdad's Green Zone.

97
00:04:33,050 --> 00:04:35,680
杰克  我认识德尔加多
Jack, uh, I know Delgado.

98
00:04:35,710 --> 00:04:36,590
你认识他吗
You know him?

99
00:04:36,740 --> 00:04:38,310
以前有过接触
I-I mean, knew him.

100
00:04:38,310 --> 00:04:40,890
曾在缅甸一家非政府组织共事
We used to work together for an NGO in Myanmar.

101
00:04:41,450 --> 00:04:42,410
什么时候的事
When was this?

102
00:04:43,100 --> 00:04:45,400
三年前  我请假离开那段时间
Three years ago when I took my leave of absence.

103
00:04:45,400 --> 00:04:46,810
你对他有什么印象
What do you remember about him?

104
00:04:46,810 --> 00:04:49,310
说实话  我觉得完全说不通
Honestly, this doesn't make any sense to me at all.

105
00:04:49,310 --> 00:04:49,980
我认识的那个人
The man that I knew --

106
00:04:49,980 --> 00:04:51,560
哪怕很生气  音量也不会提高
he could barely raise his voice in anger,

107
00:04:51,560 --> 00:04:52,890
而别提杀人了
much less escalate to murder.

108
00:04:52,890 --> 00:04:55,230
不止是杀人  他现在可是逃犯
Not only that, he's a fugitive now.

109
00:04:55,750 --> 00:04:58,450
塞格尔探员的工作就是分析
As someone whose job requires her to analyze

110
00:04:58,460 --> 00:05:01,300
并对犯罪嫌疑人给出客观侧写
and objectively profile the behaviors of criminal suspects,

111
00:05:01,300 --> 00:05:04,250
那她的判断力难道不是已经受影响了吗
wasn't Agent Seger's judgment already compromised?

112
00:05:04,250 --> 00:05:05,500
完全没有
No, not at all.

113
00:05:05,820 --> 00:05:06,920
完全没有
Not at all?

114
00:05:07,640 --> 00:05:10,290
塞格尔探员和德尔加多以前的接触
You don't believe Agent Seger's history with Mr. Delgado

115
00:05:10,300 --> 00:05:13,140
你认为不会以任何方式影响她的能力
could have in any way impacted her ability to --

116
00:05:13,140 --> 00:05:15,490
不  我不认为  正如我不相信
No, I don't, just like I don't believe

117
00:05:15,500 --> 00:05:18,310
阿特伍德副主任和我的老交情
that Deputy Director Atwood's longtime friendship with me

118
00:05:18,310 --> 00:05:20,600
可能影响他在本次讯问过程中
is going to impact his ability to be objective

119
00:05:20,600 --> 00:05:22,060
保持客观公正的能力
during this inquiry.

120
00:05:24,630 --> 00:05:26,310
塞格尔探员有没有向你
Did Agent Seger disclose to you

121
00:05:26,310 --> 00:05:27,530
或团队中其他成员
or to any other member of your team

122
00:05:27,530 --> 00:05:30,410
完全交代她过去和德尔加多先生的关系
the full extent of her prior relationship with Mr. Delgado?

123
00:05:30,420 --> 00:05:33,730
塞格尔探员坦言三年前
Agent Seger disclosed that she previously worked with him

124
00:05:33,730 --> 00:05:35,470
他们曾在缅甸共事
in Myanmar three years ago.

125
00:05:35,470 --> 00:05:36,490
她没有刚好提及
She didn't happen to mention

126
00:05:36,500 --> 00:05:38,660
和这个男人的私人关系吗
her personal relationship with this man?

127
00:05:40,000 --> 00:05:44,670
她没有提及  但这不重要  因为
No. She didn't mention it, but doesn't matter because --

128
00:05:44,670 --> 00:05:47,660
重要的是你对团队成员的了解程度
What matters is how well you know the members of your team.

129
00:05:47,740 --> 00:05:50,870
毫无疑问讯问过程中这一块十分重要
No doubt this line of questioning is important,

130
00:05:50,870 --> 00:05:52,410
但我们先跳过吧
but let me jump ahead.

131
00:05:52,420 --> 00:05:56,010
你们登陆该国后  说说有什么流程
When you landed in country, run us through the protocol.

132
00:05:56,060 --> 00:05:58,870
我们到达卡利叶后就开始
When we landed in Qalea, we began coordinating

133
00:05:58,870 --> 00:06:01,340
和巴希尔·里法伊长官协作
with Captain Basir Rifai,

134
00:06:01,340 --> 00:06:03,580
他是可吉基国家警察的负责人
head of the Kurjik National Police.

135
00:06:03,600 --> 00:06:04,350
可惜
Unfortunately,

136
00:06:04,350 --> 00:06:06,090
我手下对逃犯爱德华·德尔加多的追捕
my men have made little progress in our hunt for the fugitive,

137
00:06:06,090 --> 00:06:08,310
一无所获
Edward Delgado.

138
00:06:08,310 --> 00:06:11,340
我们倾向于认为他或许已经逃出了钢圈
We are beginning to believe he may have escaped the Steel Ring

139
00:06:11,340 --> 00:06:13,420
也可能已经死了
and may in fact be already dead.

140
00:06:14,060 --> 00:06:15,790
因为他作为一个在逃的西方人
Because as a westerner on the run,

141
00:06:15,790 --> 00:06:17,270
他可能轻易地落入
he could've easily fallen into the hands

142
00:06:17,270 --> 00:06:19,250
好战组织  信念兄弟会手中
of the militant group, the Brotherhood of Faith.

143
00:06:19,250 --> 00:06:22,260
没错  祸害我国的恐怖组织之一
Yes, one of many terror groups that plague my country.

144
00:06:22,260 --> 00:06:23,160
只有这一个
Only this one was led

145
00:06:23,160 --> 00:06:26,190
是由你们前将军之一拉尚·努里领导的
by one of your former army generals, Rashan Noori.

146
00:06:26,190 --> 00:06:28,730
是的  给我们造成了更深的伤害
Indeed. An even deeper wound for us.

147
00:06:28,730 --> 00:06:30,460
但德尔加多是个非常聪明的人  对吧
But Delgado's a pretty smart guy, right?

148
00:06:30,460 --> 00:06:32,230
你觉得他是否会在安全区外铤而走险呢
So you think if he's really gonna roll the dice

149
00:06:32,230 --> 00:06:34,310
唯一让他敢这么做的原因
outside the Ring, he's only gonna do it

150
00:06:34,310 --> 00:06:35,980
就是他确切知道哪里可以让他躲藏
if he knows exactly where he's gonna be able to hide

151
00:06:35,980 --> 00:06:36,680
一小段时间
for a little bit.

152
00:06:36,680 --> 00:06:39,950
也许贾维斯探员是对的  但以我的经验
You may be right, Agent Jarvis, but in my experience,

153
00:06:40,680 --> 00:06:44,240
穷途之人总会做出极端的决定
the desperate man always makes the desperate choice.

154
00:06:45,200 --> 00:06:48,360
现在我和塞格尔探员要检视案发现场了
Well, right now Agent Seger and I should inspect the crime scene

155
00:06:48,360 --> 00:06:50,880
西蒙斯探员会去推测嫌疑人
while Agent Simmons here evaluates our suspect's

156
00:06:50,880 --> 00:06:53,740
从居住区逃跑后的潜在路线
possible escape routes from the housing compound.

157
00:06:53,740 --> 00:06:54,700
好的  没问题
Yes, of course.

158
00:06:54,700 --> 00:06:58,190
我还需要将克丽·洛德尔和阿伦·萨布里的
I'd also like the bodies of Keri Lodel and Aron Sabri

159
00:06:58,190 --> 00:07:00,030
尸体运回  以便贾维斯探员
brought back here so Agent Jarvis

160
00:07:00,030 --> 00:07:02,520
能进行补充尸检
can conduct supplemental autopsies.

161
00:07:02,560 --> 00:07:04,400
我会安排调度的
I'll arrange for the transfer.

162
00:07:04,990 --> 00:07:07,400
组长  你之前提到的
Unit Chief, earlier you mentioned,

163
00:07:07,410 --> 00:07:10,160
如果没记错  那个可吉基的外交部长
if I'm not mistaken, that the Kurjik Foreign Minister

164
00:07:10,160 --> 00:07:12,370
就是请国际反应小组来协助
was one of the folks who had asked for

165
00:07:12,370 --> 00:07:14,750
这起案件的人之一  对吧
the IRT's help in this matter. Is that right?

166
00:07:14,760 --> 00:07:15,680
是的  没错
Yes, that's right.

167
00:07:15,680 --> 00:07:17,520
你是否
Did you or did you not

168
00:07:17,520 --> 00:07:20,870
承认并且尊重当地政府  里法伊长官
acknowledge and respect the lead investigative role

169
00:07:20,870 --> 00:07:23,380
在此次调查中的主导地位呢
of the local authority, Captain Rifai?

170
00:07:23,990 --> 00:07:28,160
副主任  国际反应小组的职责一直都是
Deputy Director, the IRT's role, as always,

171
00:07:28,160 --> 00:07:30,900
在此双尸案的调查中
was to advise and assist Captain Rifai and the KNP

172
00:07:30,900 --> 00:07:33,960
为里法伊长官和国家警察提供建议和协助
during the course of this double homicide investigation

173
00:07:33,960 --> 00:07:36,980
并且追捕在逃的爱德华·德尔加多
and the pursuit of the fugitive, Edward Delgado.

174
00:07:36,980 --> 00:07:40,190
现在许多建议和协助
Now much of that advice and assistance

175
00:07:40,200 --> 00:07:41,680
都是基于你们团队
comes from your team's ability

176
00:07:41,680 --> 00:07:45,240
建立的犯罪嫌疑人的行为侧写
to build these behavioral profiles of criminal suspects.

177
00:07:45,240 --> 00:07:46,790
-是吗  -没错
- Is that right? - Yes.

178
00:07:46,970 --> 00:07:50,400
巴恩斯助理主任指出过
And as Assistant Director Barnes has pointed out,

179
00:07:50,400 --> 00:07:52,550
塞格尔探员熟悉这位
Agent Seger was familiar with --

180
00:07:53,000 --> 00:07:55,010
或者说过分熟悉这位
perhaps a bit too familiar with

181
00:07:55,030 --> 00:07:58,180
特殊人物  德尔加多先生
the particular subject, Mr. Delgado.

182
00:07:58,180 --> 00:08:00,520
塞格尔探员在调查中并未表现出
Agent Seger demonstrated no bias

183
00:08:00,520 --> 00:08:01,780
任何偏袒
during this investigation.

184
00:08:01,790 --> 00:08:05,470
事实上  她对德尔加多过去行为的了解
In fact, her awareness of Mr. Delgado's actions in the past

185
00:08:05,710 --> 00:08:08,550
只是帮我们更深入地研究在克丽·洛德尔
only helped to contextualize the evidence we found

186
00:08:08,550 --> 00:08:10,310
死亡现场发现的证据
at Keri Lodel's crime scene.

187
00:08:18,500 --> 00:08:20,620
全球策略开发不是来帮你们部门
Isn't GSD helping to update

188
00:08:20,620 --> 00:08:22,540
提升技术安全的吗
your department's technical security?

189
00:08:22,540 --> 00:08:25,660
是的  我们的一些工作人员认识受害者
It is. Some of my officers knew the victim

190
00:08:25,960 --> 00:08:27,690
还有德尔加多先生
as well as Mr. Delgado.

191
00:08:27,900 --> 00:08:29,920
他们有见过这两人公开在一起活动吗
Did they ever see the two of them out together socially?

192
00:08:29,920 --> 00:08:30,670
没有
No.

193
00:08:32,110 --> 00:08:34,750
但你的理论不是情侣争吵然后恶性发展吗
But your theory is a lover's quarrel gone horribly wrong.

194
00:08:34,750 --> 00:08:37,620
在保安截堵到德尔加多前
Before the security guard confronted Mr. Delgado,

195
00:08:37,620 --> 00:08:38,900
他还曾用无线电请求增援
he radioed for help.

196
00:08:38,900 --> 00:08:42,630
那时是凌晨两点  他听见屋里有尖叫声
It was 2 a.m., and he'd heard screams from this apartment.

197
00:08:42,630 --> 00:08:44,550
随后他就从这里追着嫌疑人
He then pursued the suspect from here

198
00:08:44,550 --> 00:08:47,180
然后将他逼到了走廊尽头的阳台
and confronted him on the balcony at the end of the hall,

199
00:08:47,510 --> 00:08:50,150
但德尔加多打倒了他
but Mr. Delgado got the better of him.

200
00:08:50,150 --> 00:08:51,930
这也不能说明这两人之间
That doesn't confirm an intimate relationship

201
00:08:51,930 --> 00:08:53,700
-有亲密关系  -我同意
- between the two of them. - No, I agree.

202
00:08:53,700 --> 00:08:57,430
这更可能像是一次性骚扰
It more strongly confirms a probable sexual assault

203
00:08:57,560 --> 00:08:59,330
随后升级成了谋杀
that escalated to murder.

204
00:08:59,460 --> 00:09:01,890
看看这狂怒的痕迹
Just all this rage.

205
00:09:02,280 --> 00:09:05,380
对  过度杀戮  因为一些个人原因
Yeah, it's overkill. Something personal.

206
00:09:08,160 --> 00:09:09,090
你发现什么了吗  梅
What do you got, Mae?

207
00:09:09,270 --> 00:09:12,460
我发现克丽的毒检结果非常奇怪
What I got is something weird in Keri's tox panel.

208
00:09:12,460 --> 00:09:14,590
她体内有镇静剂
So she has Lorazepam in her system

209
00:09:14,590 --> 00:09:16,700
但没有任何医生给她开过这种药
even though she does not have a prescription for it,

210
00:09:16,700 --> 00:09:18,490
并且药量非常之高
and the amount of the drug is so high,

211
00:09:18,490 --> 00:09:20,060
她像是被迫注射了镇定剂
it's like she's been sedated.

212
00:09:20,060 --> 00:09:23,290
此外  克丽身上没有任何防卫伤痕
And on top of that, Keri has no defensive wounds on her.

213
00:09:23,290 --> 00:09:24,950
所以你认为克丽被下药了
So you think keri was drugged,

214
00:09:24,950 --> 00:09:26,200
然后被刺死
and then she was stabbed to death.

215
00:09:26,200 --> 00:09:28,120
从我的角度看是这样的
I mean, that's what it's looking like to me.

216
00:09:28,120 --> 00:09:30,720
那第二个受害者  阿伦·萨布里呢
What about the second victim, Aron Sabri?

217
00:09:30,730 --> 00:09:32,770
死因是钝力损伤
Well, the COD is blunt force trauma,

218
00:09:32,770 --> 00:09:35,050
与被抛下阳台的说法一致
which is consistent with being tossed off a balcony,

219
00:09:35,050 --> 00:09:36,490
但遗憾的是
but unfortunately,

220
00:09:36,490 --> 00:09:38,120
死后损伤让我很难确认
the post-mortem injuries are making it

221
00:09:38,120 --> 00:09:40,390
哪些伤痕是因为受害者
really difficult for me to confirm the extent

222
00:09:40,390 --> 00:09:42,230
与嫌疑人搏斗留下的
of the struggle with the suspect,

223
00:09:42,380 --> 00:09:46,840
并且我还不清楚他的手上为什么会有擦伤
and I'm also really puzzled by the abrasions on his hands.

224
00:09:44,430 --> 00:09:47,180
尸检报告  阿伦·萨布里

225
00:09:46,840 --> 00:09:48,990
这就是我了解到的
But, I mean, it is what it is.

226
00:09:48,990 --> 00:09:50,270
谢谢  梅
Okay, thanks, Mae.

227
00:09:50,320 --> 00:09:52,970
杰克  这里没有什么能确认或否认
Jack, there is nothing here to confirm or deny

228
00:09:52,970 --> 00:09:54,860
这两人之间存在亲密关系
an intimate relationship between these two.

229
00:09:54,860 --> 00:09:56,430
也无法证明他们之间
And there's certainly nothing to tell why

230
00:09:56,430 --> 00:09:58,090
到底有过怎样的关系
whatever relationship they did have

231
00:09:58,090 --> 00:09:59,980
能造成这样凄惨的变故
took such a tragic turn.

232
00:10:00,110 --> 00:10:02,320
也许他的房间能给我们更多信息
Maybe his room will tell us more.

233
00:10:02,520 --> 00:10:04,690
可能吧  但我认为需要对克丽·洛德尔
Maybe, but I really think we need to conduct

234
00:10:04,690 --> 00:10:06,860
进行更深入的受害者分析
a deeper victimology of Keri Lodel.

235
00:10:06,880 --> 00:10:08,160
你看看她的纪念物
If you look at her mementos,

236
00:10:08,160 --> 00:10:10,930
她显然在不同的人中都很受欢迎
she's obviously very popular with lots of different people,

237
00:10:10,930 --> 00:10:12,400
他们中的任何人都能对她
any one of whom could have developed

238
00:10:12,400 --> 00:10:14,160
发展出扭曲的渴慕之情
some twisted sense of an attachment

239
00:10:14,160 --> 00:10:16,130
从而激发出这场暴力案件
that would have motivated this violence.

240
00:10:16,210 --> 00:10:19,220
让蒙蒂跟进下
Okay. We'll have Monty follow up.

241
00:10:20,440 --> 00:10:22,740
这么说  你们调查的下一步行动
So to be clear, the next step in your investigation

242
00:10:22,740 --> 00:10:24,650
是根据塞格尔探员的建议来的
was based on Agent Seger's recommendation?

243
00:10:24,650 --> 00:10:28,810
不  进行受害者分析是我们侧写的一步
No. Conducting a victimology is part of our profile building.

244
00:10:28,810 --> 00:10:31,620
但根据你的描述  塞格尔探员说
But you just described how Agent Seger said

245
00:10:31,620 --> 00:10:34,200
深入的受害者分析能让德尔加多洗掉嫌疑
a deeper victimology would help you move off Delgado.

246
00:10:34,200 --> 00:10:35,970
我才没这么说  你一直都在
That's not what I said, and you keep trying

247
00:10:35,980 --> 00:10:37,290
扭曲我说过的话
to twist my words like that.

248
00:10:37,290 --> 00:10:38,330
我只想确认清楚
I'm only trying to clarify.

249
00:10:38,330 --> 00:10:39,910
你在有意整我们小组
You're trying to hang the IRT.

250
00:10:39,910 --> 00:10:41,300
你就是这么做的
That's what you're trying to do here.

251
00:10:41,300 --> 00:10:43,780
-可能我们该休息一下  -我认为不用
- Perhaps it's time we took a break. - I think we're fine.

252
00:10:43,780 --> 00:10:46,650
-我觉得需要休息了  -阿伦和克丽
- I think we're taking a break. - Aron Sabri and Keri Lodel

253
00:10:46,650 --> 00:10:49,210
不是这起案件仅有的受害人
are not the only victims of this case.

254
00:10:49,340 --> 00:10:51,800
一位平民嫌犯也死了
A civilian suspect lost his life

255
00:10:51,800 --> 00:10:54,650
就是因为国际反应小组的莽撞行为
because of the IRT's reckless actions.

256
00:10:55,140 --> 00:10:56,970
你认为我有意整国际反应小组
You think I want to hang the IRT?

257
00:10:57,750 --> 00:11:00,520
杰克·加勒特组长  我就跟你明说吧
Unit Chief Garrett, let me be crystal clear with you.

258
00:11:00,820 --> 00:11:02,120
等今天工作完成了
When we are all done here today,

259
00:11:02,120 --> 00:11:04,540
我会动用全部力量将国际反应小组
I will have everything I need to shatter the IRT

260
00:11:04,540 --> 00:11:06,020
彻底粉碎
into a thousand pieces

261
00:11:06,020 --> 00:11:08,150
并将灰烬四散入风
and scatter the remnants to the wind.

262
00:11:19,340 --> 00:11:22,930
其实可以  更好一点
Well, that could have gone... better.

263
00:11:23,860 --> 00:11:27,260
-进展挺顺利  -因为你并不认为
- It's going fine. - Mm, 'cause you don't think

264
00:11:27,270 --> 00:11:30,450
那样自揭底牌后  会很难证明
it's hard to prove bias when you lay your own cards

265
00:11:30,450 --> 00:11:32,160
存在偏见
out on the table like that?

266
00:11:32,560 --> 00:11:34,210
你应该轻声而动
You need to tread lightly.

267
00:11:34,240 --> 00:11:35,270
是那样吗
Is that so?

268
00:11:35,270 --> 00:11:37,900
是的  这不仅是讯问
Yes, it is. This isn't just an inquiry.

269
00:11:37,900 --> 00:11:40,180
还是政治棋局
This is a political game of chess.

270
00:11:40,640 --> 00:11:41,600
你喜欢下棋吗
You like chess?

271
00:11:42,010 --> 00:11:43,280
我喜欢拳击
I like boxing.

272
00:11:43,780 --> 00:11:47,470
看出来了  我就很喜欢下棋
I see that. Now I love chess myself.

273
00:11:47,520 --> 00:11:51,300
需要沉得住气  擅用策略
Requires patience and understanding strategy

274
00:11:51,300 --> 00:11:53,070
懂得人性的弱点
and of human weakness.

275
00:11:53,070 --> 00:11:55,670
再说总能驱王使后
Plus you always get to be king.

276
00:11:55,890 --> 00:11:57,410
我对你的打气鼓劲并非不感激
Not that I don't appreciate the pep talk,

277
00:11:57,410 --> 00:11:58,720
但我不想要
but I don't.

278
00:11:58,720 --> 00:12:01,550
冷静  我是想保护你
Settle down. I'm trying to protect you,

279
00:12:01,550 --> 00:12:04,560
而且如果你真的想实现公正
and if you really wanna see justice done,

280
00:12:04,560 --> 00:12:07,590
你要收集也只收集事实
you will gather the facts -- just the facts,

281
00:12:07,700 --> 00:12:10,260
剩下的就交给当权者
and let the powers that be do the rest.

282
00:12:29,030 --> 00:12:29,970
不用我提醒你
I shouldn't have to remind you

283
00:12:29,970 --> 00:12:32,160
房里没人被捕吧
that no one in this room is under arrest.

284
00:12:32,160 --> 00:12:33,170
所以如果不介意
So if you don't mind,

285
00:12:33,170 --> 00:12:35,360
我要活动下腿脚  倒杯咖啡
I'm gonna go stretch my legs and get some coffee.

286
00:12:38,530 --> 00:12:39,580
谁有想要的吗
Anybody want anything?

287
00:12:40,500 --> 00:12:41,920
太荒谬了
This is ridiculous.

288
00:12:42,650 --> 00:12:44,830
我想现在最好还是
Look, I think it's best if we avoid sharing

289
00:12:45,100 --> 00:12:46,070
不要交流
for the time being.

290
00:12:46,170 --> 00:12:47,510
他们在房间装了窃听器吗
You think they wired the room?

291
00:12:47,960 --> 00:12:49,450
为什么要装窃听器呢
Why would they wire the room?

292
00:12:50,470 --> 00:12:52,950
因为尽管我们并没有被捕
Because while we are not actually under arrest,

293
00:12:52,950 --> 00:12:55,260
但我们相互之间禁止讨论
we're prohibited from discussing anything that has to do

294
00:12:55,260 --> 00:12:56,820
任何本案相关的事
with the case with each other.

295
00:12:56,820 --> 00:12:58,760
难以置信  我们能有什么打算
Unbelievable. What do they think that we're gonna do,

296
00:12:58,760 --> 00:13:00,610
坐在这儿合伙编故事吗
sit in here and try to line our stories up?

297
00:13:00,610 --> 00:13:02,350
这正是他们的想法
That's exactly what they think,

298
00:13:02,350 --> 00:13:04,450
即使只是串供的表现
and even the mere appearance of collusion

299
00:13:04,450 --> 00:13:06,930
也可能导致停工  甚至是起诉
is cause for termination if not straight up prosecution.

300
00:13:14,730 --> 00:13:17,450
那么  凯伦和孩子们怎么样
So... how are Karen and the kids?

301
00:13:17,450 --> 00:13:19,660
得了吧  别说废话
Oh, come on, Walt. Cut the crap.

302
00:13:19,810 --> 00:13:22,700
抱歉  伙计  真是粗暴
I'm sorry, man. This is tough.

303
00:13:23,020 --> 00:13:25,050
但你要记住  有我支持你
But I want you to know I got your back.

304
00:13:25,060 --> 00:13:26,910
不需要你支持
I don't need you to have my back.

305
00:13:27,260 --> 00:13:29,360
杰克  你自己也听到那女人的话了
Jack, you heard the woman yourself.

306
00:13:29,360 --> 00:13:32,290
关键不在于谁对谁错
This is not about who is right or who is wrong.

307
00:13:32,510 --> 00:13:34,200
而是谁来担罪
This is about who's to blame.

308
00:13:34,210 --> 00:13:36,650
沃尔特  我们所有行动都是照规定来的
Walt, we did everything by the book.

309
00:13:36,650 --> 00:13:40,090
我知道  杰克  但有人死了
I know you did, Jack, but we got a body count.

310
00:13:40,090 --> 00:13:43,900
所以不管有没有照规定来  有人犯了错
So book or no book, somebody screwed the pooch.

311
00:13:43,900 --> 00:13:46,080
我只希望那个人不是你
I just don't want that somebody to be you.

312
00:13:48,000 --> 00:13:49,490
对我的讯问还没结束
You're not done with me yet.

313
00:13:49,740 --> 00:13:50,960
还没有
No, we're not.

314
00:13:51,070 --> 00:13:54,180
但你和巴恩斯需要中场休息
But you and Barnes needed a time-out,

315
00:13:54,180 --> 00:13:56,380
所以  失陪
so...excuse me.

316
00:14:02,930 --> 00:14:05,950
塞格尔探员  三年前你曾请假
Agent Seger, three years ago, you took a leave of absence.

317
00:14:06,800 --> 00:14:08,750
-没错  -为什么
- Yes, I did. - Why?

318
00:14:10,350 --> 00:14:12,250
-为什么  -没错  那是个问题
- Why? - Yes, that's the question.

319
00:14:13,310 --> 00:14:14,590
我恐怕不明白你的意思
I'm not sure that I understand.

320
00:14:14,590 --> 00:14:17,520
你面前就是我的个人档案
You have my personal file sitting right in front of you.

321
00:14:17,520 --> 00:14:19,860
你十分清楚我告假的原因
You know exactly why I took the time off.

322
00:14:20,740 --> 00:14:22,080
没错  我确实知道
Yes, I do know why.

323
00:14:22,870 --> 00:14:26,320
真可惜  我想自己这些审讯员的花招
Unfortunately, I suspect some of my tricks as an interrogator

324
00:14:26,320 --> 00:14:29,940
在你这种法医心理学专家面前
are going to be transparent to an expert in forensic psychology

325
00:14:29,940 --> 00:14:31,510
根本玩不起来  是吧
such as yourself, am I right?

326
00:14:31,510 --> 00:14:33,400
请你一定要包容
I'd only ask your indulgence.

327
00:14:34,130 --> 00:14:36,110
或者你也可以选择不回答该问题
Or you can choose to not answer the question,

328
00:14:36,180 --> 00:14:38,370
但那可能透露出你的心智状况
but that might suggest something about your state of mind,

329
00:14:38,380 --> 00:14:39,160
你说呢
don't you think?

330
00:14:40,280 --> 00:14:43,540
你想玩游戏  我奉陪
You want to play games? I can play your game.

331
00:14:44,660 --> 00:14:45,860
三年前
Three years ago,

332
00:14:46,260 --> 00:14:49,820
我丈夫  特别督察探员布拉德·塞格尔
my husband, SSA Brad Seger --

333
00:14:49,900 --> 00:14:52,480
在执行公务时被害
he was killed in the line of duty,

334
00:14:53,520 --> 00:14:56,970
我因为丧夫而告假
and I took a leave of absence for bereavement.

335
00:14:59,740 --> 00:15:02,110
节哀顺变
I'm very sorry for your loss.

336
00:15:03,310 --> 00:15:04,170
谢谢
Thank you.

337
00:15:05,720 --> 00:15:08,110
因丧夫休假期间  你去往世界各地
During your bereavement leave, you traveled extensively,

338
00:15:08,110 --> 00:15:10,860
但我想集中于三年前
but I'd like to focus on the time you spent in Myanmar

339
00:15:10,860 --> 00:15:12,760
你在缅甸那段
three years ago, during which time

340
00:15:12,760 --> 00:15:17,320
当时你和爱德华·德尔加多十分熟络
you became...quite familiar with Edward Delgado,

341
00:15:17,320 --> 00:15:18,780
该男子后来也成为
the man who would later become

342
00:15:18,780 --> 00:15:20,620
卡利叶调查中的重点
the focus of the investigation in Qalea

343
00:15:20,620 --> 00:15:22,810
而他和你的复杂关系
and the man whose complicated connection to you

344
00:15:22,810 --> 00:15:24,990
-使贵团队产生偏见  -这么说不对
- would prejudice your team. - That is not true.

345
00:15:25,160 --> 00:15:27,490
尽管我个人了解德尔加多
Regardless of my personal knowledge of Delgado,

346
00:15:27,500 --> 00:15:30,370
但我们团队仍不含偏见将此人视为逃犯
my team, without prejudice, pursued this man as a fugitive

347
00:15:30,380 --> 00:15:31,160
进行追捕
from the law.

348
00:15:31,160 --> 00:15:33,910
而且蒙哥马利探员还联系了他的妻子
In fact, it was Agent Montgomery who reached out to his wife

349
00:15:33,910 --> 00:15:36,660
来多加了解他可能的逃亡去向
to get a better understanding of where he might seek refuge.

350
00:15:41,250 --> 00:15:44,740
蒙哥马利探员  过去二十四小时
Agent Montgomery, I haven't been able to get ahold

351
00:15:44,740 --> 00:15:46,640
我都联系不上我丈夫
of my husband in 24 hours.

352
00:15:46,640 --> 00:15:49,970
-德尔加多夫人  -请叫我阿米莉娅
- Mrs. Delgado -- - Please call me Amelia.

353
00:15:50,370 --> 00:15:52,150
阿米莉娅  请坐
Amelia, please.

354
00:15:56,640 --> 00:15:59,030
全球战略开发的居住区发了生意外事件
There was an incident at the GSD housing compound.

355
00:15:59,030 --> 00:16:00,290
有两人被害
Two people were killed.

356
00:16:00,290 --> 00:16:03,110
一位是你丈夫的女同事克丽·洛德尔
One was a woman who worked with your husband named Keri Lodel.

357
00:16:03,110 --> 00:16:06,440
另一位是叫阿伦·萨布里的保安
The other was a security guard named Aron Sabri.

358
00:16:08,760 --> 00:16:10,470
你丈夫也失踪了
Your husband is also missing.

359
00:16:10,900 --> 00:16:11,670
失踪
Missing?

360
00:16:13,000 --> 00:16:14,260
什么意思  失踪
What do you mean, missing?

361
00:16:14,470 --> 00:16:15,640
阿米莉娅  你最近一次
Amelia, when was the last time

362
00:16:15,640 --> 00:16:17,090
和丈夫联系是什么时候
you communicated with your husband?

363
00:16:17,090 --> 00:16:19,520
他昨天早上给我发了电子邮件
He E-mailed me yesterday morning.

364
00:16:19,590 --> 00:16:20,550
说了什么
What did he say?

365
00:16:20,550 --> 00:16:22,550
没什么  只是几张照片
Nothing. He just sent me photos.

366
00:16:22,550 --> 00:16:23,520
能给我看看吗
May I see them?

367
00:16:34,100 --> 00:16:35,920
他在国外的时候
How often did the two of you communicate

368
00:16:35,920 --> 00:16:37,480
你们俩多久联系一次
while he was overseas?

369
00:16:38,180 --> 00:16:40,180
每周一次  主要通过邮件
Once a week, mainly by e-mail.

370
00:16:40,640 --> 00:16:44,260
一定很难熬  对你们俩来说
Must have been tough... for both of you.

371
00:16:45,510 --> 00:16:47,830
我为什么感觉你真正想问的是
Why do I get the feeling that what you really wanna ask me

372
00:16:47,830 --> 00:16:50,390
我有没有觉得丈夫跟克丽有染
is if I think my husband was sleeping with Keri.

373
00:16:52,510 --> 00:16:53,350
有这个可能吗
Is it possible?

374
00:16:53,350 --> 00:16:55,450
不  没可能
No, it isn't.

375
00:16:56,140 --> 00:16:58,790
他发照片给我以便我认识他的朋友
He sent me those photos so that I could see his friends,

376
00:16:58,790 --> 00:16:59,590
仅此而已
that's all.

377
00:17:00,940 --> 00:17:01,640
好吧
Okay.

378
00:17:02,920 --> 00:17:05,610
那你丈夫最近有承受不同寻常的压力吗
Well, was your husband under any unusual stress lately?

379
00:17:06,120 --> 00:17:08,040
没  据我所知没有
No, not that I know of.

380
00:17:08,570 --> 00:17:11,320
他是个好人  他跟所有人都相处融洽
He's a good man. He gets along with everyone.

381
00:17:12,550 --> 00:17:16,380
我发誓  他绝对不会伤害任何人
I swear, he'd never hurt anyone.

382
00:17:17,420 --> 00:17:18,770
德尔加多的妻子给了我权限
Delgado's wife gave me access

383
00:17:18,770 --> 00:17:20,000
登入她丈夫的社交媒体
to all of her husband's social media,

384
00:17:20,000 --> 00:17:22,000
我正在检查当中  但老实说
and I'm going through it now, but I gotta be honest,

385
00:17:22,000 --> 00:17:24,090
阿米莉娅似乎非常了解她的丈夫
Amelia seemed to know her husband really well.

386
00:17:24,090 --> 00:17:26,000
所以如果他跟克丽没有婚外情
So if he wasn't having an affair with Keri,

387
00:17:26,000 --> 00:17:27,690
那他的杀人动机是什么呢
then what would be his motive to kill her?

388
00:17:27,740 --> 00:17:29,360
要是德尔加多没有杀害克丽
Well, if Delgado didn't kill Keri,

389
00:17:29,360 --> 00:17:30,640
那他为什么袭击保安
then why does he attack the guard?

390
00:17:30,640 --> 00:17:31,740
他为什么逃跑
And why does he run?

391
00:17:31,740 --> 00:17:33,980
这带来了一个更加迫切的问题
Which brings us to our more pressing question --

392
00:17:33,980 --> 00:17:36,260
爱德华·德尔加多到底在哪里
where is Edward Delgado?

393
00:17:36,420 --> 00:17:39,420
听着  不管犯罪与否  他并非惯犯
Listen, guilty or not, he's not some hardened criminal.

394
00:17:39,420 --> 00:17:41,000
他人生地不熟
He is a stranger in a strange land,

395
00:17:41,010 --> 00:17:42,640
就像梅之前说的
and it's like Mae said before.

396
00:17:42,640 --> 00:17:44,940
如果他能够逃出钢圈
If he did manage to sneak out of the Steel Ring,

397
00:17:44,940 --> 00:17:46,940
是因为他知道在另一边
it's because he knows someone on the other side

398
00:17:46,940 --> 00:17:48,170
也许有人能保护他
who might protect him.

399
00:17:48,860 --> 00:17:50,430
我好像有发现
I may have found something.

400
00:17:50,430 --> 00:17:52,320
德尔加多似乎跟
Looks like Delgado got pretty close

401
00:17:52,320 --> 00:17:54,370
他第一位翻译的家人很亲近
to the family of his first interpreter.

402
00:17:54,410 --> 00:17:56,590
年轻人名叫奥马尔·塔汗
Young man's name is Omar Tahan.

403
00:17:55,330 --> 00:17:57,400
全球策略开发  奥马尔·塔汗  翻译

404
00:17:56,670 --> 00:17:58,090
抱歉  塞格尔探员
I apologize, Agent Seger.

405
00:17:58,090 --> 00:17:59,660
那个年轻人叫什么名字
What was the young man's name again?

406
00:17:59,660 --> 00:18:00,490
奥马尔·塔汗
Omar Tahan.

407
00:18:00,840 --> 00:18:03,250
他给德尔加多当了两周翻译
He was Delgado's translator for two weeks

408
00:18:03,250 --> 00:18:04,280
直到把职责交给了
until those duties were transferred to

409
00:18:04,280 --> 00:18:06,080
可吉基国家警察的一名警官
an officer from the KNP.

410
00:18:06,080 --> 00:18:08,000
为什么移交工作呢
And why were those duties transferred?

411
00:18:08,000 --> 00:18:09,320
德尔加多的工作使他
Delgado's work exposed him

412
00:18:09,320 --> 00:18:11,800
接触到可吉基国家警察的保密通讯
to confidential KNP communications,

413
00:18:11,800 --> 00:18:15,480
而塔汗先生没有得到权限
and Mr. Tahan would have not been permitted access.

414
00:18:15,650 --> 00:18:17,780
你们确认了塔汗先生的身份后
Once you identified Mr. Tahan,

415
00:18:17,780 --> 00:18:19,670
你和你的团队接着做了什么
what did you or your team do next?

416
00:18:19,670 --> 00:18:21,540
我们前往塔汗的家
We drove out to the Tahan house.

417
00:18:21,540 --> 00:18:24,900
距离钢圈西北方一千六百米的地方
It was located 1 mile northwest of the Steel Ring,

418
00:18:24,900 --> 00:18:27,540
我们发现德尔加多先生就躲在了那里
and that's where we discovered Mr. Delgado hiding out.

419
00:18:27,720 --> 00:18:29,190
他有反抗吗
Did he offer any resistance?

420
00:18:29,190 --> 00:18:32,440
不  他没有  他毫无抵抗地接受拘留
No, he did not. He came into custody without incident.

421
00:18:32,440 --> 00:18:34,670
塞格尔探员  是谁决定
Agent Seger, whose decision was it

422
00:18:34,670 --> 00:18:36,260
把爱德华·德尔加多转移
to transport Edward Delgado

423
00:18:36,260 --> 00:18:37,700
回国际反应小组的飞机
back to the IRT jet

424
00:18:37,700 --> 00:18:40,990
而非直接把他带给可吉基国家警察拘留呢
rather than transfer him immediately into KNP custody?

425
00:18:40,990 --> 00:18:43,190
那是加勒特组长的决定
That was Unit Chief Garrett's decision.

426
00:18:43,190 --> 00:18:46,720
你记得自己质疑过那个决定吗
And do you recall if you perhaps challenged that decision?

427
00:18:46,870 --> 00:18:48,980
-不  -你不记得  还是...
- No. - No, you don't recall, or...

428
00:18:48,980 --> 00:18:51,780
-不  我没有质疑  -你支持吗
- No, I did not challenge it. - Did you encourage it?

429
00:18:52,100 --> 00:18:53,700
听着  当时德尔加多是
Look, at this point, Delgado was a suspect

430
00:18:53,700 --> 00:18:55,330
国际反应小组和可吉基国家警察
in a joint task force investigation

431
00:18:55,330 --> 00:18:57,490
联合调查中的疑犯
between the IRT and the KNP.

432
00:18:57,490 --> 00:18:59,630
加勒特组长有权
It was well within Unit Chief Garrett's purview

433
00:18:59,630 --> 00:19:01,920
把疑犯带到飞机中审讯
to bring a suspect onto the jet for questioning.

434
00:19:01,920 --> 00:19:05,230
-谁审讯他的  -是我
- And who questioned him? - I did.

435
00:19:18,590 --> 00:19:20,690
你得告诉我  爱德
You gotta talk to me, Ed.

436
00:19:22,250 --> 00:19:24,480
你得告诉我在公寓里
You have to tell me what happened

437
00:19:24,700 --> 00:19:26,590
跟保安发生了什么事
in the apartment with the guard.

438
00:19:27,840 --> 00:19:29,020
你为什么逃走
Why did you run?

439
00:19:31,630 --> 00:19:33,200
你跟她有发生关系吗
Were you sleeping with her?

440
00:19:35,310 --> 00:19:36,480
你觉得呢
What do you think?

441
00:19:37,550 --> 00:19:40,780
老实说  我觉得你绝对不会背叛
Honestly, I don't think you'd ever betray

442
00:19:40,780 --> 00:19:42,170
你孩子的母亲
the mother of your child.

443
00:19:43,980 --> 00:19:46,290
我只是想回家
I just...wanna go home,

444
00:19:46,590 --> 00:19:49,570
我对天发誓  不是我做的
and I swear to God I didn't do this.

445
00:19:49,790 --> 00:19:52,510
我知道  所以让我帮你吧
I know, so let me help you.

446
00:19:52,510 --> 00:19:54,720
但你不懂  你帮不了的
But you don't understand. You can't.

447
00:19:57,950 --> 00:19:59,650
这太疯狂了
This is insane.

448
00:20:01,120 --> 00:20:03,020
你在这里  走进我的生活
You being here, dropping into my life,

449
00:20:03,020 --> 00:20:04,540
就像你以前那样
just like you did before.

450
00:20:06,570 --> 00:20:07,790
为了"拯救"我
To "Save" Me.

451
00:20:14,090 --> 00:20:18,030
不  我认为我们拯救了彼此
No, I think we saved each other.

452
00:20:19,920 --> 00:20:20,650
有吗
Did we?

453
00:20:22,300 --> 00:20:25,630
我依然清楚记得  你告诉我
You know, I still remember exactly where we were

454
00:20:25,630 --> 00:20:27,220
我们在一起是个错误的时候
when you told me we were together

455
00:20:27,220 --> 00:20:29,040
我们的感情到了哪一步
for all the wrong reasons.

456
00:20:30,740 --> 00:20:32,350
但不可思议的是
But the crazy thing is,

457
00:20:32,590 --> 00:20:37,230
要是你没有离开我  我就不会回家
if you don't leave me, then I don't go home.

458
00:20:37,810 --> 00:20:39,720
我就不会结婚  而且
I don't get married, and...

459
00:20:40,370 --> 00:20:43,190
在我生命里就不会有宝贝女儿  朱莉娅
I don't get my baby girl, Julia, in my life.

460
00:20:43,190 --> 00:20:47,280
对  我现在就不会在这里帮你
Yeah, and I don't get to be here with you right now to help you.

461
00:20:47,780 --> 00:20:49,580
你得相信我  爱德
You have to trust me, Ed.

462
00:20:50,090 --> 00:20:51,140
事实上
Truth is,

463
00:20:52,010 --> 00:20:55,730
世界上我只相信
there is only one person in the whole world

464
00:20:55,730 --> 00:20:57,180
一个人  克拉拉
that I trust, Clara.

465
00:20:58,560 --> 00:21:01,400
克拉拉  杰克刚和里法伊队长通完电话
Clara, Jack just got off the phone with Captain Rifai.

466
00:21:01,740 --> 00:21:03,880
他要求我们把他转送给可吉基国家警察拘留
He's asking us to transfer him to KNP custody.

467
00:21:03,880 --> 00:21:05,560
可吉基国家警察  不  慢着
KNP? No, hold on a second.

468
00:21:05,560 --> 00:21:08,440
我是被联调局逮捕的美国公民
I'm an American citizen arrested by the FBI.

469
00:21:08,440 --> 00:21:09,860
你们为什么不能拘留我
Why can't you guys hold on to me?

470
00:21:09,860 --> 00:21:12,020
一切都会没事的  爱德
Okay, everything is gonna be okay, Ed.

471
00:21:12,020 --> 00:21:14,290
我的团队和我会一路陪着你
My team and I will be with you every step of the way.

472
00:21:14,300 --> 00:21:15,890
这是联合调查
It's a joint investigation.

473
00:21:15,890 --> 00:21:17,260
其实  把他带到这里
Actually, it was easier bringing him here

474
00:21:17,270 --> 00:21:19,130
比把他带回钢圈更方便
than it will be getting him back to the Steel Ring,

475
00:21:19,130 --> 00:21:21,170
不然我就得和里法伊队长
so I'll need to coordinate security protocols

476
00:21:21,170 --> 00:21:22,220
协调安全协议
for Captain Rifai.

477
00:21:22,220 --> 00:21:23,890
好的  我帮他做准备
Okay, I'll get him ready.

478
00:21:26,020 --> 00:21:27,760
安全协议
Security protocols?

479
00:21:27,950 --> 00:21:29,920
这种加密通讯方式
Such as encrypting communications

480
00:21:29,920 --> 00:21:31,900
在可吉基国家警察和国际反应小组
between the KNP and the IRT

481
00:21:31,980 --> 00:21:34,570
转交犯人之前  期间和之后使用
before, during, and after prisoner transfers.

482
00:21:34,570 --> 00:21:36,200
-我说得对吗  -对
- Is that correct? - Yes.

483
00:21:36,610 --> 00:21:39,490
抱歉  特别督查探员西蒙斯
Excuse me, SSA Simmons.

484
00:21:39,490 --> 00:21:41,490
我们能倒回去吗
Could we rewind a moment here?

485
00:21:41,770 --> 00:21:44,100
你接到里法伊队长的电话
You get the call from Captain Rifai.

486
00:21:44,250 --> 00:21:45,910
他让你把人交给他
He asks you to give him the guy.

487
00:21:46,250 --> 00:21:49,470
你能告诉我接下来本该发生什么吗
Could you walk me through what should have happened next?

488
00:21:49,730 --> 00:21:52,240
原计划是国际反应小组将犯人
The plan was for the IRT to convoy the prisoner

489
00:21:52,320 --> 00:21:55,050
押送回钢圈内的可吉基国家警察总部
back to KNP headquarters inside the Steel Ring.

490
00:21:55,210 --> 00:21:56,830
我们本来要走由里法伊长官
We were to travel by way of secured route,

491
00:21:56,830 --> 00:21:58,440
安排的安全线路
mapped by Captain Rifai.

492
00:21:58,440 --> 00:22:00,070
行动的首要目标
The primary concern for the operation

493
00:22:00,070 --> 00:22:01,730
是避开机场
was to avoid the main road

494
00:22:01,730 --> 00:22:03,780
与钢圈之间的主干道
between the airport and the Steel Ring.

495
00:22:03,910 --> 00:22:06,000
嗯  因为他们把那条路叫什么来着
Right, because what do they call that road --

496
00:22:06,000 --> 00:22:07,450
"诅咒之路"
"Damnation Alley"?

497
00:22:07,450 --> 00:22:08,150
西蒙斯探员
Agent Simmons,

498
00:22:08,150 --> 00:22:09,690
我们知道之后本该发生什么
we know what should have happened.

499
00:22:09,690 --> 00:22:12,220
-告诉我们实际是什么情况  -我们被
- Tell us what did happen. - We were ambushed

500
00:22:13,380 --> 00:22:15,830
忠于信念兄弟会的战士伏击了
by fighters loyal to the Brotherhood of Faith.

501
00:22:15,900 --> 00:22:17,170
你知道你们怎么成为攻击目标的吗
And do you know how you were targeted?

502
00:22:17,170 --> 00:22:18,180
怎么
How?

503
00:22:19,310 --> 00:22:21,900
不  这是随机的攻击
No. It was a random attack.

504
00:22:21,900 --> 00:22:22,750
随机的
Random?

505
00:22:23,730 --> 00:22:25,560
并不是随机的
It wasn't random.

506
00:22:25,560 --> 00:22:27,210
你们被发现是因为
You were found because you got caught

507
00:22:27,210 --> 00:22:29,610
你用公开线路进行通讯时暴露了
talking on open lines of communication.

508
00:22:29,610 --> 00:22:33,520
不可能  我亲自加密了线路
That's impossible. I personally secured those lines.

509
00:22:37,940 --> 00:22:39,590
那你告诉我  先生
Well, you tell me, sir.

510
00:22:39,800 --> 00:22:42,990
你是失职  还是叛徒
Are you incompetent, or are you a traitor?

511
00:22:43,510 --> 00:22:47,570
因为电子记录显示并没有加密
'Cause the digital evidence says no encryption.

512
00:22:52,610 --> 00:22:53,620
这些日志肯定不是真的
These logs can't be right.

513
00:22:53,620 --> 00:22:55,850
这些日志来自可吉基国家警察的服务器
Those logs are from the KNP server.

514
00:22:57,420 --> 00:22:59,760
伏击过程中发生了什么
What happened during the ambush?

515
00:22:59,760 --> 00:23:01,480
我们采取了躲避策略
We engaged in evasive maneuvers.

516
00:23:01,480 --> 00:23:03,770
有一刻  我们被迫离开道路
At one point, we were forced off the road,

517
00:23:04,200 --> 00:23:05,890
紧接着发生了交火
and a gun battle ensued.

518
00:23:06,580 --> 00:23:08,240
犯人在交火时中枪
The prisoner was hit by gunfire.

519
00:23:08,240 --> 00:23:10,330
你害德尔加多中枪了
You got Delgado shot.

520
00:23:10,880 --> 00:23:12,660
就在那时我们作出决定
It was at that point the decision was made

521
00:23:12,660 --> 00:23:13,960
原路返回飞机
to double back to the jet.

522
00:23:13,960 --> 00:23:16,480
-谁做的决定  -加勒特组长
- Who made that decision? - Unit Chief Garrett.

523
00:23:17,160 --> 00:23:19,340
那是我们救德尔加多唯一的机会
It was the only chance we had to save Delgado's life.

524
00:23:19,340 --> 00:23:21,290
那是你们组长的医疗建议
Was that your unit chief's medical opinion

525
00:23:21,290 --> 00:23:24,550
还是他的外勤法医  梅·贾维斯探员的建议
or that of his field medical examiner, Agent Mae Jarvis?

526
00:23:24,550 --> 00:23:25,730
我不知道
You know, I don't know.

527
00:23:25,740 --> 00:23:27,640
我当时忙着带大家脱离险境
I was too busy getting us the hell out of there.

528
00:23:27,690 --> 00:23:29,770
告诉我们回飞机后发生了什么
Tell us what happened once you got back to the jet.

529
00:23:30,180 --> 00:23:32,070
德尔加多胸部中枪
Delgado had been shot in the chest.

530
00:23:33,000 --> 00:23:34,440
-这里  -我把他从车里拉出来
- Here, here. - I got him out of the SUV,

531
00:23:34,440 --> 00:23:36,520
我正准备帮忙将他搬进会议室
and I was gonna help carry him up to the conference room,

532
00:23:36,940 --> 00:23:38,730
就在那时他们试图登机
and that's when they tried to board the plane.

533
00:23:39,650 --> 00:23:41,920
"他们"就是兄弟会的人
"They" being those Brotherhood boys.

534
00:23:41,920 --> 00:23:44,560
没错  克拉拉和梅以及其他机组成员
Yes. Clara and Mae and the rest of our flight crew

535
00:23:44,560 --> 00:23:46,030
将德尔加多带离交火区
got Delgado out of the line of fire.

536
00:23:46,040 --> 00:23:47,180
好了  把他放在这里
All right, bring him right in here.

537
00:23:47,720 --> 00:23:48,620
好的
Okay.

538
00:23:49,660 --> 00:23:51,750
克拉拉  把他的防弹背心脱下来
Clara, can you get his vest off?

539
00:23:51,750 --> 00:23:52,520
好的
Okay.

540
00:23:53,430 --> 00:23:54,920
当时一片混乱
I mean, there was a lot of chaos.

541
00:23:59,760 --> 00:24:01,510
杰克和我抵挡住了他们的攻击
Jack and I were able to hold them back

542
00:24:01,510 --> 00:24:03,510
克拉拉和梅抢救德尔加多
while Clara and Mae tended to Delgado.

543
00:24:03,510 --> 00:24:05,150
我们得给他供氧
We should get an oxygen line started.

544
00:24:06,670 --> 00:24:07,530
再紧点
Tighter.

545
00:24:08,620 --> 00:24:10,480
其他人都没受伤吗
And nobody else got injured?

546
00:24:10,490 --> 00:24:11,500
什么
I'm sorry?

547
00:24:11,750 --> 00:24:14,760
德尔加多是唯一一个中枪的人
Delgado was the only one who got shot.

548
00:24:14,850 --> 00:24:15,970
是的
Yes, he was.

549
00:24:16,870 --> 00:24:19,150
我们尽力关上了货舱门
We were able to get the cargo bay doors closed.

550
00:24:24,870 --> 00:24:28,400
但你们没能保住德尔加多的命  是不是
But you weren't able to save Delgado's life, were you?

551
00:24:28,400 --> 00:24:30,930
拜托  坚持住  拜托
Come on. Stay with me. Come on.

552
00:24:32,320 --> 00:24:33,220
梅
Mae.

553
00:24:33,440 --> 00:24:34,590
坚持住  爱德华
Come on, Edward!

554
00:24:38,640 --> 00:24:40,930
告诉我该怎么做  该怎么做
Okay, tell me what to do. What do I do?

555
00:24:44,180 --> 00:24:45,050
梅
Mae?

556
00:24:45,610 --> 00:24:46,730
他死了
He's gone.

557
00:24:55,160 --> 00:24:56,250
抱歉
I'm sorry.

558
00:25:02,540 --> 00:25:04,200
他们好像在重新集结  杰克
Looks like they're regrouping, Jack.

559
00:25:04,290 --> 00:25:06,040
可能在呼叫增援
Probably calling in reinforcements.

560
00:25:06,040 --> 00:25:07,160
你不会认为
Well, you don't think they're gonna try

561
00:25:07,160 --> 00:25:07,930
他们想要登机吧
and board the plane, do you?

562
00:25:07,930 --> 00:25:09,460
我也不想发生那种事
I don't want to have to find out.

563
00:25:10,120 --> 00:25:12,560
里法伊长官  你保证的增援呢
Captain Rifai, where's our backup you promised?

564
00:25:12,600 --> 00:25:14,660
他们现在正在路上
They are en route to you now.

565
00:25:14,660 --> 00:25:16,820
特别督查探员贾维斯  加勒特组长
SSA Jarvis, when Unit Chief Garrett

566
00:25:16,820 --> 00:25:18,320
命令小组返回飞机的时候
ordered the unit back to the jet,

567
00:25:18,320 --> 00:25:20,620
你知道德尔加多先生的全部伤势状况吗
did you know the full extent of Mr. Delgado's injuries?

568
00:25:20,630 --> 00:25:22,990
我发现了一处枪伤
Um, I had identified an entry wound

569
00:25:22,990 --> 00:25:24,800
在他的右上侧胸部
to his upper right thoracic region,

570
00:25:24,810 --> 00:25:28,000
我推测他的肺部受损
and I suspected that his lung had collapsed.

571
00:25:28,250 --> 00:25:29,810
那你对命令提出质疑了吗
So did you challenge the order?

572
00:25:29,810 --> 00:25:33,080
-没有  -你面前的伤者胸部中枪
- No. - You had a man with a gaping chest wound,

573
00:25:33,080 --> 00:25:36,210
你却没有坚持改道去拥有战地医院的
and you didn't insist on being rerouted to U.S. Camp Granato,

574
00:25:36,250 --> 00:25:37,720
美军格拉纳托驻地吗
where they have a field hospital?

575
00:25:37,860 --> 00:25:39,860
不  我没有  因为
No, I didn't, because

576
00:25:40,040 --> 00:25:42,390
事实上  我知道飞机上的设备
I mean, truth is, I knew that what I had on the plane

577
00:25:42,390 --> 00:25:45,730
能够稳定他的情况  而其他选择
could stabilize him, and everything else

578
00:25:45,730 --> 00:25:47,360
都是未知且充满变数的
was just an unknown variable,

579
00:25:47,360 --> 00:25:49,900
而且这一切是我们被敌人攻击时发生的
and it was all happening while we were under enemy fire.

580
00:25:50,660 --> 00:25:52,130
我知道  当时情况很危急
I get it. It was tough out there.

581
00:25:52,130 --> 00:25:54,970
-是的  -也许这就能解释为什么
- Yeah, it was. - Maybe that speaks to why,

582
00:25:54,970 --> 00:25:58,010
从医学院毕业后  你没有做外科医生
after medical school, you became a medical examiner

583
00:25:58,010 --> 00:26:00,140
而是成为了一名法医
instead of continuing in trauma medicine.

584
00:26:01,160 --> 00:26:02,300
什么
Excuse me?

585
00:26:02,910 --> 00:26:05,650
你记得一位
Do you recall a young man

586
00:26:05,660 --> 00:26:08,380
叫迪伦·雅各布斯的年轻人吗
by the name of Dylan Jacobs?

587
00:26:09,680 --> 00:26:12,730
记得  我记得迪伦
Yeah. Yeah, I remember Dylan.

588
00:26:12,770 --> 00:26:16,450
他入院的那晚  你是圣柯莱特
You were a resident at St. Colette's Trauma Center

589
00:26:16,450 --> 00:26:17,500
外伤治疗中心的住院医生
the night he was brought in.

590
00:26:17,500 --> 00:26:19,080
你记得他发生了什么事吗
Do you recall what happened to him?

591
00:26:19,890 --> 00:26:21,430
记得  他死在了手术台上
Yeah, he died on the table.

592
00:26:22,250 --> 00:26:25,110
他的家人认为是你和贾斯汀·怀亚特医生
And his family felt that you and Dr. Justin Wyatt

593
00:26:25,110 --> 00:26:26,840
以及医院的疏忽大意造成他死亡
and the hospital were negligent.

594
00:26:26,840 --> 00:26:28,280
他们提起了诉讼
They filed a lawsuit.

595
00:26:28,570 --> 00:26:30,790
那起诉讼庭外和解了
Uh, that was settled out of court

596
00:26:31,450 --> 00:26:33,160
签订了保密协议
with a nondisclosure agreement.

597
00:26:33,170 --> 00:26:36,960
意思是你无法透露你是否觉得
So are you saying you can't disclose whether or not

598
00:26:36,960 --> 00:26:39,430
自己应该对雅各布斯的死负责吗
you feel responsible for Mr. Jacobs' death?

599
00:26:47,900 --> 00:26:50,820
杰克  我很抱歉
Jack, I am so sorry.

600
00:26:50,990 --> 00:26:52,380
我本该把一切都告诉你的
I-I should have told you everything.

601
00:26:52,380 --> 00:26:54,050
没事的  克拉拉
No, it's all right, Clara.

602
00:26:54,050 --> 00:26:55,780
你把该告诉的都告诉我了
You told me everything you needed to.

603
00:26:58,460 --> 00:26:59,510
两位  听着
Hey, guys, listen.

604
00:26:59,510 --> 00:27:01,200
我知道我们不该交谈
I-I know we're not supposed to talk,

605
00:27:01,750 --> 00:27:03,560
但事情有点不对劲
but there is something else going on here.

606
00:27:03,630 --> 00:27:06,380
巴恩斯和阿特伍德基本上把伏击的事
Barnes and Atwood basically blamed me

607
00:27:06,480 --> 00:27:07,840
都怪在我头上
for the entire ambush.

608
00:27:08,060 --> 00:27:10,920
他们说我没有加密通讯线路
They said that I didn't encrypt the lines of communications,

609
00:27:10,990 --> 00:27:12,320
他们还提供了证据
and what they offered as proof

610
00:27:12,320 --> 00:27:15,080
来自可吉基国家警察指挥所的电子日志
were the digital log books from the KNP command post.

611
00:27:15,410 --> 00:27:17,100
相信我  那些日志肯定被篡改了
I'm telling you, those logs were doctored.

612
00:27:17,650 --> 00:27:18,370
但按理来说
But, presumably,

613
00:27:18,370 --> 00:27:20,010
只有可吉基国家警察内部的人
only somebody who works for the KNP

614
00:27:20,010 --> 00:27:21,420
-才能做到  -没错
- could have done that. - Right.

615
00:27:21,760 --> 00:27:23,880
克拉拉  我觉得你一开始就是对的
Clara, I think you were right from the start.

616
00:27:23,990 --> 00:27:26,920
德尔加多从来都不符合克丽凶手的侧写
Delgado never fit the profile of Keri's killer.

617
00:27:28,250 --> 00:27:30,710
问题是  他为什么要跑
Question is, why did he run?

618
00:27:31,050 --> 00:27:32,940
也许他不相信当地警方
Maybe he didn't trust the local cops.

619
00:27:33,090 --> 00:27:37,470
也许吧  德尔加多的工作重点是提高
Maybe. Delgado's job focused primarily on improving

620
00:27:37,470 --> 00:27:39,520
可吉基国家警察的网络安全
cybersecurity for the KNP,

621
00:27:39,520 --> 00:27:41,330
所以如果他无意中发现了一些
so what if he came across something

622
00:27:41,330 --> 00:27:42,780
不该发现的东西呢
that he shouldn't have?

623
00:27:43,000 --> 00:27:45,420
一个秘密  一个如此危险的秘密
A secret, something so compromising

624
00:27:45,420 --> 00:27:47,250
以至于可吉基国家警察内部的人
that someone inside the KNP would be

625
00:27:47,250 --> 00:27:49,300
不惜将谋杀案嫁祸给他
willing to frame him for murder.

626
00:27:49,960 --> 00:27:51,750
好吧  还有一件事
Okay, but consider this.

627
00:27:51,750 --> 00:27:54,240
你知道那个保安  阿伦·萨布里吗
You know that security guard, Aron Sabri?

628
00:27:54,240 --> 00:27:57,070
阿伦·萨布里
安保团队

629
00:27:54,280 --> 00:27:56,290
在全球策略开发做保安只是他的副业
he was only moonlighting at the GSD compound.

630
00:27:56,290 --> 00:27:59,350
他的主要工作是可吉基国家警察的巡警
His primary job was patrol officer for the KNP.

631
00:27:59,440 --> 00:28:00,710
记得他手上的擦伤吗
Remember the abrasions on his hands?

632
00:28:00,930 --> 00:28:02,580
那些梅无法解释的擦伤
the ones that Mae really couldn't explain?

633
00:28:01,090 --> 00:28:02,600
尸检报告

634
00:28:03,260 --> 00:28:05,460
如果擦伤不是因为和德尔加多扭打呢
What if they hadn't come from a struggle with Delgado?

635
00:28:05,460 --> 00:28:07,430
如果那是在一遍又一遍
What if they were a result of stabbing Keri

636
00:28:07,440 --> 00:28:08,580
刺伤克丽时产生的呢
over and over again?

637
00:28:08,580 --> 00:28:11,810
所以你认为最初的计划是保安杀死克丽
So you think the original plan was the guard kills Keri,

638
00:28:11,810 --> 00:28:15,090
然后在德尔加多企图逃跑时杀了他
then he kills Delgado as he tries to escape.

639
00:28:15,370 --> 00:28:17,240
不过德尔加多没让他得逞
Only Delgado got the better of him.

640
00:28:17,660 --> 00:28:19,930
很可惜  虽然听起来很合理
Unfortunately, as good as this sounds,

641
00:28:19,940 --> 00:28:21,430
这仍然只是推测
it's pure speculation.

642
00:28:21,430 --> 00:28:23,320
是啊  鉴于我们现在的状态
Yeah, and given our current status,

643
00:28:23,320 --> 00:28:24,660
我们需要确凿的证据证明
we need some hard evidence to prove

644
00:28:24,660 --> 00:28:27,670
可吉基国家警察内部的人是幕后黑手
that someone from the KNP was behind all of this.

645
00:28:27,670 --> 00:28:29,860
我不确定在被剥夺一切的情况下
And I'm not sure we're gonna be able to prove anything

646
00:28:29,870 --> 00:28:32,030
我们还能证明什么
when we've been stripped of everything.

647
00:28:33,200 --> 00:28:34,480
也许并不是一切
Maybe not everything.

648
00:28:35,290 --> 00:28:36,880
如果德尔加多的事我们没猜错
Look, if we're right about Delgado,

649
00:28:36,880 --> 00:28:38,840
他确实发现了可吉基国家警察的肮脏秘密
and he did discover the KNP's dirty little secret,

650
00:28:38,840 --> 00:28:40,800
如果他还是我印象中的那个人
if he's the man that I remember,

651
00:28:40,940 --> 00:28:42,970
他会将证据藏起来
he would have hedged his bets on the evidence.

652
00:28:43,000 --> 00:28:44,000
什么意思
What do you mean?

653
00:28:44,200 --> 00:28:46,200
他有可能将发现的证据
I think that he would have sent his proof

654
00:28:46,210 --> 00:28:48,080
发给了这世上他唯一信任的人
to the only person in the world that he trusts.

655
00:29:02,490 --> 00:29:04,770
-你还好吗  -还好
- You okay? - Sure.

656
00:29:11,080 --> 00:29:12,920
他们只是和我们玩心理游戏
Look, you know they're just playing these mind games

657
00:29:12,920 --> 00:29:14,640
想要摧毁我们的意志
in order to try to break you.

658
00:29:15,490 --> 00:29:17,090
是啊  那他们真的很厉害
Yeah, well, they're ballers at it,

659
00:29:17,090 --> 00:29:19,810
因为我已经无力招架了
'cause I feel pretty broken.

660
00:29:20,970 --> 00:29:22,250
一切都会没事的
It'll be all right.

661
00:29:24,060 --> 00:29:25,460
我不在乎别人怎么说
I mean, I don't care what anybody says.

662
00:29:25,460 --> 00:29:29,660
但当别人的性命在你手上
When you have someone's life in your hands,

663
00:29:30,070 --> 00:29:32,960
你就能感受到责任的重量
you feel the weight of that responsibility.

664
00:29:34,230 --> 00:29:37,180
当然  你表面上能装作很坚强
And, yeah, you can -- you can put on a brave face,

665
00:29:38,060 --> 00:29:41,950
但我觉得我永远都学不会如何
but I don't think you ever really learn how to...

666
00:29:42,350 --> 00:29:44,110
能将自己的情感控制自如
turn your emotions on and off.

667
00:29:45,810 --> 00:29:47,520
如果那个人最终没活下来
And if you lose that person,

668
00:29:49,920 --> 00:29:51,950
你永远都会质疑自己
you never stop second-guessing yourself.

669
00:30:00,310 --> 00:30:02,920
蒙哥马利探员  请你回想一下
Agent Montgomery, I'd like to direct your attention

670
00:30:02,920 --> 00:30:07,590
德尔加多先生死后发生的事情
to the events that took place after Mr. Delgado's death.

671
00:30:07,880 --> 00:30:11,500
你记不记得接到了前方的求救电话
You recall receiving a distress call from Betsy Ross?

672
00:30:11,740 --> 00:30:12,760
记得
Yes, I do.

673
00:30:12,760 --> 00:30:14,180
老大  怎么了
Hey, boss, what's going on?

674
00:30:14,180 --> 00:30:15,130
我们有麻烦了
We're in trouble.

675
00:30:15,140 --> 00:30:16,890
我们被兄弟会伏击了
We got ambushed by the Brotherhood.

676
00:30:16,890 --> 00:30:18,850
一人遇难  看起来
We sustained a casualty. It looks like

677
00:30:18,850 --> 00:30:20,170
他们想要登机
they're gonna try to board the plane.

678
00:30:20,170 --> 00:30:21,690
好的  我立刻联系可吉基国家警察
Okay, I'll call the KNP right now.

679
00:30:21,690 --> 00:30:23,240
我试过了  他们鞭长莫及
I tried that. They're too far away.

680
00:30:23,240 --> 00:30:24,670
你现在得立刻联系
I need you to call in the cavalry

681
00:30:24,670 --> 00:30:26,600
美军格拉纳托驻地的装甲部队
from U.S. Camp Granato right now.

682
00:30:28,570 --> 00:30:32,020
你为什么无视加勒特组长的直接命令
Why did you ignore Unit Chief Garrett's direct order?

683
00:30:32,020 --> 00:30:34,340
我没有无视  我评估了局势
I didn't ignore it. I assessed the situation.

684
00:30:34,340 --> 00:30:36,490
查看了地图  他们也太远了
I looked at the map. They were too far away.

685
00:30:36,650 --> 00:30:39,200
也许你可以告诉我们
Perhaps you would be willing to tell us

686
00:30:39,230 --> 00:30:42,100
你是什么时候知道
when you first became aware of the existence

687
00:30:42,100 --> 00:30:45,090
Z-TAC夜鹰S-2的存在的
of the Z-TAC Nighthawk S-2.

688
00:30:45,640 --> 00:30:49,090
我不能告诉你一个不存在的项目  对吧
I can't tell you about a program that doesn't exist, now, can I?

689
00:30:49,150 --> 00:30:50,580
你肯定觉得自己聪明极了
You must think you're pretty smart.

690
00:30:50,580 --> 00:30:53,270
我认为夜鹰S-2是美国情报界
I think the Nighthawk S-2 is the worst kept secret

691
00:30:53,270 --> 00:30:54,810
人尽皆知的秘密
in the U.S. Intelligence community.

692
00:30:55,090 --> 00:30:57,690
是杰克·加勒特命令你黑进
Did Jack Garrett direct you to compromise

693
00:30:57,690 --> 00:30:58,930
夜鹰系统的吗
the Nighthawk system?

694
00:30:58,980 --> 00:31:00,090
不是
No, he did not.

695
00:31:00,480 --> 00:31:02,560
-现在什么情况  -他们在撞门
- What's going on? - They're knocking at the door.

696
00:31:02,560 --> 00:31:03,930
杰克  依我看来
Okay, Jack, the way I see it,

697
00:31:03,930 --> 00:31:06,040
你唯一的选择就是立刻起飞
your only option is to take off right now.

698
00:31:06,040 --> 00:31:07,580
这我可能无法做到
I'm not sure how that's gonna happen.

699
00:31:07,580 --> 00:31:09,540
-他们把我们包围了  -不会很久
- They've got us surrounded. - Not for long.

700
00:31:15,110 --> 00:31:16,450
蒙哥马利探员
Agent Montgomery,

701
00:31:15,230 --> 00:31:16,890
全球无人机控制系统

702
00:31:16,450 --> 00:31:18,950
你知道盗用并损毁
do you know what it means to misappropriate

703
00:31:18,950 --> 00:31:24,450
一架1.64亿美元的无人机是什么后果吗
and destroy a $164 million unmanned aerial vehicle?

704
00:31:24,450 --> 00:31:26,190
无意冒犯  1.64亿美元
With all due respect, $164 million

705
00:31:26,190 --> 00:31:28,260
是包括项目的研发费用
suggests that you're including the R&D on the project.

706
00:31:28,260 --> 00:31:31,980
一架无人机的价格是374万美元
The price tag for a single drone is $3.74 million.

707
00:31:31,980 --> 00:31:34,130
你觉得这是开玩笑吗
Do you honestly think this is a joke?

708
00:31:34,130 --> 00:31:36,890
是的  你想知道我有没有偷无人机
Yes. Do you wanna know if I stole the drone?

709
00:31:37,020 --> 00:31:40,160
我偷了  我偷无人机是因为有武装分子
Yes, I stole the drone because there were men with guns

710
00:31:40,160 --> 00:31:42,610
追杀我的队友  所以我黑进了
going after my team, so I hacked

711
00:31:42,610 --> 00:31:44,540
附近正在飞行的最近的监控无人机
the nearest surveillance drone in flight

712
00:31:44,540 --> 00:31:48,870
用其扫射了飞机场  好几遍
and I strafed the airfield with it...several times.

713
00:31:51,250 --> 00:31:52,240
还好那些信念兄弟会的人
Thank God those boys over at the Brotherhood of Faith

714
00:31:52,240 --> 00:31:53,590
非常不擅长射飞靶
are really bad at skeet shooting,

715
00:31:53,590 --> 00:31:54,770
因为这样会
because that gave them time

716
00:31:54,770 --> 00:31:56,860
把他们的注意力从飞机那里吸引过来
to draw away from the plane

717
00:31:56,860 --> 00:32:01,120
而我则是制造了一个374万美金的灯光秀
and for me to create a $3.74 million light show,

718
00:32:02,260 --> 00:32:03,960
来让我的队友驾驶飞机起飞
which allowed my team to get off the tarmac

719
00:32:03,960 --> 00:32:05,110
逃出生天
and get out of harm's way.

720
00:32:05,120 --> 00:32:06,960
你知道敌方的伤亡吗
Were you aware of enemy casualties?

721
00:32:06,960 --> 00:32:10,290
-没有伤亡  -当时你并不知道
- There were none. - You didn't know that at the time.

722
00:32:10,330 --> 00:32:11,890
我明白这事到头来
I understand at the end of all this,

723
00:32:11,890 --> 00:32:13,120
必须要有人来担责
there has to be a blame game,

724
00:32:13,230 --> 00:32:14,900
但是事实是
but the truth of the matter is

725
00:32:15,310 --> 00:32:19,190
只有极少数的一部分被选中的人
there's only a chosen few who will ever be qualified

726
00:32:19,230 --> 00:32:20,490
是有资格在前线工作的
to work in the field.

727
00:32:21,370 --> 00:32:22,970
这是无可辩驳的
There's no other way to say it.

728
00:32:23,460 --> 00:32:26,260
他们有更好的直觉  判断
Their instincts, their judgment,

729
00:32:27,730 --> 00:32:29,740
勇气
their courage --

730
00:32:29,800 --> 00:32:33,710
因为这是必需的
it's better... because it has to be.

731
00:32:34,040 --> 00:32:35,800
因为在情急之下
Because in the heat of the moment,

732
00:32:36,100 --> 00:32:37,980
他们要做出艰难的选择
they make the hard choices.

733
00:32:38,770 --> 00:32:42,830
你觉得你是那少数被选中人之一吗
And do you think that you are one of those chosen few?

734
00:32:45,260 --> 00:32:46,380
我不是觉得
I don't think it.

735
00:32:48,000 --> 00:32:50,170
我是清楚知道  所以我做了那些事
I know, so I did what I did.

736
00:32:50,170 --> 00:32:51,220
下次我还会这么做
I'd do it again,

737
00:32:51,220 --> 00:32:53,860
现在我准备接受我的行为所带来的后果
and I'm now prepared to accept the consequences of my actions.

738
00:32:54,390 --> 00:32:57,810
很好  蒙哥马利探员  因为
Good, because, Agent Montgomery...

739
00:32:58,130 --> 00:32:59,430
你由于故意盗窃
...you're under arrest,

740
00:32:59,640 --> 00:33:01,940
玩忽职守
for willful theft, malfeasance,

741
00:33:01,940 --> 00:33:03,980
和破坏政府财物而被捕了
and destruction of government property.

742
00:33:04,100 --> 00:33:05,250
交出你的警徽
I need your badge.

743
00:33:21,120 --> 00:33:22,200
你好  阿米莉亚
Hello, Amelia.

744
00:33:24,010 --> 00:33:26,280
谢谢你来见我
Thank you for, for meeting me.

745
00:33:29,720 --> 00:33:31,820
我和爱德之间无所不谈  克拉拉
Ed and I had no secrets, Clara.

746
00:33:32,890 --> 00:33:34,810
今天我来是因为我知道
I came here today because I know

747
00:33:34,810 --> 00:33:36,460
你是他的生命中很重要的一个人
that you were important to his life,

748
00:33:36,460 --> 00:33:39,010
而我真的需要有人能为他
and I really need someone to get justice for him

749
00:33:39,020 --> 00:33:40,110
还有克丽伸张正义
and for Keri.

750
00:33:41,150 --> 00:33:42,890
这正是我想要做的
That's exactly what I intend to do.

751
00:33:44,590 --> 00:33:47,520
我可以看看他给你发的照片吗
May I see the photos that he e-mailed you?

752
00:33:56,630 --> 00:33:57,890
爱德有这种习惯吗
Did Ed have a habit

753
00:33:57,890 --> 00:34:00,340
会经常给你发他偷拍的快照
of sending you candid snapshots like these?

754
00:34:00,350 --> 00:34:02,740
没有  不过还好他发了
No. But I'm glad he did.

755
00:34:06,240 --> 00:34:08,490
你能把这些也给我发一份吗
Do you mind e-mailing me copies of these?

756
00:34:09,380 --> 00:34:10,330
为什么
Why?

757
00:34:10,790 --> 00:34:12,400
阿米莉亚  我和我的队友认为
Amelia, my team and I believe

758
00:34:12,400 --> 00:34:14,280
爱德是因为发现了一个秘密
that Ed was framed for Keri's murder

759
00:34:14,280 --> 00:34:16,300
而被陷害谋杀了克丽
because of a secret that he discovered,

760
00:34:16,300 --> 00:34:18,930
而我认为这些照片能告诉我
and I think these photos will tell me

761
00:34:18,930 --> 00:34:20,350
秘密到底是什么
exactly what that secret is.

762
00:34:24,810 --> 00:34:26,450
这怎么回事
Hey, what's going on here?

763
00:34:27,590 --> 00:34:29,760
-没事的  杰克  -不  有事
- It's all right, Jack. - No, it's not all right.

764
00:34:29,760 --> 00:34:33,090
别插手  朋友  随它去吧
Let it go, my friend. Let it play out.

765
00:34:33,090 --> 00:34:34,330
都是按规章走的流程
It's all part of the process.

766
00:34:34,330 --> 00:34:35,260
罪名是什么
What's the charge?

767
00:34:35,260 --> 00:34:36,420
这重要吗  杰克
What does it matter, Jack?

768
00:34:36,420 --> 00:34:38,170
这已经是最糟的情况了
This is the worst of it.

769
00:34:38,170 --> 00:34:39,270
沃尔特  听我说
Walter, listen to me.

770
00:34:39,270 --> 00:34:40,780
德尔加多是被陷害的
Delgado was set up.

771
00:34:40,860 --> 00:34:42,610
我或许有办法拿到证据
I may have a way to get the evidence.

772
00:34:42,610 --> 00:34:44,770
西格尔和西蒙斯探员正在...
Agent Seger and Simmons are working on --

773
00:34:45,700 --> 00:34:47,740
西格尔和西蒙斯不能参与任何工作
Seger and Simmons can't be working on anything.

774
00:34:47,750 --> 00:34:48,870
你知道的
You know that.

775
00:34:49,480 --> 00:34:50,570
该死的  杰克
Oh, damn it, Jack.

776
00:34:50,570 --> 00:34:52,670
你又把你自己陷于不利
You have just opened yourself right back up.

777
00:34:52,670 --> 00:34:54,520
你这可是违抗命令
We're talking insubordination.

778
00:34:54,520 --> 00:34:56,590
是是  更不用说
Yeah, yeah, not to mention

779
00:34:56,590 --> 00:34:59,010
有失联邦政府官员身份的行为了
conduct unbecoming a federal officer.

780
00:34:59,600 --> 00:35:01,050
把他带回楼上
Take him back upstairs.

781
00:35:17,690 --> 00:35:20,060
请坐
Please, take a seat.

782
00:35:22,100 --> 00:35:23,200
加勒特组长
Unit Chief Garrett,

783
00:35:23,200 --> 00:35:25,150
在今天的会谈过程中
during the course of the proceedings today,

784
00:35:25,150 --> 00:35:27,050
你是否与你的国际反应小组成员
did you or did you not communicate

785
00:35:27,050 --> 00:35:28,810
有过交流
with members of your IRT unit?

786
00:35:28,810 --> 00:35:30,720
-是的  -你是什么时候
- I did. - Where and when did

787
00:35:30,720 --> 00:35:33,030
在什么地方与他们进行的违规交流
these prohibited communications take place?

788
00:35:33,030 --> 00:35:34,210
和我小组里的其他成员一样
Like the rest of my team,

789
00:35:34,210 --> 00:35:37,040
我要对德尔加多先生的死负责
I feel responsible for Mr. Delgado's death.

790
00:35:37,050 --> 00:35:38,090
我问的不是这个
That wasn't the question.

791
00:35:38,090 --> 00:35:39,240
这是我们在这里的原因
It's the reason we're here.

792
00:35:39,240 --> 00:35:40,030
加勒特组长
Unit Chief Garrett.

793
00:35:40,030 --> 00:35:42,470
造成德尔加多先生死亡的真正原因
The real reason that Mr. Delgado is dead

794
00:35:43,300 --> 00:35:44,470
是背叛
is betrayal.

795
00:35:45,730 --> 00:35:46,940
你在说什么
What are you talking about?

796
00:35:47,050 --> 00:35:48,870
他是个好人  尽忠职守
He was a good man doing good work,

797
00:35:48,870 --> 00:35:51,280
只不过碰巧发现了一个秘密
who, by chance, uncovered a secret.

798
00:35:51,500 --> 00:35:53,630
他发现了可吉基国家警察
He found out about a deal between the KNP

799
00:35:53,630 --> 00:35:55,550
和信念兄弟会首脑之间的交易
and the leader of the Brotherhood of Faith,

800
00:35:55,560 --> 00:35:56,850
也就是拉尚·努里
Rashan Noori.

801
00:35:57,760 --> 00:35:59,830
他们出卖恐怖分子的名单
In exchange for ratting out terrorist cells,

802
00:35:59,830 --> 00:36:01,690
作为交换  可吉基国家警察向努里保证
Noori was guaranteed that the KNP

803
00:36:01,690 --> 00:36:02,620
会对他们的犯罪行为
would turn a blind eye

804
00:36:02,620 --> 00:36:04,460
睁一只眼闭一只眼
toward its own criminal activities

805
00:36:04,460 --> 00:36:07,930
这其中包括买卖可吉基儿童
which include the trafficking of Kurjik children.

806
00:36:08,060 --> 00:36:10,190
你怎么知道这些的
You know all this how?

807
00:36:10,190 --> 00:36:12,010
德尔加多遵循了规章制度
Delgado followed the protocol.

808
00:36:12,010 --> 00:36:14,280
他在卡利叶见了美国反贪调查员
He met with the U.S. Ombudsman in Qalea.

809
00:36:14,280 --> 00:36:17,230
提供了证据  不过为了回答你的问题
He offered evidence, but to answer your question,

810
00:36:17,230 --> 00:36:21,260
我知道这一切是由于德尔加多先生
I know about all this because Mr. Delgado

811
00:36:21,260 --> 00:36:23,460
还违反了规章
also violated protocol.

812
00:36:23,700 --> 00:36:26,330
他还把一份证据副本用加密信息
He sent copies of the same evidence to his wife

813
00:36:26,870 --> 00:36:29,710
藏在照片里发给了他的妻子
in encrypted messages in photos.

814
00:36:30,950 --> 00:36:32,150
就是这一份
Like this one.

815
00:36:36,140 --> 00:36:39,130
你是说爱德华·德尔加多用了隐写术吗
Saying that Edward Delgado used steganography?

816
00:36:39,130 --> 00:36:43,000
对  他用一份电子档案作为另一份的伪装
Yes. He was able to camouflage one digital file within another,

817
00:36:43,000 --> 00:36:45,390
如果你继续翻后面那些图片
and if you continue to swipe past those images,

818
00:36:45,390 --> 00:36:47,720
你会找到行为分析部的技术分析员
you'll find the encryption that was provided to me

819
00:36:47,720 --> 00:36:51,050
佩内洛普·加西亚提供给我的加密信息
by BAU Technical Analyst, Penelope Garcia.

820
00:36:51,320 --> 00:36:52,550
让我看看
Let me see that.

821
00:36:54,680 --> 00:36:57,310
抛开这份证据不谈  你的行为...
Despite this evidence, your conduct --

822
00:36:57,310 --> 00:36:59,670
这份证据证明了国际行动小组
This evidence helps to prove that the IRT

823
00:36:59,670 --> 00:37:01,900
和德尔加多一样是被陷害的
was also set up, just like Delgado.

824
00:37:02,010 --> 00:37:02,990
被陷害
Set up?

825
00:37:02,990 --> 00:37:05,800
对  因为这份与魔鬼的协议
Yes, because the most compromising part

826
00:37:05,800 --> 00:37:07,500
最有损名誉的部分是
of this deal with the devil is that

827
00:37:07,500 --> 00:37:10,710
这一切都是在一位美国情报部门官员的
it was all illegally sanctioned

828
00:37:10,710 --> 00:37:12,220
非法批准下进行的
by a U.S. Intelligence officer.

829
00:37:12,410 --> 00:37:14,270
这就是必须要陷害德尔加多的原因
That's why Delgado had to be framed.

830
00:37:14,270 --> 00:37:16,500
这就是必须要伏击我的团队的原因
That's why my team had to be ambushed --

831
00:37:16,510 --> 00:37:19,060
为了保护这位代号为"象"的
to protect the identity of the officer,

832
00:37:20,230 --> 00:37:21,680
官员的身份
code-named "Bishop."

833
00:37:22,180 --> 00:37:24,920
我必须要告诉你如果你指控
I have an obligation to tell you that if you accuse

834
00:37:24,990 --> 00:37:26,850
一位情报部门官员
an Intelligence officer of a crime

835
00:37:26,850 --> 00:37:28,270
而没有足够证据的话...
without sufficient evidence...

836
00:37:28,270 --> 00:37:30,030
这才是关键所在  对吧
That's the real trick, isn't it?

837
00:37:30,460 --> 00:37:32,930
如果你生活在一个被谎言笼罩的世界
How do you get to the truth in a shadow world

838
00:37:32,930 --> 00:37:34,350
又何从找到真相
defended by lies?

839
00:37:35,690 --> 00:37:38,820
我想这就是档案派上用场的时候了
I like to think that's where profiling comes in handy.

840
00:37:39,240 --> 00:37:43,140
能找到行为背后的动机
The ability to decipher motive behind behavior,

841
00:37:43,360 --> 00:37:45,690
谎言背后的始作俑者
the liar behind the lie.

842
00:37:47,350 --> 00:37:48,880
我觉得你已经知道了
Something tells me you think

843
00:37:48,880 --> 00:37:50,260
这些问题的答案  杰克
you already know the answer to that, Jack.

844
00:37:50,260 --> 00:37:52,010
我的确是知道的  琳达
I think I do, Linda.

845
00:37:52,460 --> 00:37:55,470
首先要好好想想谁会从中获益
First, you have to ask yourself who benefits?

846
00:37:56,530 --> 00:37:59,110
利用像努里这样现成的资源
Who would be best served by taking advantage

847
00:37:59,110 --> 00:38:00,990
谁是最大的受益者
of an off-the-shelf resource like Noori?

848
00:38:00,990 --> 00:38:03,500
更重要的是  谁有这个胆量
But more importantly, who would have the nerve

849
00:38:03,500 --> 00:38:05,530
敢和魔鬼做交易
to make that deal with the devil?

850
00:38:07,590 --> 00:38:09,990
这个人肯定是心安理得地
It would have to be somebody who felt comfortable

851
00:38:09,990 --> 00:38:13,000
将必要采取的恶行合理化
rationalizing all those necessary evils

852
00:38:13,000 --> 00:38:15,940
来保护更大的利益
in order to protect the greater good.

853
00:38:16,340 --> 00:38:17,790
这个人一定是认为
It'd have to be somebody who believes that

854
00:38:17,790 --> 00:38:19,360
结果比过程更重要
the ends always justify the means.

855
00:38:19,360 --> 00:38:20,270
没错
Right.

856
00:38:21,480 --> 00:38:22,910
你明白我在说什么吧
You see what I'm saying?

857
00:38:23,900 --> 00:38:28,870
象  所以这个人
Bishop. So maybe even someone who enjoys

858
00:38:28,870 --> 00:38:30,060
可能也很喜欢国际象棋吧
the game of chess?

859
00:38:30,370 --> 00:38:33,260
因为在国际象棋中  象这个角色
Because in chess, the Bishop's personality

860
00:38:33,260 --> 00:38:36,020
往往被视为阴险  狡猾
is often considered sly, cunning...

861
00:38:37,860 --> 00:38:39,140
并且堕落
and corrupt.

862
00:38:39,520 --> 00:38:41,550
而你总能驱王使后
Plus you always get to be king.

863
00:38:43,690 --> 00:38:45,200
巴恩斯助理主任
Assistant Director Barnes,

864
00:38:45,200 --> 00:38:48,870
要是我是你  我接下来会谨言慎行的
I would consider your next move carefully.

865
00:38:49,020 --> 00:38:51,340
我就是这么打算的
Oh. I am.

866
00:38:52,260 --> 00:38:54,200
阿特伍德副主任  你被捕了
Deputy Director Atwood, you're under arrest.

867
00:38:54,210 --> 00:38:55,980
你有权保持沉默
You have the right to remain silent.

868
00:38:55,980 --> 00:38:57,750
你不是来真的吧
You can't be serious.

869
00:38:58,300 --> 00:38:59,980
杰克的那套心理侧写
Jack's psycho profile

870
00:38:59,980 --> 00:39:01,550
就是一派胡言  算不上证据
B.S. isn't evidence.

871
00:39:01,550 --> 00:39:03,330
但是加西亚探员在你的私人服务器上
But the e-mails that Agent Garcia

872
00:39:03,330 --> 00:39:06,110
发现的邮件是证据  沃尔特
found on your private server are, Walter.

873
00:39:07,560 --> 00:39:10,590
你根本不知道你做了什么
You have no idea what you've done.

874
00:39:10,590 --> 00:39:12,030
你这个混蛋
You son of a bitch.

875
00:39:12,840 --> 00:39:14,550
你害死了德尔加多
You had Delgado killed.

876
00:39:14,710 --> 00:39:16,280
你让我的团队处于险境
You put my team in the line of fire

877
00:39:16,280 --> 00:39:17,350
把我们当成牺牲品
like we were expendable.

878
00:39:17,350 --> 00:39:19,070
你们就是牺牲品
You are expendable!

879
00:39:19,600 --> 00:39:22,050
因为你们是士兵  杰克  我也是
Because you're soldiers, Jack, just like I am.

880
00:39:22,130 --> 00:39:24,540
士兵们会牺牲自己
And soldiers sacrifice themselves

881
00:39:24,540 --> 00:39:26,190
来保护其他人
so others won't have to.

882
00:39:26,450 --> 00:39:29,570
你以为我喜欢和努里这种混蛋同流合污吗
You think I like lying down with dogs like Noori?

883
00:39:29,800 --> 00:39:32,520
你说得对  这就是必须采取的恶行
You're damn right it's a necessary evil.

884
00:39:32,680 --> 00:39:33,280
知道为什么吗
You know why?

885
00:39:33,280 --> 00:39:36,010
因为我们正处在战争中  朋友们
Because we're at war, my friends.

886
00:39:36,060 --> 00:39:38,120
别搞错了  就是因为我们告诉大家
Make no mistake, just because we're telling people

887
00:39:38,120 --> 00:39:40,190
可以一如既往地安居乐业
to keep streaming and shopping,

888
00:39:40,470 --> 00:39:43,530
我们为了实现这些理想才进行肮脏的斗争
we're in a dog fight for everything we hold to be true.

889
00:39:43,980 --> 00:39:45,320
如果没有我这种人
And without men like me,

890
00:39:45,680 --> 00:39:48,680
没有我这种采取必要恶行的人
without men willing to do what is necessary,

891
00:39:48,780 --> 00:39:50,590
我们就会输
we will lose!

892
00:39:50,610 --> 00:39:52,600
少摆出这副自以为是的样子
Spare me the self-righteousness,

893
00:39:52,600 --> 00:39:55,730
你怎么好意思把自己
and don't you dare compare yourself

894
00:39:55,730 --> 00:39:57,430
和那些士兵们相提并论
to the men and women in uniform.

895
00:39:58,580 --> 00:39:59,680
你就是个小办事员
You're a clerk

896
00:40:00,390 --> 00:40:01,540
还是名罪犯
and a criminal.

897
00:40:02,300 --> 00:40:03,460
带他出去
Get him outta here.

898
00:40:20,280 --> 00:40:21,340
你怎么样
How you doing?

899
00:40:22,210 --> 00:40:24,140
好多了  毕竟现在没带着手铐了
Better, now that I got the handcuffs off.

900
00:40:24,140 --> 00:40:26,390
但到底是怎么回事
But...what's going on?

901
00:40:30,630 --> 00:40:32,310
鉴于我们目前的情况
Given our current state of affairs,

902
00:40:32,310 --> 00:40:34,440
我对这个结果没意见
I've agreed to this little tite-e-tite.

903
00:40:35,030 --> 00:40:36,040
谢谢
Thank you.

904
00:40:36,380 --> 00:40:37,720
显然  我没有隐瞒自己的想法
Obviously, I've made no secret

905
00:40:37,720 --> 00:40:39,970
我想削弱国际反应小组的作用
about my desire to diminish the IRT's role.

906
00:40:39,970 --> 00:40:41,590
你想摆脱我们
You'd like to get rid of us.

907
00:40:41,660 --> 00:40:42,840
我想要你们能负起责任
I'd like you to be accountable.

908
00:40:42,840 --> 00:40:45,510
我们是负责的  一直如此
We are. We always have been.

909
00:40:45,700 --> 00:40:47,510
那你叫我来干什么呢  杰克
Then why did you ask me here, Jack?

910
00:40:47,600 --> 00:40:50,420
不是来要求对蒙哥马利探员宽大处理的吗
If not to ask for leniency for Agent Montgomery?

911
00:40:50,550 --> 00:40:52,050
这正是我想说的
And this is what I'm talking about.

912
00:40:52,050 --> 00:40:54,970
尽管他意图是好的  结果也不坏
The fact remains that in spite of his good intentions

913
00:40:54,970 --> 00:40:57,260
但蒙哥马利探员
or the positive results, Agent Montgomery

914
00:40:57,260 --> 00:40:59,350
必须为他自己的行为负责
must be held accountable for his actions.

915
00:40:59,680 --> 00:41:01,090
就算我同意
And even if I were to recommend

916
00:41:01,150 --> 00:41:02,970
不提起刑事诉讼
not seeking criminal prosecution,

917
00:41:03,250 --> 00:41:06,110
但最起码局里必须要辞退他
at the very least, the Bureau must terminate his employment.

918
00:41:06,900 --> 00:41:07,960
她说得对  杰克
She's right, Jack.

919
00:41:08,270 --> 00:41:09,520
我不认同
No, I don't think so.

920
00:41:10,290 --> 00:41:12,310
因为蒙哥马利探员的行为
Because Agent Montgomery's actions

921
00:41:12,310 --> 00:41:14,900
和我团队中任何人所做的任何行为
or any actions taken by a member of my team

922
00:41:15,140 --> 00:41:16,190
都是基于我的命令
are done on my orders,

923
00:41:16,190 --> 00:41:18,580
无论是直接下达的还是暗示的
whether directly stated or implied.

924
00:41:18,580 --> 00:41:20,170
一切责任都应该由我承担
The buck stops with me, always,

925
00:41:20,170 --> 00:41:23,750
就算有人要被开除  那也该是我
so if anyone's gonna get fired, it's me.

926
00:41:24,790 --> 00:41:26,120
我认真的  琳达
I'm serious, Linda.

927
00:41:26,130 --> 00:41:28,470
我知道你是认真的  杰克  但你可能
I know you are, Jack, but I'm not sure

928
00:41:28,470 --> 00:41:30,640
还不清楚现在的情况
you appreciate the scope of the situation here.

929
00:41:30,770 --> 00:41:31,550
你刚刚扳倒了
You just took down

930
00:41:31,550 --> 00:41:33,320
国家情报局的副主任
the Deputy Director of National Intelligence.

931
00:41:33,320 --> 00:41:35,360
现在要我来停你的职吗
Now I'm gonna be the one to take your badge?

932
00:41:35,360 --> 00:41:37,970
没错啊  因为就该如此
Yes, because that's how it works.

933
00:41:37,970 --> 00:41:39,370
这就是责任
That's accountability.

934
00:41:44,520 --> 00:41:47,400
杰克·加勒特组长  我先跟你说清楚
Unit Chief Jack Garrett, let me be crystal clear.

935
00:41:47,860 --> 00:41:50,960
我会盯着你和你的小组
You and your unit are on notice.

936
00:41:50,960 --> 00:41:52,560
你可以把这当成是第一振
You may consider this your first strike,

937
00:41:52,560 --> 00:41:55,390
在这场博弈中  第二振你就会出局
and in this game, a second strike means you are out.

938
00:42:08,140 --> 00:42:09,090
你还好吗
You good?

939
00:42:09,380 --> 00:42:12,470
别提我了  他们都准备把你关起来了
Me? Forget about me. They were about to lock you up.

940
00:42:12,470 --> 00:42:14,500
嗯  但我知道你们会来救我的  对吧
Yeah, but I knew you guys would come break me out, right?

941
00:42:14,530 --> 00:42:16,010
也可能是和你关在一起
Or share a cell with you.

942
00:42:16,330 --> 00:42:17,850
我们是彼此的坚强后盾
We had each other's backs.

943
00:42:18,060 --> 00:42:22,160
的确  我们回家吧  休息一下
Yes, we did. Let's go home, get some rest.

944
00:42:23,450 --> 00:42:24,720
各位
Uh, guys?

945
00:42:28,960 --> 00:42:31,070
坏蛋们可从不休息
Well... no rest for the wicked.

946
00:42:34,420 --> 00:42:35,340
确实
No.

947
00:42:36,940 --> 00:42:38,600
看来我们又有工作了
'Cause we got a job to do.

948
00:42:39,460 --> 00:42:43,070
联邦调查局国际反应小组

