1
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:05,000
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

2
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:05,000
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

3
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:05,000
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

4
00:00:00,500 --> 00:00:05,000
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

5
00:00:00,500 --> 00:00:05,000
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35

6
00:00:00,500 --> 00:00:05,000
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

7
00:00:00,500 --> 00:00:05,000
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

8
00:00:06,220 --> 00:00:41,220
m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

9
00:00:05,720 --> 00:00:41,220
m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

10
00:00:01,640 --> 00:00:03,390
Over 68 million Americans

11
00:00:03,390 --> 00:00:05,880
leave the safety of our borders every year.

12
00:00:06,050 --> 00:00:07,610
If danger strikes,

13
00:00:07,840 --> 00:00:10,440
the FBI's International Response Team

14
00:00:10,440 --> 00:00:12,010
is called into action.

15
00:00:37,940 --> 00:00:38,960
We got you.

16
00:01:20,460 --> 00:01:22,180
Unit Chief Jack Garrett,

17
00:01:22,190 --> 00:01:24,200
you have the right to remain silent

18
00:01:24,200 --> 00:01:26,230
and refuse to answer questions today.

19
00:01:26,360 --> 00:01:28,250
If you give up that right, anything you say

20
00:01:28,250 --> 00:01:30,760
can and will be used against you in a court of law.

21
00:01:30,980 --> 00:01:32,610
You have the right to consult with an attorney

22
00:01:32,610 --> 00:01:34,730
before and during this questioning.

23
00:01:35,100 --> 00:01:36,660
If you cannot afford an attorney...

24
00:01:40,320 --> 00:01:41,230
I'm sorry.

25
00:01:42,900 --> 00:01:44,570
Unit Chief Garrett, do you understand these rights

26
00:01:44,570 --> 00:01:45,850
as I've explained them to you?

27
00:01:47,930 --> 00:01:48,760
Yes.

28
00:02:38,550 --> 00:02:40,800
Are you willing to sit down now and answer our questions?

29
00:02:42,330 --> 00:02:43,180
Yes.

30
00:02:47,200 --> 00:02:50,110
Jack, are you sure you don't want your lawyer?

31
00:02:50,360 --> 00:02:51,530
It could get rough.

32
00:02:52,620 --> 00:02:53,880
I don't need a lawyer.

33
00:02:54,220 --> 00:02:56,620
Let the record reflect that IRT Unit Chief Jack Garrett

34
00:02:56,620 --> 00:02:58,860
has waived his right to counsel at this time.

35
00:02:58,990 --> 00:03:01,500
Let us identify those also present for this session --

36
00:03:01,500 --> 00:03:03,510
Agents Brian Lynch and Jody Reynolds

37
00:03:03,510 --> 00:03:06,410
with the FBI's Office of Professional Responsibility.

38
00:03:06,680 --> 00:03:09,290
Janice Reichel, Deputy Counsel, District of Columbia,

39
00:03:09,290 --> 00:03:11,320
representing the Department of Justice.

40
00:03:11,340 --> 00:03:13,930
Walter Atwood, Deputy Director of National Intelligence,

41
00:03:13,930 --> 00:03:16,700
and I am Linda Barnes, Executive Assistant Director

42
00:03:16,700 --> 00:03:18,760
of the FBI's National Security Branch.

43
00:03:18,920 --> 00:03:21,240
Deputy Director Atwood and I have been authorized

44
00:03:21,240 --> 00:03:23,590
to conduct this joint inquiry for the FBI and DNI.

45
00:03:23,590 --> 00:03:24,990
Now, Unit Chief Garrett,

46
00:03:24,990 --> 00:03:26,280
can you walk us through the beginnings

47
00:03:26,290 --> 00:03:28,270
of Case Number 67-16-01

48
00:03:28,270 --> 00:03:30,270
in Qalea, Kurjikistan?

49
00:03:30,510 --> 00:03:33,020
We were refueling in Lisbon,

50
00:03:33,200 --> 00:03:36,250
when Agent Russell Montgomery gave notification

51
00:03:36,250 --> 00:03:39,600
about a request from the U.S. Ambassador

52
00:03:39,820 --> 00:03:42,250
and the Kurjikistan Foreign Minister.

53
00:03:42,380 --> 00:03:45,600
It was a double homicide involving a U.S. Citizen

54
00:03:45,600 --> 00:03:47,210
and a Kurjik national.

55
00:03:47,240 --> 00:03:48,550
Keri Lodel, 29.

56
00:03:48,550 --> 00:03:50,470
She's from Providence, Rhode Island,

57
00:03:50,480 --> 00:03:52,710
and she worked as a network engineer

58
00:03:52,720 --> 00:03:56,490
for a U.S. Contractor called Global Strategem Development.

59
00:03:56,490 --> 00:03:57,950
Also, Aron Sabri,

60
00:03:57,950 --> 00:03:59,800
32, from Qalea.

61
00:03:59,800 --> 00:04:01,820
He worked as a security guard for GSD.

62
00:04:01,830 --> 00:04:04,830
Now according to Captain Rifai of the Kurjik National Police,

63
00:04:04,830 --> 00:04:06,980
Keri was stabbed to death by by a co-worker

64
00:04:06,980 --> 00:04:09,110
who she was allegedly having an affair with.

65
00:04:09,190 --> 00:04:11,370
That man's name is Edward Delgado.

66
00:04:11,370 --> 00:04:12,920
Delgado is 46 years old,

67
00:04:12,920 --> 00:04:14,530
from Alexandria, Virginia.

68
00:04:14,540 --> 00:04:15,610
He's a systems analyst,

69
00:04:15,610 --> 00:04:17,480
and he's married with a 2-year-old daughter.

70
00:04:17,480 --> 00:04:18,980
Sabri, the local security guard,

71
00:04:18,980 --> 00:04:19,870
appears to have died

72
00:04:19,870 --> 00:04:21,340
during the struggle with Delgado

73
00:04:21,340 --> 00:04:23,740
as he fled the GSD housing compound.

74
00:04:23,800 --> 00:04:24,870
So it looks like all this took place

75
00:04:24,870 --> 00:04:26,520
inside of Qalea's Steel Ring.

76
00:04:27,080 --> 00:04:28,120
Steel Ring?

77
00:04:28,220 --> 00:04:30,800
It's a heavily fortified 4-square-mile area

78
00:04:30,800 --> 00:04:32,720
much like Baghdad's Green Zone.

79
00:04:33,050 --> 00:04:35,680
Jack, uh, I know Delgado.

80
00:04:35,710 --> 00:04:36,590
You know him?

81
00:04:36,740 --> 00:04:38,310
I-I mean, knew him.

82
00:04:38,310 --> 00:04:40,890
We used to work together for an NGO in Myanmar.

83
00:04:41,450 --> 00:04:42,410
When was this?

84
00:04:43,100 --> 00:04:45,400
Three years ago when I took my leave of absence.

85
00:04:45,400 --> 00:04:46,810
What do you remember about him?

86
00:04:46,810 --> 00:04:49,310
Honestly, this doesn't make any sense to me at all.

87
00:04:49,310 --> 00:04:49,980
The man that I knew --

88
00:04:49,980 --> 00:04:51,560
he could barely raise his voice in anger,

89
00:04:51,560 --> 00:04:52,890
much less escalate to murder.

90
00:04:52,890 --> 00:04:55,230
Not only that, he's a fugitive now.

91
00:04:55,750 --> 00:04:58,450
As someone whose job requires her to analyze

92
00:04:58,460 --> 00:05:01,300
and objectively profile the behaviors of criminal suspects,

93
00:05:01,300 --> 00:05:04,250
wasn't Agent Seger's judgment already compromised?

94
00:05:04,250 --> 00:05:05,500
No, not at all.

95
00:05:05,820 --> 00:05:06,920
Not at all?

96
00:05:07,640 --> 00:05:10,290
You don't believe Agent Seger's history with Mr. Delgado

97
00:05:10,300 --> 00:05:13,140
could have in any way impacted her ability to --

98
00:05:13,140 --> 00:05:15,490
No, I don't, just like I don't believe

99
00:05:15,500 --> 00:05:18,310
that Deputy Director Atwood's longtime friendship with me

100
00:05:18,310 --> 00:05:20,600
is going to impact his ability to be objective

101
00:05:20,600 --> 00:05:22,060
during this inquiry.

102
00:05:24,630 --> 00:05:26,310
Did Agent Seger disclose to you

103
00:05:26,310 --> 00:05:27,530
or to any other member of your team

104
00:05:27,530 --> 00:05:30,410
the full extent of her prior relationship with Mr. Delgado?

105
00:05:30,420 --> 00:05:33,730
Agent Seger disclosed that she previously worked with him

106
00:05:33,730 --> 00:05:35,470
in Myanmar three years ago.

107
00:05:35,470 --> 00:05:36,490
She didn't happen to mention

108
00:05:36,500 --> 00:05:38,660
her personal relationship with this man?

109
00:05:40,000 --> 00:05:44,670
No. She didn't mention it, but doesn't matter because --

110
00:05:44,670 --> 00:05:47,660
What matters is how well you know the members of your team.

111
00:05:47,740 --> 00:05:50,870
No doubt this line of questioning is important,

112
00:05:50,870 --> 00:05:52,410
but let me jump ahead.

113
00:05:52,420 --> 00:05:56,010
When you landed in country, run us through the protocol.

114
00:05:56,060 --> 00:05:58,870
When we landed in Qalea, we began coordinating

115
00:05:58,870 --> 00:06:01,340
with Captain Basir Rifai,

116
00:06:01,340 --> 00:06:03,580
head of the Kurjik National Police.

117
00:06:03,600 --> 00:06:04,350
Unfortunately,

118
00:06:04,350 --> 00:06:06,090
my men have made little progress in our hunt for the fugitive,

119
00:06:06,090 --> 00:06:08,310
Edward Delgado.

120
00:06:08,310 --> 00:06:11,340
We are beginning to believe he may have escaped the Steel Ring

121
00:06:11,340 --> 00:06:13,420
and may in fact be already dead.

122
00:06:14,060 --> 00:06:15,790
Because as a westerner on the run,

123
00:06:15,790 --> 00:06:17,270
he could've easily fallen into the hands

124
00:06:17,270 --> 00:06:19,250
of the militant group, the Brotherhood of Faith.

125
00:06:19,250 --> 00:06:22,260
Yes, one of many terror groups that plague my country.

126
00:06:22,260 --> 00:06:23,160
Only this one was led

127
00:06:23,160 --> 00:06:26,190
by one of your former army generals, Rashan Noori.

128
00:06:26,190 --> 00:06:28,730
Indeed. An even deeper wound for us.

129
00:06:28,730 --> 00:06:30,460
But Delgado's a pretty smart guy, right?

130
00:06:30,460 --> 00:06:32,230
So you think if he's really gonna roll the dice

131
00:06:32,230 --> 00:06:34,310
outside the Ring, he's only gonna do it

132
00:06:34,310 --> 00:06:35,980
if he knows exactly where he's gonna be able to hide

133
00:06:35,980 --> 00:06:36,680
for a little bit.

134
00:06:36,680 --> 00:06:39,950
You may be right, Agent Jarvis, but in my experience,

135
00:06:40,680 --> 00:06:44,240
the desperate man always makes the desperate choice.

136
00:06:45,200 --> 00:06:48,360
Well, right now Agent Seger and I should inspect the crime scene

137
00:06:48,360 --> 00:06:50,880
while Agent Simmons here evaluates our suspect's

138
00:06:50,880 --> 00:06:53,740
possible escape routes from the housing compound.

139
00:06:53,740 --> 00:06:54,700
Yes, of course.

140
00:06:54,700 --> 00:06:58,190
I'd also like the bodies of Keri Lodel and Aron Sabri

141
00:06:58,190 --> 00:07:00,030
brought back here so Agent Jarvis

142
00:07:00,030 --> 00:07:02,520
can conduct supplemental autopsies.

143
00:07:02,560 --> 00:07:04,400
I'll arrange for the transfer.

144
00:07:04,990 --> 00:07:07,400
Unit Chief, earlier you mentioned,

145
00:07:07,410 --> 00:07:10,160
if I'm not mistaken, that the Kurjik Foreign Minister

146
00:07:10,160 --> 00:07:12,370
was one of the folks who had asked for

147
00:07:12,370 --> 00:07:14,750
the IRT's help in this matter. Is that right?

148
00:07:14,760 --> 00:07:15,680
Yes, that's right.

149
00:07:15,680 --> 00:07:17,520
Did you or did you not

150
00:07:17,520 --> 00:07:20,870
acknowledge and respect the lead investigative role

151
00:07:20,870 --> 00:07:23,380
of the local authority, Captain Rifai?

152
00:07:23,990 --> 00:07:28,160
Deputy Director, the IRT's role, as always,

153
00:07:28,160 --> 00:07:30,900
was to advise and assist Captain Rifai and the KNP

154
00:07:30,900 --> 00:07:33,960
during the course of this double homicide investigation

155
00:07:33,960 --> 00:07:36,980
and the pursuit of the fugitive, Edward Delgado.

156
00:07:36,980 --> 00:07:40,190
Now much of that advice and assistance

157
00:07:40,200 --> 00:07:41,680
comes from your team's ability

158
00:07:41,680 --> 00:07:45,240
to build these behavioral profiles of criminal suspects.

159
00:07:45,240 --> 00:07:46,790
- Is that right? - Yes.

160
00:07:46,970 --> 00:07:50,400
And as Assistant Director Barnes has pointed out,

161
00:07:50,400 --> 00:07:52,550
Agent Seger was familiar with --

162
00:07:53,000 --> 00:07:55,010
perhaps a bit too familiar with

163
00:07:55,030 --> 00:07:58,180
the particular subject, Mr. Delgado.

164
00:07:58,180 --> 00:08:00,520
Agent Seger demonstrated no bias

165
00:08:00,520 --> 00:08:01,780
during this investigation.

166
00:08:01,790 --> 00:08:05,470
In fact, her awareness of Mr. Delgado's actions in the past

167
00:08:05,710 --> 00:08:08,550
only helped to contextualize the evidence we found

168
00:08:08,550 --> 00:08:10,310
at Keri Lodel's crime scene.

169
00:08:18,500 --> 00:08:20,620
Isn't GSD helping to update

170
00:08:20,620 --> 00:08:22,540
your department's technical security?

171
00:08:22,540 --> 00:08:25,660
It is. Some of my officers knew the victim

172
00:08:25,960 --> 00:08:27,690
as well as Mr. Delgado.

173
00:08:27,900 --> 00:08:29,920
Did they ever see the two of them out together socially?

174
00:08:29,920 --> 00:08:30,670
No.

175
00:08:32,110 --> 00:08:34,750
But your theory is a lover's quarrel gone horribly wrong.

176
00:08:34,750 --> 00:08:37,620
Before the security guard confronted Mr. Delgado,

177
00:08:37,620 --> 00:08:38,900
he radioed for help.

178
00:08:38,900 --> 00:08:42,630
It was 2 a.m., and he'd heard screams from this apartment.

179
00:08:42,630 --> 00:08:44,550
He then pursued the suspect from here

180
00:08:44,550 --> 00:08:47,180
and confronted him on the balcony at the end of the hall,

181
00:08:47,510 --> 00:08:50,150
but Mr. Delgado got the better of him.

182
00:08:50,150 --> 00:08:51,930
That doesn't confirm an intimate relationship

183
00:08:51,930 --> 00:08:53,700
- between the two of them. - No, I agree.

184
00:08:53,700 --> 00:08:57,430
It more strongly confirms a probable sexual assault

185
00:08:57,560 --> 00:08:59,330
that escalated to murder.

186
00:08:59,460 --> 00:09:01,890
Just all this rage.

187
00:09:02,280 --> 00:09:05,380
Yeah, it's overkill. Something personal.

188
00:09:08,160 --> 00:09:09,090
What do you got, Mae?

189
00:09:09,270 --> 00:09:12,460
What I got is something weird in Keri's tox panel.

190
00:09:12,460 --> 00:09:14,590
So she has Lorazepam in her system

191
00:09:14,590 --> 00:09:16,700
even though she does not have a prescription for it,

192
00:09:16,700 --> 00:09:18,490
and the amount of the drug is so high,

193
00:09:18,490 --> 00:09:20,060
it's like she's been sedated.

194
00:09:20,060 --> 00:09:23,290
And on top of that, Keri has no defensive wounds on her.

195
00:09:23,290 --> 00:09:24,950
So you think keri was drugged,

196
00:09:24,950 --> 00:09:26,200
and then she was stabbed to death.

197
00:09:26,200 --> 00:09:28,120
I mean, that's what it's looking like to me.

198
00:09:28,120 --> 00:09:30,720
What about the second victim, Aron Sabri?

199
00:09:30,730 --> 00:09:32,770
Well, the COD is blunt force trauma,

200
00:09:32,770 --> 00:09:35,050
which is consistent with being tossed off a balcony,

201
00:09:35,050 --> 00:09:36,490
but unfortunately,

202
00:09:36,490 --> 00:09:38,120
the post-mortem injuries are making it

203
00:09:38,120 --> 00:09:40,390
really difficult for me to confirm the extent

204
00:09:40,390 --> 00:09:42,230
of the struggle with the suspect,

205
00:09:42,380 --> 00:09:46,840
and I'm also really puzzled by the abrasions on his hands.

206
00:09:46,840 --> 00:09:48,990
But, I mean, it is what it is.

207
00:09:48,990 --> 00:09:50,270
Okay, thanks, Mae.

208
00:09:50,320 --> 00:09:52,970
Jack, there is nothing here to confirm or deny

209
00:09:52,970 --> 00:09:54,860
an intimate relationship between these two.

210
00:09:54,860 --> 00:09:56,430
And there's certainly nothing to tell why

211
00:09:56,430 --> 00:09:58,090
whatever relationship they did have

212
00:09:58,090 --> 00:09:59,980
took such a tragic turn.

213
00:10:00,110 --> 00:10:02,320
Maybe his room will tell us more.

214
00:10:02,520 --> 00:10:04,690
Maybe, but I really think we need to conduct

215
00:10:04,690 --> 00:10:06,860
a deeper victimology of Keri Lodel.

216
00:10:06,880 --> 00:10:08,160
If you look at her mementos,

217
00:10:08,160 --> 00:10:10,930
she's obviously very popular with lots of different people,

218
00:10:10,930 --> 00:10:12,400
any one of whom could have developed

219
00:10:12,400 --> 00:10:14,160
some twisted sense of an attachment

220
00:10:14,160 --> 00:10:16,130
that would have motivated this violence.

221
00:10:16,210 --> 00:10:19,220
Okay. We'll have Monty follow up.

222
00:10:20,440 --> 00:10:22,740
So to be clear, the next step in your investigation

223
00:10:22,740 --> 00:10:24,650
was based on Agent Seger's recommendation?

224
00:10:24,650 --> 00:10:28,810
No. Conducting a victimology is part of our profile building.

225
00:10:28,810 --> 00:10:31,620
But you just described how Agent Seger said

226
00:10:31,620 --> 00:10:34,200
a deeper victimology would help you move off Delgado.

227
00:10:34,200 --> 00:10:35,970
That's not what I said, and you keep trying

228
00:10:35,980 --> 00:10:37,290
to twist my words like that.

229
00:10:37,290 --> 00:10:38,330
I'm only trying to clarify.

230
00:10:38,330 --> 00:10:39,910
You're trying to hang the IRT.

231
00:10:39,910 --> 00:10:41,300
That's what you're trying to do here.

232
00:10:41,300 --> 00:10:43,780
- Perhaps it's time we took a break. - I think we're fine.

233
00:10:43,780 --> 00:10:46,650
- I think we're taking a break. - Aron Sabri and Keri Lodel

234
00:10:46,650 --> 00:10:49,210
are not the only victims of this case.

235
00:10:49,340 --> 00:10:51,800
A civilian suspect lost his life

236
00:10:51,800 --> 00:10:54,650
because of the IRT's reckless actions.

237
00:10:55,140 --> 00:10:56,970
You think I want to hang the IRT?

238
00:10:57,750 --> 00:11:00,520
Unit Chief Garrett, let me be crystal clear with you.

239
00:11:00,820 --> 00:11:02,120
When we are all done here today,

240
00:11:02,120 --> 00:11:04,540
I will have everything I need to shatter the IRT

241
00:11:04,540 --> 00:11:06,020
into a thousand pieces

242
00:11:06,020 --> 00:11:08,150
and scatter the remnants to the wind.

243
00:11:19,340 --> 00:11:22,930
Well, that could have gone... better.

244
00:11:23,860 --> 00:11:27,260
- It's going fine. - Mm, 'cause you don't think

245
00:11:27,270 --> 00:11:30,450
it's hard to prove bias when you lay your own cards

246
00:11:30,450 --> 00:11:32,160
out on the table like that?

247
00:11:32,560 --> 00:11:34,210
You need to tread lightly.

248
00:11:34,240 --> 00:11:35,270
Is that so?

249
00:11:35,270 --> 00:11:37,900
Yes, it is. This isn't just an inquiry.

250
00:11:37,900 --> 00:11:40,180
This is a political game of chess.

251
00:11:40,640 --> 00:11:41,600
You like chess?

252
00:11:42,010 --> 00:11:43,280
I like boxing.

253
00:11:43,780 --> 00:11:47,470
I see that. Now I love chess myself.

254
00:11:47,520 --> 00:11:51,300
Requires patience and understanding strategy

255
00:11:51,300 --> 00:11:53,070
and of human weakness.

256
00:11:53,070 --> 00:11:55,670
Plus you always get to be king.

257
00:11:55,890 --> 00:11:57,410
Not that I don't appreciate the pep talk,

258
00:11:57,410 --> 00:11:58,720
but I don't.

259
00:11:58,720 --> 00:12:01,550
Settle down. I'm trying to protect you,

260
00:12:01,550 --> 00:12:04,560
and if you really wanna see justice done,

261
00:12:04,560 --> 00:12:07,590
you will gather the facts -- just the facts,

262
00:12:07,700 --> 00:12:10,260
and let the powers that be do the rest.

263
00:12:29,030 --> 00:12:29,970
I shouldn't have to remind you

264
00:12:29,970 --> 00:12:32,160
that no one in this room is under arrest.

265
00:12:32,160 --> 00:12:33,170
So if you don't mind,

266
00:12:33,170 --> 00:12:35,360
I'm gonna go stretch my legs and get some coffee.

267
00:12:38,530 --> 00:12:39,580
Anybody want anything?

268
00:12:40,500 --> 00:12:41,920
This is ridiculous.

269
00:12:42,650 --> 00:12:44,830
Look, I think it's best if we avoid sharing

270
00:12:45,100 --> 00:12:46,070
for the time being.

271
00:12:46,170 --> 00:12:47,510
You think they wired the room?

272
00:12:47,960 --> 00:12:49,450
Why would they wire the room?

273
00:12:50,470 --> 00:12:52,950
Because while we are not actually under arrest,

274
00:12:52,950 --> 00:12:55,260
we're prohibited from discussing anything that has to do

275
00:12:55,260 --> 00:12:56,820
with the case with each other.

276
00:12:56,820 --> 00:12:58,760
Unbelievable. What do they think that we're gonna do,

277
00:12:58,760 --> 00:13:00,610
sit in here and try to line our stories up?

278
00:13:00,610 --> 00:13:02,350
That's exactly what they think,

279
00:13:02,350 --> 00:13:04,450
and even the mere appearance of collusion

280
00:13:04,450 --> 00:13:06,930
is cause for termination if not straight up prosecution.

281
00:13:14,730 --> 00:13:17,450
So... how are Karen and the kids?

282
00:13:17,450 --> 00:13:19,660
Oh, come on, Walt. Cut the crap.

283
00:13:19,810 --> 00:13:22,700
I'm sorry, man. This is tough.

284
00:13:23,020 --> 00:13:25,050
But I want you to know I got your back.

285
00:13:25,060 --> 00:13:26,910
I don't need you to have my back.

286
00:13:27,260 --> 00:13:29,360
Jack, you heard the woman yourself.

287
00:13:29,360 --> 00:13:32,290
This is not about who is right or who is wrong.

288
00:13:32,510 --> 00:13:34,200
This is about who's to blame.

289
00:13:34,210 --> 00:13:36,650
Walt, we did everything by the book.

290
00:13:36,650 --> 00:13:40,090
I know you did, Jack, but we got a body count.

291
00:13:40,090 --> 00:13:43,900
So book or no book, somebody screwed the pooch.

292
00:13:43,900 --> 00:13:46,080
I just don't want that somebody to be you.

293
00:13:48,000 --> 00:13:49,490
You're not done with me yet.

294
00:13:49,740 --> 00:13:50,960
No, we're not.

295
00:13:51,070 --> 00:13:54,180
But you and Barnes needed a time-out,

296
00:13:54,180 --> 00:13:56,380
so...excuse me.

297
00:14:02,930 --> 00:14:05,950
Agent Seger, three years ago, you took a leave of absence.

298
00:14:06,800 --> 00:14:08,750
- Yes, I did. - Why?

299
00:14:10,350 --> 00:14:12,250
- Why? - Yes, that's the question.

300
00:14:13,310 --> 00:14:14,590
I'm not sure that I understand.

301
00:14:14,590 --> 00:14:17,520
You have my personal file sitting right in front of you.

302
00:14:17,520 --> 00:14:19,860
You know exactly why I took the time off.

303
00:14:20,740 --> 00:14:22,080
Yes, I do know why.

304
00:14:22,870 --> 00:14:26,320
Unfortunately, I suspect some of my tricks as an interrogator

305
00:14:26,320 --> 00:14:29,940
are going to be transparent to an expert in forensic psychology

306
00:14:29,940 --> 00:14:31,510
such as yourself, am I right?

307
00:14:31,510 --> 00:14:33,400
I'd only ask your indulgence.

308
00:14:34,130 --> 00:14:36,110
Or you can choose to not answer the question,

309
00:14:36,180 --> 00:14:38,370
but that might suggest something about your state of mind,

310
00:14:38,380 --> 00:14:39,160
don't you think?

311
00:14:40,280 --> 00:14:43,540
You want to play games? I can play your game.

312
00:14:44,660 --> 00:14:45,860
Three years ago,

313
00:14:46,260 --> 00:14:49,820
my husband, SSA Brad Seger --

314
00:14:49,900 --> 00:14:52,480
he was killed in the line of duty,

315
00:14:53,520 --> 00:14:56,970
and I took a leave of absence for bereavement.

316
00:14:59,740 --> 00:15:02,110
I'm very sorry for your loss.

317
00:15:03,310 --> 00:15:04,170
Thank you.

318
00:15:05,720 --> 00:15:08,110
During your bereavement leave, you traveled extensively,

319
00:15:08,110 --> 00:15:10,860
but I'd like to focus on the time you spent in Myanmar

320
00:15:10,860 --> 00:15:12,760
three years ago, during which time

321
00:15:12,760 --> 00:15:17,320
you became...quite familiar with Edward Delgado,

322
00:15:17,320 --> 00:15:18,780
the man who would later become

323
00:15:18,780 --> 00:15:20,620
the focus of the investigation in Qalea

324
00:15:20,620 --> 00:15:22,810
and the man whose complicated connection to you

325
00:15:22,810 --> 00:15:24,990
- would prejudice your team. - That is not true.

326
00:15:25,160 --> 00:15:27,490
Regardless of my personal knowledge of Delgado,

327
00:15:27,500 --> 00:15:30,370
my team, without prejudice, pursued this man as a fugitive

328
00:15:30,380 --> 00:15:31,160
from the law.

329
00:15:31,160 --> 00:15:33,910
In fact, it was Agent Montgomery who reached out to his wife

330
00:15:33,910 --> 00:15:36,660
to get a better understanding of where he might seek refuge.

331
00:15:41,250 --> 00:15:44,740
Agent Montgomery, I haven't been able to get ahold

332
00:15:44,740 --> 00:15:46,640
of my husband in 24 hours.

333
00:15:46,640 --> 00:15:49,970
- Mrs. Delgado -- - Please call me Amelia.

334
00:15:50,370 --> 00:15:52,150
Amelia, please.

335
00:15:56,640 --> 00:15:59,030
There was an incident at the GSD housing compound.

336
00:15:59,030 --> 00:16:00,290
Two people were killed.

337
00:16:00,290 --> 00:16:03,110
One was a woman who worked with your husband named Keri Lodel.

338
00:16:03,110 --> 00:16:06,440
The other was a security guard named Aron Sabri.

339
00:16:08,760 --> 00:16:10,470
Your husband is also missing.

340
00:16:10,900 --> 00:16:11,670
Missing?

341
00:16:13,000 --> 00:16:14,260
What do you mean, missing?

342
00:16:14,470 --> 00:16:15,640
Amelia, when was the last time

343
00:16:15,640 --> 00:16:17,090
you communicated with your husband?

344
00:16:17,090 --> 00:16:19,520
He E-mailed me yesterday morning.

345
00:16:19,590 --> 00:16:20,550
What did he say?

346
00:16:20,550 --> 00:16:22,550
Nothing. He just sent me photos.

347
00:16:22,550 --> 00:16:23,520
May I see them?

348
00:16:34,100 --> 00:16:35,920
How often did the two of you communicate

349
00:16:35,920 --> 00:16:37,480
while he was overseas?

350
00:16:38,180 --> 00:16:40,180
Once a week, mainly by e-mail.

351
00:16:40,640 --> 00:16:44,260
Must have been tough... for both of you.

352
00:16:45,510 --> 00:16:47,830
Why do I get the feeling that what you really wanna ask me

353
00:16:47,830 --> 00:16:50,390
is if I think my husband was sleeping with Keri.

354
00:16:52,510 --> 00:16:53,350
Is it possible?

355
00:16:53,350 --> 00:16:55,450
No, it isn't.

356
00:16:56,140 --> 00:16:58,790
He sent me those photos so that I could see his friends,

357
00:16:58,790 --> 00:16:59,590
that's all.

358
00:17:00,940 --> 00:17:01,640
Okay.

359
00:17:02,920 --> 00:17:05,610
Well, was your husband under any unusual stress lately?

360
00:17:06,120 --> 00:17:08,040
No, not that I know of.

361
00:17:08,570 --> 00:17:11,320
He's a good man. He gets along with everyone.

362
00:17:12,550 --> 00:17:16,380
I swear, he'd never hurt anyone.

363
00:17:17,420 --> 00:17:18,770
Delgado's wife gave me access

364
00:17:18,770 --> 00:17:20,000
to all of her husband's social media,

365
00:17:20,000 --> 00:17:22,000
and I'm going through it now, but I gotta be honest,

366
00:17:22,000 --> 00:17:24,090
Amelia seemed to know her husband really well.

367
00:17:24,090 --> 00:17:26,000
So if he wasn't having an affair with Keri,

368
00:17:26,000 --> 00:17:27,690
then what would be his motive to kill her?

369
00:17:27,740 --> 00:17:29,360
Well, if Delgado didn't kill Keri,

370
00:17:29,360 --> 00:17:30,640
then why does he attack the guard?

371
00:17:30,640 --> 00:17:31,740
And why does he run?

372
00:17:31,740 --> 00:17:33,980
Which brings us to our more pressing question --

373
00:17:33,980 --> 00:17:36,260
where is Edward Delgado?

374
00:17:36,420 --> 00:17:39,420
Listen, guilty or not, he's not some hardened criminal.

375
00:17:39,420 --> 00:17:41,000
He is a stranger in a strange land,

376
00:17:41,010 --> 00:17:42,640
and it's like Mae said before.

377
00:17:42,640 --> 00:17:44,940
If he did manage to sneak out of the Steel Ring,

378
00:17:44,940 --> 00:17:46,940
it's because he knows someone on the other side

379
00:17:46,940 --> 00:17:48,170
who might protect him.

380
00:17:48,860 --> 00:17:50,430
I may have found something.

381
00:17:50,430 --> 00:17:52,320
Looks like Delgado got pretty close

382
00:17:52,320 --> 00:17:54,370
to the family of his first interpreter.

383
00:17:54,410 --> 00:17:56,590
Young man's name is Omar Tahan.

384
00:17:56,670 --> 00:17:58,090
I apologize, Agent Seger.

385
00:17:58,090 --> 00:17:59,660
What was the young man's name again?

386
00:17:59,660 --> 00:18:00,490
Omar Tahan.

387
00:18:00,840 --> 00:18:03,250
He was Delgado's translator for two weeks

388
00:18:03,250 --> 00:18:04,280
until those duties were transferred to

389
00:18:04,280 --> 00:18:06,080
an officer from the KNP.

390
00:18:06,080 --> 00:18:08,000
And why were those duties transferred?

391
00:18:08,000 --> 00:18:09,320
Delgado's work exposed him

392
00:18:09,320 --> 00:18:11,800
to confidential KNP communications,

393
00:18:11,800 --> 00:18:15,480
and Mr. Tahan would have not been permitted access.

394
00:18:15,650 --> 00:18:17,780
Once you identified Mr. Tahan,

395
00:18:17,780 --> 00:18:19,670
what did you or your team do next?

396
00:18:19,670 --> 00:18:21,540
We drove out to the Tahan house.

397
00:18:21,540 --> 00:18:24,900
It was located 1 mile northwest of the Steel Ring,

398
00:18:24,900 --> 00:18:27,540
and that's where we discovered Mr. Delgado hiding out.

399
00:18:27,720 --> 00:18:29,190
Did he offer any resistance?

400
00:18:29,190 --> 00:18:32,440
No, he did not. He came into custody without incident.

401
00:18:32,440 --> 00:18:34,670
Agent Seger, whose decision was it

402
00:18:34,670 --> 00:18:36,260
to transport Edward Delgado

403
00:18:36,260 --> 00:18:37,700
back to the IRT jet

404
00:18:37,700 --> 00:18:40,990
rather than transfer him immediately into KNP custody?

405
00:18:40,990 --> 00:18:43,190
That was Unit Chief Garrett's decision.

406
00:18:43,190 --> 00:18:46,720
And do you recall if you perhaps challenged that decision?

407
00:18:46,870 --> 00:18:48,980
- No. - No, you don't recall, or...

408
00:18:48,980 --> 00:18:51,780
- No, I did not challenge it. - Did you encourage it?

409
00:18:52,100 --> 00:18:53,700
Look, at this point, Delgado was a suspect

410
00:18:53,700 --> 00:18:55,330
in a joint task force investigation

411
00:18:55,330 --> 00:18:57,490
between the IRT and the KNP.

412
00:18:57,490 --> 00:18:59,630
It was well within Unit Chief Garrett's purview

413
00:18:59,630 --> 00:19:01,920
to bring a suspect onto the jet for questioning.

414
00:19:01,920 --> 00:19:05,230
- And who questioned him? - I did.

415
00:19:18,590 --> 00:19:20,690
You gotta talk to me, Ed.

416
00:19:22,250 --> 00:19:24,480
You have to tell me what happened

417
00:19:24,700 --> 00:19:26,590
in the apartment with the guard.

418
00:19:27,840 --> 00:19:29,020
Why did you run?

419
00:19:31,630 --> 00:19:33,200
Were you sleeping with her?

420
00:19:35,310 --> 00:19:36,480
What do you think?

421
00:19:37,550 --> 00:19:40,780
Honestly, I don't think you'd ever betray

422
00:19:40,780 --> 00:19:42,170
the mother of your child.

423
00:19:43,980 --> 00:19:46,290
I just...wanna go home,

424
00:19:46,590 --> 00:19:49,570
and I swear to God I didn't do this.

425
00:19:49,790 --> 00:19:52,510
I know, so let me help you.

426
00:19:52,510 --> 00:19:54,720
But you don't understand. You can't.

427
00:19:57,950 --> 00:19:59,650
This is insane.

428
00:20:01,120 --> 00:20:03,020
You being here, dropping into my life,

429
00:20:03,020 --> 00:20:04,540
just like you did before.

430
00:20:06,570 --> 00:20:07,790
To "Save" Me.

431
00:20:14,090 --> 00:20:18,030
No, I think we saved each other.

432
00:20:19,920 --> 00:20:20,650
Did we?

433
00:20:22,300 --> 00:20:25,630
You know, I still remember exactly where we were

434
00:20:25,630 --> 00:20:27,220
when you told me we were together

435
00:20:27,220 --> 00:20:29,040
for all the wrong reasons.

436
00:20:30,740 --> 00:20:32,350
But the crazy thing is,

437
00:20:32,590 --> 00:20:37,230
if you don't leave me, then I don't go home.

438
00:20:37,810 --> 00:20:39,720
I don't get married, and...

439
00:20:40,370 --> 00:20:43,190
I don't get my baby girl, Julia, in my life.

440
00:20:43,190 --> 00:20:47,280
Yeah, and I don't get to be here with you right now to help you.

441
00:20:47,780 --> 00:20:49,580
You have to trust me, Ed.

442
00:20:50,090 --> 00:20:51,140
Truth is,

443
00:20:52,010 --> 00:20:55,730
there is only one person in the whole world

444
00:20:55,730 --> 00:20:57,180
that I trust, Clara.

445
00:20:58,560 --> 00:21:01,400
Clara, Jack just got off the phone with Captain Rifai.

446
00:21:01,740 --> 00:21:03,880
He's asking us to transfer him to KNP custody.

447
00:21:03,880 --> 00:21:05,560
KNP? No, hold on a second.

448
00:21:05,560 --> 00:21:08,440
I'm an American citizen arrested by the FBI.

449
00:21:08,440 --> 00:21:09,860
Why can't you guys hold on to me?

450
00:21:09,860 --> 00:21:12,020
Okay, everything is gonna be okay, Ed.

451
00:21:12,020 --> 00:21:14,290
My team and I will be with you every step of the way.

452
00:21:14,300 --> 00:21:15,890
It's a joint investigation.

453
00:21:15,890 --> 00:21:17,260
Actually, it was easier bringing him here

454
00:21:17,270 --> 00:21:19,130
than it will be getting him back to the Steel Ring,

455
00:21:19,130 --> 00:21:21,170
so I'll need to coordinate security protocols

456
00:21:21,170 --> 00:21:22,220
for Captain Rifai.

457
00:21:22,220 --> 00:21:23,890
Okay, I'll get him ready.

458
00:21:26,020 --> 00:21:27,760
Security protocols?

459
00:21:27,950 --> 00:21:29,920
Such as encrypting communications

460
00:21:29,920 --> 00:21:31,900
between the KNP and the IRT

461
00:21:31,980 --> 00:21:34,570
before, during, and after prisoner transfers.

462
00:21:34,570 --> 00:21:36,200
- Is that correct? - Yes.

463
00:21:36,610 --> 00:21:39,490
Excuse me, SSA Simmons.

464
00:21:39,490 --> 00:21:41,490
Could we rewind a moment here?

465
00:21:41,770 --> 00:21:44,100
You get the call from Captain Rifai.

466
00:21:44,250 --> 00:21:45,910
He asks you to give him the guy.

467
00:21:46,250 --> 00:21:49,470
Could you walk me through what should have happened next?

468
00:21:49,730 --> 00:21:52,240
The plan was for the IRT to convoy the prisoner

469
00:21:52,320 --> 00:21:55,050
back to KNP headquarters inside the Steel Ring.

470
00:21:55,210 --> 00:21:56,830
We were to travel by way of secured route,

471
00:21:56,830 --> 00:21:58,440
mapped by Captain Rifai.

472
00:21:58,440 --> 00:22:00,070
The primary concern for the operation

473
00:22:00,070 --> 00:22:01,730
was to avoid the main road

474
00:22:01,730 --> 00:22:03,780
between the airport and the Steel Ring.

475
00:22:03,910 --> 00:22:06,000
Right, because what do they call that road --

476
00:22:06,000 --> 00:22:07,450
"Damnation Alley"?

477
00:22:07,450 --> 00:22:08,150
Agent Simmons,

478
00:22:08,150 --> 00:22:09,690
we know what should have happened.

479
00:22:09,690 --> 00:22:12,220
- Tell us what did happen. - We were ambushed

480
00:22:13,380 --> 00:22:15,830
by fighters loyal to the Brotherhood of Faith.

481
00:22:15,900 --> 00:22:17,170
And do you know how you were targeted?

482
00:22:17,170 --> 00:22:18,180
How?

483
00:22:19,310 --> 00:22:21,900
No. It was a random attack.

484
00:22:21,900 --> 00:22:22,750
Random?

485
00:22:23,730 --> 00:22:25,560
It wasn't random.

486
00:22:25,560 --> 00:22:27,210
You were found because you got caught

487
00:22:27,210 --> 00:22:29,610
talking on open lines of communication.

488
00:22:29,610 --> 00:22:33,520
That's impossible. I personally secured those lines.

489
00:22:37,940 --> 00:22:39,590
Well, you tell me, sir.

490
00:22:39,800 --> 00:22:42,990
Are you incompetent, or are you a traitor?

491
00:22:43,510 --> 00:22:47,570
'Cause the digital evidence says no encryption.

492
00:22:52,610 --> 00:22:53,620
These logs can't be right.

493
00:22:53,620 --> 00:22:55,850
Those logs are from the KNP server.

494
00:22:57,420 --> 00:22:59,760
What happened during the ambush?

495
00:22:59,760 --> 00:23:01,480
We engaged in evasive maneuvers.

496
00:23:01,480 --> 00:23:03,770
At one point, we were forced off the road,

497
00:23:04,200 --> 00:23:05,890
and a gun battle ensued.

498
00:23:06,580 --> 00:23:08,240
The prisoner was hit by gunfire.

499
00:23:08,240 --> 00:23:10,330
You got Delgado shot.

500
00:23:10,880 --> 00:23:12,660
It was at that point the decision was made

501
00:23:12,660 --> 00:23:13,960
to double back to the jet.

502
00:23:13,960 --> 00:23:16,480
- Who made that decision? - Unit Chief Garrett.

503
00:23:17,160 --> 00:23:19,340
It was the only chance we had to save Delgado's life.

504
00:23:19,340 --> 00:23:21,290
Was that your unit chief's medical opinion

505
00:23:21,290 --> 00:23:24,550
or that of his field medical examiner, Agent Mae Jarvis?

506
00:23:24,550 --> 00:23:25,730
You know, I don't know.

507
00:23:25,740 --> 00:23:27,640
I was too busy getting us the hell out of there.

508
00:23:27,690 --> 00:23:29,770
Tell us what happened once you got back to the jet.

509
00:23:30,180 --> 00:23:32,070
Delgado had been shot in the chest.

510
00:23:33,000 --> 00:23:34,440
- Here, here. - I got him out of the SUV,

511
00:23:34,440 --> 00:23:36,520
and I was gonna help carry him up to the conference room,

512
00:23:36,940 --> 00:23:38,730
and that's when they tried to board the plane.

513
00:23:39,650 --> 00:23:41,920
"They" being those Brotherhood boys.

514
00:23:41,920 --> 00:23:44,560
Yes. Clara and Mae and the rest of our flight crew

515
00:23:44,560 --> 00:23:46,030
got Delgado out of the line of fire.

516
00:23:46,040 --> 00:23:47,180
All right, bring him right in here.

517
00:23:47,720 --> 00:23:48,620
Okay.

518
00:23:49,660 --> 00:23:51,750
Clara, can you get his vest off?

519
00:23:51,750 --> 00:23:52,520
Okay.

520
00:23:53,430 --> 00:23:54,920
I mean, there was a lot of chaos.

521
00:23:59,760 --> 00:24:01,510
Jack and I were able to hold them back

522
00:24:01,510 --> 00:24:03,510
while Clara and Mae tended to Delgado.

523
00:24:03,510 --> 00:24:05,150
We should get an oxygen line started.

524
00:24:06,670 --> 00:24:07,530
Tighter.

525
00:24:08,620 --> 00:24:10,480
And nobody else got injured?

526
00:24:10,490 --> 00:24:11,500
I'm sorry?

527
00:24:11,750 --> 00:24:14,760
Delgado was the only one who got shot.

528
00:24:14,850 --> 00:24:15,970
Yes, he was.

529
00:24:16,870 --> 00:24:19,150
We were able to get the cargo bay doors closed.

530
00:24:24,870 --> 00:24:28,400
But you weren't able to save Delgado's life, were you?

531
00:24:28,400 --> 00:24:30,930
Come on. Stay with me. Come on.

532
00:24:32,320 --> 00:24:33,220
Mae.

533
00:24:33,440 --> 00:24:34,590
Come on, Edward!

534
00:24:38,640 --> 00:24:40,930
Okay, tell me what to do. What do I do?

535
00:24:44,180 --> 00:24:45,050
Mae?

536
00:24:45,610 --> 00:24:46,730
He's gone.

537
00:24:55,160 --> 00:24:56,250
I'm sorry.

538
00:25:02,540 --> 00:25:04,200
Looks like they're regrouping, Jack.

539
00:25:04,290 --> 00:25:06,040
Probably calling in reinforcements.

540
00:25:06,040 --> 00:25:07,160
Well, you don't think they're gonna try

541
00:25:07,160 --> 00:25:07,930
and board the plane, do you?

542
00:25:07,930 --> 00:25:09,460
I don't want to have to find out.

543
00:25:10,120 --> 00:25:12,560
Captain Rifai, where's our backup you promised?

544
00:25:12,600 --> 00:25:14,660
They are en route to you now.

545
00:25:14,660 --> 00:25:16,820
SSA Jarvis, when Unit Chief Garrett

546
00:25:16,820 --> 00:25:18,320
ordered the unit back to the jet,

547
00:25:18,320 --> 00:25:20,620
did you know the full extent of Mr. Delgado's injuries?

548
00:25:20,630 --> 00:25:22,990
Um, I had identified an entry wound

549
00:25:22,990 --> 00:25:24,800
to his upper right thoracic region,

550
00:25:24,810 --> 00:25:28,000
and I suspected that his lung had collapsed.

551
00:25:28,250 --> 00:25:29,810
So did you challenge the order?

552
00:25:29,810 --> 00:25:33,080
- No. - You had a man with a gaping chest wound,

553
00:25:33,080 --> 00:25:36,210
and you didn't insist on being rerouted to U.S. Camp Granato,

554
00:25:36,250 --> 00:25:37,720
where they have a field hospital?

555
00:25:37,860 --> 00:25:39,860
No, I didn't, because

556
00:25:40,040 --> 00:25:42,390
I mean, truth is, I knew that what I had on the plane

557
00:25:42,390 --> 00:25:45,730
could stabilize him, and everything else

558
00:25:45,730 --> 00:25:47,360
was just an unknown variable,

559
00:25:47,360 --> 00:25:49,900
and it was all happening while we were under enemy fire.

560
00:25:50,660 --> 00:25:52,130
I get it. It was tough out there.

561
00:25:52,130 --> 00:25:54,970
- Yeah, it was. - Maybe that speaks to why,

562
00:25:54,970 --> 00:25:58,010
after medical school, you became a medical examiner

563
00:25:58,010 --> 00:26:00,140
instead of continuing in trauma medicine.

564
00:26:01,160 --> 00:26:02,300
Excuse me?

565
00:26:02,910 --> 00:26:05,650
Do you recall a young man

566
00:26:05,660 --> 00:26:08,380
by the name of Dylan Jacobs?

567
00:26:09,680 --> 00:26:12,730
Yeah. Yeah, I remember Dylan.

568
00:26:12,770 --> 00:26:16,450
You were a resident at St. Colette's Trauma Center

569
00:26:16,450 --> 00:26:17,500
the night he was brought in.

570
00:26:17,500 --> 00:26:19,080
Do you recall what happened to him?

571
00:26:19,890 --> 00:26:21,430
Yeah, he died on the table.

572
00:26:22,250 --> 00:26:25,110
And his family felt that you and Dr. Justin Wyatt

573
00:26:25,110 --> 00:26:26,840
and the hospital were negligent.

574
00:26:26,840 --> 00:26:28,280
They filed a lawsuit.

575
00:26:28,570 --> 00:26:30,790
Uh, that was settled out of court

576
00:26:31,450 --> 00:26:33,160
with a nondisclosure agreement.

577
00:26:33,170 --> 00:26:36,960
So are you saying you can't disclose whether or not

578
00:26:36,960 --> 00:26:39,430
you feel responsible for Mr. Jacobs' death?

579
00:26:47,900 --> 00:26:50,820
Jack, I am so sorry.

580
00:26:50,990 --> 00:26:52,380
I-I should have told you everything.

581
00:26:52,380 --> 00:26:54,050
No, it's all right, Clara.

582
00:26:54,050 --> 00:26:55,780
You told me everything you needed to.

583
00:26:58,460 --> 00:26:59,510
Hey, guys, listen.

584
00:26:59,510 --> 00:27:01,200
I-I know we're not supposed to talk,

585
00:27:01,750 --> 00:27:03,560
but there is something else going on here.

586
00:27:03,630 --> 00:27:06,380
Barnes and Atwood basically blamed me

587
00:27:06,480 --> 00:27:07,840
for the entire ambush.

588
00:27:08,060 --> 00:27:10,920
They said that I didn't encrypt the lines of communications,

589
00:27:10,990 --> 00:27:12,320
and what they offered as proof

590
00:27:12,320 --> 00:27:15,080
were the digital log books from the KNP command post.

591
00:27:15,410 --> 00:27:17,100
I'm telling you, those logs were doctored.

592
00:27:17,650 --> 00:27:18,370
But, presumably,

593
00:27:18,370 --> 00:27:20,010
only somebody who works for the KNP

594
00:27:20,010 --> 00:27:21,420
- could have done that. - Right.

595
00:27:21,760 --> 00:27:23,880
Clara, I think you were right from the start.

596
00:27:23,990 --> 00:27:26,920
Delgado never fit the profile of Keri's killer.

597
00:27:28,250 --> 00:27:30,710
Question is, why did he run?

598
00:27:31,050 --> 00:27:32,940
Maybe he didn't trust the local cops.

599
00:27:33,090 --> 00:27:37,470
Maybe. Delgado's job focused primarily on improving

600
00:27:37,470 --> 00:27:39,520
cybersecurity for the KNP,

601
00:27:39,520 --> 00:27:41,330
so what if he came across something

602
00:27:41,330 --> 00:27:42,780
that he shouldn't have?

603
00:27:43,000 --> 00:27:45,420
A secret, something so compromising

604
00:27:45,420 --> 00:27:47,250
that someone inside the KNP would be

605
00:27:47,250 --> 00:27:49,300
willing to frame him for murder.

606
00:27:49,960 --> 00:27:51,750
Okay, but consider this.

607
00:27:51,750 --> 00:27:54,240
You know that security guard, Aron Sabri?

608
00:27:54,280 --> 00:27:56,290
he was only moonlighting at the GSD compound.

609
00:27:56,290 --> 00:27:59,350
His primary job was patrol officer for the KNP.

610
00:27:59,440 --> 00:28:00,710
Remember the abrasions on his hands?

611
00:28:00,930 --> 00:28:02,580
the ones that Mae really couldn't explain?

612
00:28:03,260 --> 00:28:05,460
What if they hadn't come from a struggle with Delgado?

613
00:28:05,460 --> 00:28:07,430
What if they were a result of stabbing Keri

614
00:28:07,440 --> 00:28:08,580
over and over again?

615
00:28:08,580 --> 00:28:11,810
So you think the original plan was the guard kills Keri,

616
00:28:11,810 --> 00:28:15,090
then he kills Delgado as he tries to escape.

617
00:28:15,370 --> 00:28:17,240
Only Delgado got the better of him.

618
00:28:17,660 --> 00:28:19,930
Unfortunately, as good as this sounds,

619
00:28:19,940 --> 00:28:21,430
it's pure speculation.

620
00:28:21,430 --> 00:28:23,320
Yeah, and given our current status,

621
00:28:23,320 --> 00:28:24,660
we need some hard evidence to prove

622
00:28:24,660 --> 00:28:27,670
that someone from the KNP was behind all of this.

623
00:28:27,670 --> 00:28:29,860
And I'm not sure we're gonna be able to prove anything

624
00:28:29,870 --> 00:28:32,030
when we've been stripped of everything.

625
00:28:33,200 --> 00:28:34,480
Maybe not everything.

626
00:28:35,290 --> 00:28:36,880
Look, if we're right about Delgado,

627
00:28:36,880 --> 00:28:38,840
and he did discover the KNP's dirty little secret,

628
00:28:38,840 --> 00:28:40,800
if he's the man that I remember,

629
00:28:40,940 --> 00:28:42,970
he would have hedged his bets on the evidence.

630
00:28:43,000 --> 00:28:44,000
What do you mean?

631
00:28:44,200 --> 00:28:46,200
I think that he would have sent his proof

632
00:28:46,210 --> 00:28:48,080
to the only person in the world that he trusts.

633
00:29:02,490 --> 00:29:04,770
- You okay? - Sure.

634
00:29:11,080 --> 00:29:12,920
Look, you know they're just playing these mind games

635
00:29:12,920 --> 00:29:14,640
in order to try to break you.

636
00:29:15,490 --> 00:29:17,090
Yeah, well, they're ballers at it,

637
00:29:17,090 --> 00:29:19,810
'cause I feel pretty broken.

638
00:29:20,970 --> 00:29:22,250
It'll be all right.

639
00:29:24,060 --> 00:29:25,460
I mean, I don't care what anybody says.

640
00:29:25,460 --> 00:29:29,660
When you have someone's life in your hands,

641
00:29:30,070 --> 00:29:32,960
you feel the weight of that responsibility.

642
00:29:34,230 --> 00:29:37,180
And, yeah, you can -- you can put on a brave face,

643
00:29:38,060 --> 00:29:41,950
but I don't think you ever really learn how to...

644
00:29:42,350 --> 00:29:44,110
turn your emotions on and off.

645
00:29:45,810 --> 00:29:47,520
And if you lose that person,

646
00:29:49,920 --> 00:29:51,950
you never stop second-guessing yourself.

647
00:30:00,310 --> 00:30:02,920
Agent Montgomery, I'd like to direct your attention

648
00:30:02,920 --> 00:30:07,590
to the events that took place after Mr. Delgado's death.

649
00:30:07,880 --> 00:30:11,500
You recall receiving a distress call from Betsy Ross?

650
00:30:11,740 --> 00:30:12,760
Yes, I do.

651
00:30:12,760 --> 00:30:14,180
Hey, boss, what's going on?

652
00:30:14,180 --> 00:30:15,130
We're in trouble.

653
00:30:15,140 --> 00:30:16,890
We got ambushed by the Brotherhood.

654
00:30:16,890 --> 00:30:18,850
We sustained a casualty. It looks like

655
00:30:18,850 --> 00:30:20,170
they're gonna try to board the plane.

656
00:30:20,170 --> 00:30:21,690
Okay, I'll call the KNP right now.

657
00:30:21,690 --> 00:30:23,240
I tried that. They're too far away.

658
00:30:23,240 --> 00:30:24,670
I need you to call in the cavalry

659
00:30:24,670 --> 00:30:26,600
from U.S. Camp Granato right now.

660
00:30:28,570 --> 00:30:32,020
Why did you ignore Unit Chief Garrett's direct order?

661
00:30:32,020 --> 00:30:34,340
I didn't ignore it. I assessed the situation.

662
00:30:34,340 --> 00:30:36,490
I looked at the map. They were too far away.

663
00:30:36,650 --> 00:30:39,200
Perhaps you would be willing to tell us

664
00:30:39,230 --> 00:30:42,100
when you first became aware of the existence

665
00:30:42,100 --> 00:30:45,090
of the Z-TAC Nighthawk S-2.

666
00:30:45,640 --> 00:30:49,090
I can't tell you about a program that doesn't exist, now, can I?

667
00:30:49,150 --> 00:30:50,580
You must think you're pretty smart.

668
00:30:50,580 --> 00:30:53,270
I think the Nighthawk S-2 is the worst kept secret

669
00:30:53,270 --> 00:30:54,810
in the U.S. Intelligence community.

670
00:30:55,090 --> 00:30:57,690
Did Jack Garrett direct you to compromise

671
00:30:57,690 --> 00:30:58,930
the Nighthawk system?

672
00:30:58,980 --> 00:31:00,090
No, he did not.

673
00:31:00,480 --> 00:31:02,560
- What's going on? - They're knocking at the door.

674
00:31:02,560 --> 00:31:03,930
Okay, Jack, the way I see it,

675
00:31:03,930 --> 00:31:06,040
your only option is to take off right now.

676
00:31:06,040 --> 00:31:07,580
I'm not sure how that's gonna happen.

677
00:31:07,580 --> 00:31:09,540
- They've got us surrounded. - Not for long.

678
00:31:15,110 --> 00:31:16,450
Agent Montgomery,

679
00:31:16,450 --> 00:31:18,950
do you know what it means to misappropriate

680
00:31:18,950 --> 00:31:24,450
and destroy a $164 million unmanned aerial vehicle?

681
00:31:24,450 --> 00:31:26,190
With all due respect, $164 million

682
00:31:26,190 --> 00:31:28,260
suggests that you're including the R&D on the project.

683
00:31:28,260 --> 00:31:31,980
The price tag for a single drone is $3.74 million.

684
00:31:31,980 --> 00:31:34,130
Do you honestly think this is a joke?

685
00:31:34,130 --> 00:31:36,890
Yes. Do you wanna know if I stole the drone?

686
00:31:37,020 --> 00:31:40,160
Yes, I stole the drone because there were men with guns

687
00:31:40,160 --> 00:31:42,610
going after my team, so I hacked

688
00:31:42,610 --> 00:31:44,540
the nearest surveillance drone in flight

689
00:31:44,540 --> 00:31:48,870
and I strafed the airfield with it...several times.

690
00:31:51,250 --> 00:31:52,240
Thank God those boys over at the Brotherhood of Faith

691
00:31:52,240 --> 00:31:53,590
are really bad at skeet shooting,

692
00:31:53,590 --> 00:31:54,770
because that gave them time

693
00:31:54,770 --> 00:31:56,860
to draw away from the plane

694
00:31:56,860 --> 00:32:01,120
and for me to create a $3.74 million light show,

695
00:32:02,260 --> 00:32:03,960
which allowed my team to get off the tarmac

696
00:32:03,960 --> 00:32:05,110
and get out of harm's way.

697
00:32:05,120 --> 00:32:06,960
Were you aware of enemy casualties?

698
00:32:06,960 --> 00:32:10,290
- There were none. - You didn't know that at the time.

699
00:32:10,330 --> 00:32:11,890
I understand at the end of all this,

700
00:32:11,890 --> 00:32:13,120
there has to be a blame game,

701
00:32:13,230 --> 00:32:14,900
but the truth of the matter is

702
00:32:15,310 --> 00:32:19,190
there's only a chosen few who will ever be qualified

703
00:32:19,230 --> 00:32:20,490
to work in the field.

704
00:32:21,370 --> 00:32:22,970
There's no other way to say it.

705
00:32:23,460 --> 00:32:26,260
Their instincts, their judgment,

706
00:32:27,730 --> 00:32:29,740
their courage --

707
00:32:29,800 --> 00:32:33,710
it's better... because it has to be.

708
00:32:34,040 --> 00:32:35,800
Because in the heat of the moment,

709
00:32:36,100 --> 00:32:37,980
they make the hard choices.

710
00:32:38,770 --> 00:32:42,830
And do you think that you are one of those chosen few?

711
00:32:45,260 --> 00:32:46,380
I don't think it.

712
00:32:48,000 --> 00:32:50,170
I know, so I did what I did.

713
00:32:50,170 --> 00:32:51,220
I'd do it again,

714
00:32:51,220 --> 00:32:53,860
and I'm now prepared to accept the consequences of my actions.

715
00:32:54,390 --> 00:32:57,810
Good, because, Agent Montgomery...

716
00:32:58,130 --> 00:32:59,430
...you're under arrest,

717
00:32:59,640 --> 00:33:01,940
for willful theft, malfeasance,

718
00:33:01,940 --> 00:33:03,980
and destruction of government property.

719
00:33:04,100 --> 00:33:05,250
I need your badge.

720
00:33:21,120 --> 00:33:22,200
Hello, Amelia.

721
00:33:24,010 --> 00:33:26,280
Thank you for, for meeting me.

722
00:33:29,720 --> 00:33:31,820
Ed and I had no secrets, Clara.

723
00:33:32,890 --> 00:33:34,810
I came here today because I know

724
00:33:34,810 --> 00:33:36,460
that you were important to his life,

725
00:33:36,460 --> 00:33:39,010
and I really need someone to get justice for him

726
00:33:39,020 --> 00:33:40,110
and for Keri.

727
00:33:41,150 --> 00:33:42,890
That's exactly what I intend to do.

728
00:33:44,590 --> 00:33:47,520
May I see the photos that he e-mailed you?

729
00:33:56,630 --> 00:33:57,890
Did Ed have a habit

730
00:33:57,890 --> 00:34:00,340
of sending you candid snapshots like these?

731
00:34:00,350 --> 00:34:02,740
No. But I'm glad he did.

732
00:34:06,240 --> 00:34:08,490
Do you mind e-mailing me copies of these?

733
00:34:09,380 --> 00:34:10,330
Why?

734
00:34:10,790 --> 00:34:12,400
Amelia, my team and I believe

735
00:34:12,400 --> 00:34:14,280
that Ed was framed for Keri's murder

736
00:34:14,280 --> 00:34:16,300
because of a secret that he discovered,

737
00:34:16,300 --> 00:34:18,930
and I think these photos will tell me

738
00:34:18,930 --> 00:34:20,350
exactly what that secret is.

739
00:34:24,810 --> 00:34:26,450
Hey, what's going on here?

740
00:34:27,590 --> 00:34:29,760
- It's all right, Jack. - No, it's not all right.

741
00:34:29,760 --> 00:34:33,090
Let it go, my friend. Let it play out.

742
00:34:33,090 --> 00:34:34,330
It's all part of the process.

743
00:34:34,330 --> 00:34:35,260
What's the charge?

744
00:34:35,260 --> 00:34:36,420
What does it matter, Jack?

745
00:34:36,420 --> 00:34:38,170
This is the worst of it.

746
00:34:38,170 --> 00:34:39,270
Walter, listen to me.

747
00:34:39,270 --> 00:34:40,780
Delgado was set up.

748
00:34:40,860 --> 00:34:42,610
I may have a way to get the evidence.

749
00:34:42,610 --> 00:34:44,770
Agent Seger and Simmons are working on --

750
00:34:45,700 --> 00:34:47,740
Seger and Simmons can't be working on anything.

751
00:34:47,750 --> 00:34:48,870
You know that.

752
00:34:49,480 --> 00:34:50,570
Oh, damn it, Jack.

753
00:34:50,570 --> 00:34:52,670
You have just opened yourself right back up.

754
00:34:52,670 --> 00:34:54,520
We're talking insubordination.

755
00:34:54,520 --> 00:34:56,590
Yeah, yeah, not to mention

756
00:34:56,590 --> 00:34:59,010
conduct unbecoming a federal officer.

757
00:34:59,600 --> 00:35:01,050
Take him back upstairs.

758
00:35:17,690 --> 00:35:20,060
Please, take a seat.

759
00:35:22,100 --> 00:35:23,200
Unit Chief Garrett,

760
00:35:23,200 --> 00:35:25,150
during the course of the proceedings today,

761
00:35:25,150 --> 00:35:27,050
did you or did you not communicate

762
00:35:27,050 --> 00:35:28,810
with members of your IRT unit?

763
00:35:28,810 --> 00:35:30,720
- I did. - Where and when did

764
00:35:30,720 --> 00:35:33,030
these prohibited communications take place?

765
00:35:33,030 --> 00:35:34,210
Like the rest of my team,

766
00:35:34,210 --> 00:35:37,040
I feel responsible for Mr. Delgado's death.

767
00:35:37,050 --> 00:35:38,090
That wasn't the question.

768
00:35:38,090 --> 00:35:39,240
It's the reason we're here.

769
00:35:39,240 --> 00:35:40,030
Unit Chief Garrett.

770
00:35:40,030 --> 00:35:42,470
The real reason that Mr. Delgado is dead

771
00:35:43,300 --> 00:35:44,470
is betrayal.

772
00:35:45,730 --> 00:35:46,940
What are you talking about?

773
00:35:47,050 --> 00:35:48,870
He was a good man doing good work,

774
00:35:48,870 --> 00:35:51,280
who, by chance, uncovered a secret.

775
00:35:51,500 --> 00:35:53,630
He found out about a deal between the KNP

776
00:35:53,630 --> 00:35:55,550
and the leader of the Brotherhood of Faith,

777
00:35:55,560 --> 00:35:56,850
Rashan Noori.

778
00:35:57,760 --> 00:35:59,830
In exchange for ratting out terrorist cells,

779
00:35:59,830 --> 00:36:01,690
Noori was guaranteed that the KNP

780
00:36:01,690 --> 00:36:02,620
would turn a blind eye

781
00:36:02,620 --> 00:36:04,460
toward its own criminal activities

782
00:36:04,460 --> 00:36:07,930
which include the trafficking of Kurjik children.

783
00:36:08,060 --> 00:36:10,190
You know all this how?

784
00:36:10,190 --> 00:36:12,010
Delgado followed the protocol.

785
00:36:12,010 --> 00:36:14,280
He met with the U.S. Ombudsman in Qalea.

786
00:36:14,280 --> 00:36:17,230
He offered evidence, but to answer your question,

787
00:36:17,230 --> 00:36:21,260
I know about all this because Mr. Delgado

788
00:36:21,260 --> 00:36:23,460
also violated protocol.

789
00:36:23,700 --> 00:36:26,330
He sent copies of the same evidence to his wife

790
00:36:26,870 --> 00:36:29,710
in encrypted messages in photos.

791
00:36:30,950 --> 00:36:32,150
Like this one.

792
00:36:36,140 --> 00:36:39,130
Saying that Edward Delgado used steganography?

793
00:36:39,130 --> 00:36:43,000
Yes. He was able to camouflage one digital file within another,

794
00:36:43,000 --> 00:36:45,390
and if you continue to swipe past those images,

795
00:36:45,390 --> 00:36:47,720
you'll find the encryption that was provided to me

796
00:36:47,720 --> 00:36:51,050
by BAU Technical Analyst, Penelope Garcia.

797
00:36:51,320 --> 00:36:52,550
Let me see that.

798
00:36:54,680 --> 00:36:57,310
Despite this evidence, your conduct --

799
00:36:57,310 --> 00:36:59,670
This evidence helps to prove that the IRT

800
00:36:59,670 --> 00:37:01,900
was also set up, just like Delgado.

801
00:37:02,010 --> 00:37:02,990
Set up?

802
00:37:02,990 --> 00:37:05,800
Yes, because the most compromising part

803
00:37:05,800 --> 00:37:07,500
of this deal with the devil is that

804
00:37:07,500 --> 00:37:10,710
it was all illegally sanctioned

805
00:37:10,710 --> 00:37:12,220
by a U.S. Intelligence officer.

806
00:37:12,410 --> 00:37:14,270
That's why Delgado had to be framed.

807
00:37:14,270 --> 00:37:16,500
That's why my team had to be ambushed --

808
00:37:16,510 --> 00:37:19,060
to protect the identity of the officer,

809
00:37:20,230 --> 00:37:21,680
code-named "Bishop."

810
00:37:22,180 --> 00:37:24,920
I have an obligation to tell you that if you accuse

811
00:37:24,990 --> 00:37:26,850
an Intelligence officer of a crime

812
00:37:26,850 --> 00:37:28,270
without sufficient evidence...

813
00:37:28,270 --> 00:37:30,030
That's the real trick, isn't it?

814
00:37:30,460 --> 00:37:32,930
How do you get to the truth in a shadow world

815
00:37:32,930 --> 00:37:34,350
defended by lies?

816
00:37:35,690 --> 00:37:38,820
I like to think that's where profiling comes in handy.

817
00:37:39,240 --> 00:37:43,140
The ability to decipher motive behind behavior,

818
00:37:43,360 --> 00:37:45,690
the liar behind the lie.

819
00:37:47,350 --> 00:37:48,880
Something tells me you think

820
00:37:48,880 --> 00:37:50,260
you already know the answer to that, Jack.

821
00:37:50,260 --> 00:37:52,010
I think I do, Linda.

822
00:37:52,460 --> 00:37:55,470
First, you have to ask yourself who benefits?

823
00:37:56,530 --> 00:37:59,110
Who would be best served by taking advantage

824
00:37:59,110 --> 00:38:00,990
of an off-the-shelf resource like Noori?

825
00:38:00,990 --> 00:38:03,500
But more importantly, who would have the nerve

826
00:38:03,500 --> 00:38:05,530
to make that deal with the devil?

827
00:38:07,590 --> 00:38:09,990
It would have to be somebody who felt comfortable

828
00:38:09,990 --> 00:38:13,000
rationalizing all those necessary evils

829
00:38:13,000 --> 00:38:15,940
in order to protect the greater good.

830
00:38:16,340 --> 00:38:17,790
It'd have to be somebody who believes that

831
00:38:17,790 --> 00:38:19,360
the ends always justify the means.

832
00:38:19,360 --> 00:38:20,270
Right.

833
00:38:21,480 --> 00:38:22,910
You see what I'm saying?

834
00:38:23,900 --> 00:38:28,870
Bishop. So maybe even someone who enjoys

835
00:38:28,870 --> 00:38:30,060
the game of chess?

836
00:38:30,370 --> 00:38:33,260
Because in chess, the Bishop's personality

837
00:38:33,260 --> 00:38:36,020
is often considered sly, cunning...

838
00:38:37,860 --> 00:38:39,140
and corrupt.

839
00:38:39,520 --> 00:38:41,550
Plus you always get to be king.

840
00:38:43,690 --> 00:38:45,200
Assistant Director Barnes,

841
00:38:45,200 --> 00:38:48,870
I would consider your next move carefully.

842
00:38:49,020 --> 00:38:51,340
Oh. I am.

843
00:38:52,260 --> 00:38:54,200
Deputy Director Atwood, you're under arrest.

844
00:38:54,210 --> 00:38:55,980
You have the right to remain silent.

845
00:38:55,980 --> 00:38:57,750
You can't be serious.

846
00:38:58,300 --> 00:38:59,980
Jack's psycho profile

847
00:38:59,980 --> 00:39:01,550
B.S. isn't evidence.

848
00:39:01,550 --> 00:39:03,330
But the e-mails that Agent Garcia

849
00:39:03,330 --> 00:39:06,110
found on your private server are, Walter.

850
00:39:07,560 --> 00:39:10,590
You have no idea what you've done.

851
00:39:10,590 --> 00:39:12,030
You son of a bitch.

852
00:39:12,840 --> 00:39:14,550
You had Delgado killed.

853
00:39:14,710 --> 00:39:16,280
You put my team in the line of fire

854
00:39:16,280 --> 00:39:17,350
like we were expendable.

855
00:39:17,350 --> 00:39:19,070
You are expendable!

856
00:39:19,600 --> 00:39:22,050
Because you're soldiers, Jack, just like I am.

857
00:39:22,130 --> 00:39:24,540
And soldiers sacrifice themselves

858
00:39:24,540 --> 00:39:26,190
so others won't have to.

859
00:39:26,450 --> 00:39:29,570
You think I like lying down with dogs like Noori?

860
00:39:29,800 --> 00:39:32,520
You're damn right it's a necessary evil.

861
00:39:32,680 --> 00:39:33,280
You know why?

862
00:39:33,280 --> 00:39:36,010
Because we're at war, my friends.

863
00:39:36,060 --> 00:39:38,120
Make no mistake, just because we're telling people

864
00:39:38,120 --> 00:39:40,190
to keep streaming and shopping,

865
00:39:40,470 --> 00:39:43,530
we're in a dog fight for everything we hold to be true.

866
00:39:43,980 --> 00:39:45,320
And without men like me,

867
00:39:45,680 --> 00:39:48,680
without men willing to do what is necessary,

868
00:39:48,780 --> 00:39:50,590
we will lose!

869
00:39:50,610 --> 00:39:52,600
Spare me the self-righteousness,

870
00:39:52,600 --> 00:39:55,730
and don't you dare compare yourself

871
00:39:55,730 --> 00:39:57,430
to the men and women in uniform.

872
00:39:58,580 --> 00:39:59,680
You're a clerk

873
00:40:00,390 --> 00:40:01,540
and a criminal.

874
00:40:02,300 --> 00:40:03,460
Get him outta here.

875
00:40:20,280 --> 00:40:21,340
How you doing?

876
00:40:22,210 --> 00:40:24,140
Better, now that I got the handcuffs off.

877
00:40:24,140 --> 00:40:26,390
But...what's going on?

878
00:40:30,630 --> 00:40:32,310
Given our current state of affairs,

879
00:40:32,310 --> 00:40:34,440
I've agreed to this little tite-e-tite.

880
00:40:35,030 --> 00:40:36,040
Thank you.

881
00:40:36,380 --> 00:40:37,720
Obviously, I've made no secret

882
00:40:37,720 --> 00:40:39,970
about my desire to diminish the IRT's role.

883
00:40:39,970 --> 00:40:41,590
You'd like to get rid of us.

884
00:40:41,660 --> 00:40:42,840
I'd like you to be accountable.

885
00:40:42,840 --> 00:40:45,510
We are. We always have been.

886
00:40:45,700 --> 00:40:47,510
Then why did you ask me here, Jack?

887
00:40:47,600 --> 00:40:50,420
If not to ask for leniency for Agent Montgomery?

888
00:40:50,550 --> 00:40:52,050
And this is what I'm talking about.

889
00:40:52,050 --> 00:40:54,970
The fact remains that in spite of his good intentions

890
00:40:54,970 --> 00:40:57,260
or the positive results, Agent Montgomery

891
00:40:57,260 --> 00:40:59,350
must be held accountable for his actions.

892
00:40:59,680 --> 00:41:01,090
And even if I were to recommend

893
00:41:01,150 --> 00:41:02,970
not seeking criminal prosecution,

894
00:41:03,250 --> 00:41:06,110
at the very least, the Bureau must terminate his employment.

895
00:41:06,900 --> 00:41:07,960
She's right, Jack.

896
00:41:08,270 --> 00:41:09,520
No, I don't think so.

897
00:41:10,290 --> 00:41:12,310
Because Agent Montgomery's actions

898
00:41:12,310 --> 00:41:14,900
or any actions taken by a member of my team

899
00:41:15,140 --> 00:41:16,190
are done on my orders,

900
00:41:16,190 --> 00:41:18,580
whether directly stated or implied.

901
00:41:18,580 --> 00:41:20,170
The buck stops with me, always,

902
00:41:20,170 --> 00:41:23,750
so if anyone's gonna get fired, it's me.

903
00:41:24,790 --> 00:41:26,120
I'm serious, Linda.

904
00:41:26,130 --> 00:41:28,470
I know you are, Jack, but I'm not sure

905
00:41:28,470 --> 00:41:30,640
you appreciate the scope of the situation here.

906
00:41:30,770 --> 00:41:31,550
You just took down

907
00:41:31,550 --> 00:41:33,320
the Deputy Director of National Intelligence.

908
00:41:33,320 --> 00:41:35,360
Now I'm gonna be the one to take your badge?

909
00:41:35,360 --> 00:41:37,970
Yes, because that's how it works.

910
00:41:37,970 --> 00:41:39,370
That's accountability.

911
00:41:44,520 --> 00:41:47,400
Unit Chief Jack Garrett, let me be crystal clear.

912
00:41:47,860 --> 00:41:50,960
You and your unit are on notice.

913
00:41:50,960 --> 00:41:52,560
You may consider this your first strike,

914
00:41:52,560 --> 00:41:55,390
and in this game, a second strike means you are out.

915
00:42:08,140 --> 00:42:09,090
You good?

916
00:42:09,380 --> 00:42:12,470
Me? Forget about me. They were about to lock you up.

917
00:42:12,470 --> 00:42:14,500
Yeah, but I knew you guys would come break me out, right?

918
00:42:14,530 --> 00:42:16,010
Or share a cell with you.

919
00:42:16,330 --> 00:42:17,850
We had each other's backs.

920
00:42:18,060 --> 00:42:22,160
Yes, we did. Let's go home, get some rest.

921
00:42:23,450 --> 00:42:24,720
Uh, guys?

922
00:42:28,960 --> 00:42:31,070
Well... no rest for the wicked.

923
00:42:34,420 --> 00:42:35,340
No.

924
00:42:36,940 --> 00:42:38,600
'Cause we got a job to do.

