1
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:05,000
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

2
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:05,000
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

3
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:05,000
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

4
00:00:00,500 --> 00:00:05,000
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

5
00:00:00,500 --> 00:00:05,000
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35

6
00:00:00,500 --> 00:00:05,000
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

7
00:00:00,500 --> 00:00:05,000
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

8
00:00:00,500 --> 00:00:05,000
原創翻譯  雙語字幕

9
00:00:01,000 --> 00:00:05,000
最新連載海外影視劇下載
請登陸 www.YYeTs.com
僅供交流學習  禁止商用盈利

10
00:00:06,220 --> 00:00:41,220
m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

11
00:00:05,720 --> 00:00:41,220
m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

12
00:00:06,220 --> 00:00:11,220
翻譯     showeryhe  Brisingr

13
00:00:11,220 --> 00:00:16,220
翻譯     胖達萌萌噠  瀟然

14
00:00:16,220 --> 00:00:21,220
翻譯     無序腳印  tokilltime

15
00:00:21,220 --> 00:00:26,220
校對     瀟然  胡說大王

16
00:00:26,220 --> 00:00:31,220
時間軸     風吹來的那片云

17
00:00:31,220 --> 00:00:36,220
后期     灰灰是菇涼

18
00:00:36,220 --> 00:00:41,220
總監     showeryhe

19
00:00:00,700 --> 00:00:02,530
聯調局國際反應小組

20
00:00:01,640 --> 00:00:03,390
每年有超過6800萬美國人
Over 68 million Americans

21
00:00:03,390 --> 00:00:05,880
離開安全的國內
leave the safety of our borders every year.

22
00:00:06,050 --> 00:00:07,610
當危險來襲
If danger strikes,

23
00:00:07,840 --> 00:00:10,440
聯調局國際反應小組
the FBI's International Response Team

24
00:00:10,440 --> 00:00:12,010
隨時出動
is called into action.

25
00:00:11,230 --> 00:00:13,740
弗吉尼亞州  匡提科

26
00:00:37,940 --> 00:00:38,960
沒事的
We got you.

27
00:01:20,460 --> 00:01:22,180
杰克·加勒特組長
Unit Chief Jack Garrett,

28
00:01:22,190 --> 00:01:24,200
今天你有權保持沉默
you have the right to remain silent

29
00:01:24,200 --> 00:01:26,230
并拒絕回答問題
and refuse to answer questions today.

30
00:01:26,360 --> 00:01:28,250
如果放棄該權利  那你所說的所有內容
If you give up that right, anything you say

31
00:01:28,250 --> 00:01:30,760
都可以并將用來作為呈堂證供
can and will be used against you in a court of law.

32
00:01:30,980 --> 00:01:32,610
在訊問開始之前及進行過程中
You have the right to consult with an attorney

33
00:01:32,610 --> 00:01:34,730
你都有權找律師咨詢
before and during this questioning.

34
00:01:35,100 --> 00:01:36,660
如果你無力聘請律師
If you cannot afford an attorney...

35
00:01:40,320 --> 00:01:41,230
對不起
I'm sorry.

36
00:01:42,900 --> 00:01:44,570
杰克·加勒特組長  你明白
Unit Chief Garrett, do you understand these rights

37
00:01:44,570 --> 00:01:45,850
我剛才解釋的這些權利了嗎
as I've explained them to you?

38
00:01:47,930 --> 00:01:48,760
明白
Yes.

39
00:01:51,770 --> 00:01:54,300
犯罪心理  國境之外

40
00:01:52,620 --> 00:01:54,300
第二季第九集

41
00:02:29,310 --> 00:02:34,990
要想保守秘密

42
00:02:31,210 --> 00:02:34,990
除非其他知情者都是死人

43
00:02:33,070 --> 00:02:34,990
本杰明·富蘭克林

44
00:02:38,550 --> 00:02:40,800
你現在是否愿意坐下回答我們的問題
Are you willing to sit down now and answer our questions?

45
00:02:42,330 --> 00:02:43,180
是的
Yes.

46
00:02:47,200 --> 00:02:50,110
杰克  你確定不要律師嗎
Jack, are you sure you don't want your lawyer?

47
00:02:50,360 --> 00:02:51,530
可能會來狠的
It could get rough.

48
00:02:52,620 --> 00:02:53,880
我不需要律師
I don't need a lawyer.

49
00:02:54,220 --> 00:02:56,620
請記錄國際反應小組組長杰克·加勒特
Let the record reflect that IRT Unit Chief Jack Garrett

50
00:02:56,620 --> 00:02:58,860
此次放棄咨詢律師的權利
has waived his right to counsel at this time.

51
00:02:58,990 --> 00:03:01,500
此次與會的還有
Let us identify those also present for this session --

52
00:03:01,500 --> 00:03:03,510
來自聯調局職業責任辦公室的
Agents Brian Lynch and Jody Reynolds

53
00:03:03,510 --> 00:03:06,410
布萊恩·林奇和喬迪·雷諾茲探員
with the FBI's Office of Professional Responsibility.

54
00:03:06,680 --> 00:03:09,290
哥倫比亞特區的副法顧賈尼絲·賴切爾
Janice Reichel, Deputy Counsel, District of Columbia,

55
00:03:09,290 --> 00:03:11,320
代表司法部出席
representing the Department of Justice.

56
00:03:11,340 --> 00:03:13,930
國家情報局副主任沃爾特·阿特伍德
Walter Atwood, Deputy Director of National Intelligence,

57
00:03:13,930 --> 00:03:16,700
而我是聯調局國家安全處的執行助理主任
and I am Linda Barnes, Executive Assistant Director

58
00:03:16,700 --> 00:03:18,760
琳達·巴恩斯
of the FBI's National Security Branch.

59
00:03:18,920 --> 00:03:21,240
阿特伍德副主任和我受全權委托
Deputy Director Atwood and I have been authorized

60
00:03:21,240 --> 00:03:23,590
來負責此次聯調局與國情局的聯合訊問
to conduct this joint inquiry for the FBI and DNI.

61
00:03:23,590 --> 00:03:24,990
加勒特組長
Now, Unit Chief Garrett,

62
00:03:24,990 --> 00:03:26,280
你能否從頭開始
can you walk us through the beginnings

63
00:03:26,290 --> 00:03:28,270
說說可吉基斯坦卡利葉
of Case Number 67-16-01

64
00:03:28,270 --> 00:03:30,270
編號67-16-01的案件
in Qalea, Kurjikistan?

65
00:03:30,510 --> 00:03:33,020
我們在里斯本給飛機加燃料
We were refueling in Lisbon,

66
00:03:30,510 --> 00:03:33,020
葡萄牙首都

67
00:03:33,200 --> 00:03:36,250
這時羅素·蒙哥馬利探員通知我們
when Agent Russell Montgomery gave notification

68
00:03:36,250 --> 00:03:39,600
美國大使及可吉基斯坦外交部
about a request from the U.S. Ambassador

69
00:03:39,820 --> 00:03:42,250
要求我們參與協助
and the Kurjikistan Foreign Minister.

70
00:03:42,380 --> 00:03:45,600
是涉及一位美國公民及一位可吉基公民的
It was a double homicide involving a U.S. Citizen

71
00:03:45,600 --> 00:03:47,210
雙尸案
and a Kurjik national.

72
00:03:47,240 --> 00:03:48,550
克麗·洛德爾  二十九歲
Keri Lodel, 29.

73
00:03:48,550 --> 00:03:50,470
是羅得島州普羅維登斯人
She's from Providence, Rhode Island,

74
00:03:50,480 --> 00:03:52,710
她在全球策略開發
and she worked as a network engineer

75
00:03:52,720 --> 00:03:56,490
這家美國承包單位  做網絡工程師
for a U.S. Contractor called Global Strategem Development.

76
00:03:56,490 --> 00:03:57,950
還有阿倫·薩布里
Also, Aron Sabri,

77
00:03:57,950 --> 00:03:59,800
三十二歲  卡利葉人
32, from Qalea.

78
00:03:59,800 --> 00:04:01,820
他在全球策略開發做保安
He worked as a security guard for GSD.

79
00:04:01,830 --> 00:04:04,830
據可吉基國家警察的里法伊長官
Now according to Captain Rifai of the Kurjik National Police,

80
00:04:04,830 --> 00:04:06,980
一位據稱與克麗有染的同事
Keri was stabbed to death by by a co-worker

81
00:04:06,980 --> 00:04:09,110
將她活活捅死
who she was allegedly having an affair with.

82
00:04:09,190 --> 00:04:11,370
那個人叫愛德華·德爾加多
That man's name is Edward Delgado.

83
00:04:11,370 --> 00:04:12,920
德爾加多  四十六歲
Delgado is 46 years old,

84
00:04:12,920 --> 00:04:14,530
是弗吉尼亞州亞歷山德里亞人
from Alexandria, Virginia.

85
00:04:14,540 --> 00:04:15,610
擔任系統分析員
He's a systems analyst,

86
00:04:15,610 --> 00:04:17,480
已婚并育有一個兩歲的女兒
and he's married with a 2-year-old daughter.

87
00:04:17,480 --> 00:04:18,980
當地保安薩布里
Sabri, the local security guard,

88
00:04:18,980 --> 00:04:19,870
似乎在與德爾加多
appears to have died

89
00:04:19,870 --> 00:04:21,340
打斗過程中身亡
during the struggle with Delgado

90
00:04:21,340 --> 00:04:23,740
而德爾加多則趁機逃出居住區
as he fled the GSD housing compound.

91
00:04:23,800 --> 00:04:24,870
看來都發生在
So it looks like all this took place

92
00:04:24,870 --> 00:04:26,520
卡利葉的鋼圈中
inside of Qalea's Steel Ring.

93
00:04:27,080 --> 00:04:28,120
鋼圈
Steel Ring?

94
00:04:28,220 --> 00:04:30,800
是一片六平方千米的嚴守地區
It's a heavily fortified 4-square-mile area

95
00:04:30,800 --> 00:04:32,720
伊拉克首都

96
00:04:30,800 --> 00:04:32,720
類似于巴格達的綠區
much like Baghdad's Green Zone.

97
00:04:33,050 --> 00:04:35,680
杰克  我認識德爾加多
Jack, uh, I know Delgado.

98
00:04:35,710 --> 00:04:36,590
你認識他嗎
You know him?

99
00:04:36,740 --> 00:04:38,310
以前有過接觸
I-I mean, knew him.

100
00:04:38,310 --> 00:04:40,890
曾在緬甸一家非政府組織共事
We used to work together for an NGO in Myanmar.

101
00:04:41,450 --> 00:04:42,410
什么時候的事
When was this?

102
00:04:43,100 --> 00:04:45,400
三年前  我請假離開那段時間
Three years ago when I took my leave of absence.

103
00:04:45,400 --> 00:04:46,810
你對他有什么印象
What do you remember about him?

104
00:04:46,810 --> 00:04:49,310
說實話  我覺得完全說不通
Honestly, this doesn't make any sense to me at all.

105
00:04:49,310 --> 00:04:49,980
我認識的那個人
The man that I knew --

106
00:04:49,980 --> 00:04:51,560
哪怕很生氣  音量也不會提高
he could barely raise his voice in anger,

107
00:04:51,560 --> 00:04:52,890
而別提殺人了
much less escalate to murder.

108
00:04:52,890 --> 00:04:55,230
不止是殺人  他現在可是逃犯
Not only that, he's a fugitive now.

109
00:04:55,750 --> 00:04:58,450
塞格爾探員的工作就是分析
As someone whose job requires her to analyze

110
00:04:58,460 --> 00:05:01,300
并對犯罪嫌疑人給出客觀側寫
and objectively profile the behaviors of criminal suspects,

111
00:05:01,300 --> 00:05:04,250
那她的判斷力難道不是已經受影響了嗎
wasn't Agent Seger's judgment already compromised?

112
00:05:04,250 --> 00:05:05,500
完全沒有
No, not at all.

113
00:05:05,820 --> 00:05:06,920
完全沒有
Not at all?

114
00:05:07,640 --> 00:05:10,290
塞格爾探員和德爾加多以前的接觸
You don't believe Agent Seger's history with Mr. Delgado

115
00:05:10,300 --> 00:05:13,140
你認為不會以任何方式影響她的能力
could have in any way impacted her ability to --

116
00:05:13,140 --> 00:05:15,490
不  我不認為  正如我不相信
No, I don't, just like I don't believe

117
00:05:15,500 --> 00:05:18,310
阿特伍德副主任和我的老交情
that Deputy Director Atwood's longtime friendship with me

118
00:05:18,310 --> 00:05:20,600
可能影響他在本次訊問過程中
is going to impact his ability to be objective

119
00:05:20,600 --> 00:05:22,060
保持客觀公正的能力
during this inquiry.

120
00:05:24,630 --> 00:05:26,310
塞格爾探員有沒有向你
Did Agent Seger disclose to you

121
00:05:26,310 --> 00:05:27,530
或團隊中其他成員
or to any other member of your team

122
00:05:27,530 --> 00:05:30,410
完全交代她過去和德爾加多先生的關系
the full extent of her prior relationship with Mr. Delgado?

123
00:05:30,420 --> 00:05:33,730
塞格爾探員坦言三年前
Agent Seger disclosed that she previously worked with him

124
00:05:33,730 --> 00:05:35,470
他們曾在緬甸共事
in Myanmar three years ago.

125
00:05:35,470 --> 00:05:36,490
她沒有剛好提及
She didn't happen to mention

126
00:05:36,500 --> 00:05:38,660
和這個男人的私人關系嗎
her personal relationship with this man?

127
00:05:40,000 --> 00:05:44,670
她沒有提及  但這不重要  因為
No. She didn't mention it, but doesn't matter because --

128
00:05:44,670 --> 00:05:47,660
重要的是你對團隊成員的了解程度
What matters is how well you know the members of your team.

129
00:05:47,740 --> 00:05:50,870
毫無疑問訊問過程中這一塊十分重要
No doubt this line of questioning is important,

130
00:05:50,870 --> 00:05:52,410
但我們先跳過吧
but let me jump ahead.

131
00:05:52,420 --> 00:05:56,010
你們登陸該國后  說說有什么流程
When you landed in country, run us through the protocol.

132
00:05:56,060 --> 00:05:58,870
我們到達卡利葉后就開始
When we landed in Qalea, we began coordinating

133
00:05:58,870 --> 00:06:01,340
和巴希爾·里法伊長官協作
with Captain Basir Rifai,

134
00:06:01,340 --> 00:06:03,580
他是可吉基國家警察的負責人
head of the Kurjik National Police.

135
00:06:03,600 --> 00:06:04,350
可惜
Unfortunately,

136
00:06:04,350 --> 00:06:06,090
我手下對逃犯愛德華·德爾加多的追捕
my men have made little progress in our hunt for the fugitive,

137
00:06:06,090 --> 00:06:08,310
一無所獲
Edward Delgado.

138
00:06:08,310 --> 00:06:11,340
我們傾向于認為他或許已經逃出了鋼圈
We are beginning to believe he may have escaped the Steel Ring

139
00:06:11,340 --> 00:06:13,420
也可能已經死了
and may in fact be already dead.

140
00:06:14,060 --> 00:06:15,790
因為他作為一個在逃的西方人
Because as a westerner on the run,

141
00:06:15,790 --> 00:06:17,270
他可能輕易地落入
he could've easily fallen into the hands

142
00:06:17,270 --> 00:06:19,250
好戰組織  信念兄弟會手中
of the militant group, the Brotherhood of Faith.

143
00:06:19,250 --> 00:06:22,260
沒錯  禍害我國的恐怖組織之一
Yes, one of many terror groups that plague my country.

144
00:06:22,260 --> 00:06:23,160
只有這一個
Only this one was led

145
00:06:23,160 --> 00:06:26,190
是由你們前將軍之一拉尚·努里領導的
by one of your former army generals, Rashan Noori.

146
00:06:26,190 --> 00:06:28,730
是的  給我們造成了更深的傷害
Indeed. An even deeper wound for us.

147
00:06:28,730 --> 00:06:30,460
但德爾加多是個非常聰明的人  對吧
But Delgado's a pretty smart guy, right?

148
00:06:30,460 --> 00:06:32,230
你覺得他是否會在安全區外鋌而走險呢
So you think if he's really gonna roll the dice

149
00:06:32,230 --> 00:06:34,310
唯一讓他敢這么做的原因
outside the Ring, he's only gonna do it

150
00:06:34,310 --> 00:06:35,980
就是他確切知道哪里可以讓他躲藏
if he knows exactly where he's gonna be able to hide

151
00:06:35,980 --> 00:06:36,680
一小段時間
for a little bit.

152
00:06:36,680 --> 00:06:39,950
也許賈維斯探員是對的  但以我的經驗
You may be right, Agent Jarvis, but in my experience,

153
00:06:40,680 --> 00:06:44,240
窮途之人總會做出極端的決定
the desperate man always makes the desperate choice.

154
00:06:45,200 --> 00:06:48,360
現在我和塞格爾探員要檢視案發現場了
Well, right now Agent Seger and I should inspect the crime scene

155
00:06:48,360 --> 00:06:50,880
西蒙斯探員會去推測嫌疑人
while Agent Simmons here evaluates our suspect's

156
00:06:50,880 --> 00:06:53,740
從居住區逃跑后的潛在路線
possible escape routes from the housing compound.

157
00:06:53,740 --> 00:06:54,700
好的  沒問題
Yes, of course.

158
00:06:54,700 --> 00:06:58,190
我還需要將克麗·洛德爾和阿倫·薩布里的
I'd also like the bodies of Keri Lodel and Aron Sabri

159
00:06:58,190 --> 00:07:00,030
尸體運回  以便賈維斯探員
brought back here so Agent Jarvis

160
00:07:00,030 --> 00:07:02,520
能進行補充尸檢
can conduct supplemental autopsies.

161
00:07:02,560 --> 00:07:04,400
我會安排調度的
I'll arrange for the transfer.

162
00:07:04,990 --> 00:07:07,400
組長  你之前提到的
Unit Chief, earlier you mentioned,

163
00:07:07,410 --> 00:07:10,160
如果沒記錯  那個可吉基的外交部長
if I'm not mistaken, that the Kurjik Foreign Minister

164
00:07:10,160 --> 00:07:12,370
就是請國際反應小組來協助
was one of the folks who had asked for

165
00:07:12,370 --> 00:07:14,750
這起案件的人之一  對吧
the IRT's help in this matter. Is that right?

166
00:07:14,760 --> 00:07:15,680
是的  沒錯
Yes, that's right.

167
00:07:15,680 --> 00:07:17,520
你是否
Did you or did you not

168
00:07:17,520 --> 00:07:20,870
承認并且尊重當地政府  里法伊長官
acknowledge and respect the lead investigative role

169
00:07:20,870 --> 00:07:23,380
在此次調查中的主導地位呢
of the local authority, Captain Rifai?

170
00:07:23,990 --> 00:07:28,160
副主任  國際反應小組的職責一直都是
Deputy Director, the IRT's role, as always,

171
00:07:28,160 --> 00:07:30,900
在此雙尸案的調查中
was to advise and assist Captain Rifai and the KNP

172
00:07:30,900 --> 00:07:33,960
為里法伊長官和國家警察提供建議和協助
during the course of this double homicide investigation

173
00:07:33,960 --> 00:07:36,980
并且追捕在逃的愛德華·德爾加多
and the pursuit of the fugitive, Edward Delgado.

174
00:07:36,980 --> 00:07:40,190
現在許多建議和協助
Now much of that advice and assistance

175
00:07:40,200 --> 00:07:41,680
都是基于你們團隊
comes from your team's ability

176
00:07:41,680 --> 00:07:45,240
建立的犯罪嫌疑人的行為側寫
to build these behavioral profiles of criminal suspects.

177
00:07:45,240 --> 00:07:46,790
-是嗎  -沒錯
- Is that right? - Yes.

178
00:07:46,970 --> 00:07:50,400
巴恩斯助理主任指出過
And as Assistant Director Barnes has pointed out,

179
00:07:50,400 --> 00:07:52,550
塞格爾探員熟悉這位
Agent Seger was familiar with --

180
00:07:53,000 --> 00:07:55,010
或者說過分熟悉這位
perhaps a bit too familiar with

181
00:07:55,030 --> 00:07:58,180
特殊人物  德爾加多先生
the particular subject, Mr. Delgado.

182
00:07:58,180 --> 00:08:00,520
塞格爾探員在調查中并未表現出
Agent Seger demonstrated no bias

183
00:08:00,520 --> 00:08:01,780
任何偏袒
during this investigation.

184
00:08:01,790 --> 00:08:05,470
事實上  她對德爾加多過去行為的了解
In fact, her awareness of Mr. Delgado's actions in the past

185
00:08:05,710 --> 00:08:08,550
只是幫我們更深入地研究在克麗·洛德爾
only helped to contextualize the evidence we found

186
00:08:08,550 --> 00:08:10,310
死亡現場發現的證據
at Keri Lodel's crime scene.

187
00:08:18,500 --> 00:08:20,620
全球策略開發不是來幫你們部門
Isn't GSD helping to update

188
00:08:20,620 --> 00:08:22,540
提升技術安全的嗎
your department's technical security?

189
00:08:22,540 --> 00:08:25,660
是的  我們的一些工作人員認識受害者
It is. Some of my officers knew the victim

190
00:08:25,960 --> 00:08:27,690
還有德爾加多先生
as well as Mr. Delgado.

191
00:08:27,900 --> 00:08:29,920
他們有見過這兩人公開在一起活動嗎
Did they ever see the two of them out together socially?

192
00:08:29,920 --> 00:08:30,670
沒有
No.

193
00:08:32,110 --> 00:08:34,750
但你的理論不是情侶爭吵然后惡性發展嗎
But your theory is a lover's quarrel gone horribly wrong.

194
00:08:34,750 --> 00:08:37,620
在保安截堵到德爾加多前
Before the security guard confronted Mr. Delgado,

195
00:08:37,620 --> 00:08:38,900
他還曾用無線電請求增援
he radioed for help.

196
00:08:38,900 --> 00:08:42,630
那時是凌晨兩點  他聽見屋里有尖叫聲
It was 2 a.m., and he'd heard screams from this apartment.

197
00:08:42,630 --> 00:08:44,550
隨后他就從這里追著嫌疑人
He then pursued the suspect from here

198
00:08:44,550 --> 00:08:47,180
然后將他逼到了走廊盡頭的陽臺
and confronted him on the balcony at the end of the hall,

199
00:08:47,510 --> 00:08:50,150
但德爾加多打倒了他
but Mr. Delgado got the better of him.

200
00:08:50,150 --> 00:08:51,930
這也不能說明這兩人之間
That doesn't confirm an intimate relationship

201
00:08:51,930 --> 00:08:53,700
-有親密關系  -我同意
- between the two of them. - No, I agree.

202
00:08:53,700 --> 00:08:57,430
這更可能像是一次性騷擾
It more strongly confirms a probable sexual assault

203
00:08:57,560 --> 00:08:59,330
隨后升級成了謀殺
that escalated to murder.

204
00:08:59,460 --> 00:09:01,890
看看這狂怒的痕跡
Just all this rage.

205
00:09:02,280 --> 00:09:05,380
對  過度殺戮  因為一些個人原因
Yeah, it's overkill. Something personal.

206
00:09:08,160 --> 00:09:09,090
你發現什么了嗎  梅
What do you got, Mae?

207
00:09:09,270 --> 00:09:12,460
我發現克麗的毒檢結果非常奇怪
What I got is something weird in Keri's tox panel.

208
00:09:12,460 --> 00:09:14,590
她體內有鎮靜劑
So she has Lorazepam in her system

209
00:09:14,590 --> 00:09:16,700
但沒有任何醫生給她開過這種藥
even though she does not have a prescription for it,

210
00:09:16,700 --> 00:09:18,490
并且藥量非常之高
and the amount of the drug is so high,

211
00:09:18,490 --> 00:09:20,060
她像是被迫注射了鎮定劑
it's like she's been sedated.

212
00:09:20,060 --> 00:09:23,290
此外  克麗身上沒有任何防衛傷痕
And on top of that, Keri has no defensive wounds on her.

213
00:09:23,290 --> 00:09:24,950
所以你認為克麗被下藥了
So you think keri was drugged,

214
00:09:24,950 --> 00:09:26,200
然后被刺死
and then she was stabbed to death.

215
00:09:26,200 --> 00:09:28,120
從我的角度看是這樣的
I mean, that's what it's looking like to me.

216
00:09:28,120 --> 00:09:30,720
那第二個受害者  阿倫·薩布里呢
What about the second victim, Aron Sabri?

217
00:09:30,730 --> 00:09:32,770
死因是鈍力損傷
Well, the COD is blunt force trauma,

218
00:09:32,770 --> 00:09:35,050
與被拋下陽臺的說法一致
which is consistent with being tossed off a balcony,

219
00:09:35,050 --> 00:09:36,490
但遺憾的是
but unfortunately,

220
00:09:36,490 --> 00:09:38,120
死后損傷讓我很難確認
the post-mortem injuries are making it

221
00:09:38,120 --> 00:09:40,390
哪些傷痕是因為受害者
really difficult for me to confirm the extent

222
00:09:40,390 --> 00:09:42,230
與嫌疑人搏斗留下的
of the struggle with the suspect,

223
00:09:42,380 --> 00:09:46,840
并且我還不清楚他的手上為什么會有擦傷
and I'm also really puzzled by the abrasions on his hands.

224
00:09:44,430 --> 00:09:47,180
尸檢報告  阿倫·薩布里

225
00:09:46,840 --> 00:09:48,990
這就是我了解到的
But, I mean, it is what it is.

226
00:09:48,990 --> 00:09:50,270
謝謝  梅
Okay, thanks, Mae.

227
00:09:50,320 --> 00:09:52,970
杰克  這里沒有什么能確認或否認
Jack, there is nothing here to confirm or deny

228
00:09:52,970 --> 00:09:54,860
這兩人之間存在親密關系
an intimate relationship between these two.

229
00:09:54,860 --> 00:09:56,430
也無法證明他們之間
And there's certainly nothing to tell why

230
00:09:56,430 --> 00:09:58,090
到底有過怎樣的關系
whatever relationship they did have

231
00:09:58,090 --> 00:09:59,980
能造成這樣凄慘的變故
took such a tragic turn.

232
00:10:00,110 --> 00:10:02,320
也許他的房間能給我們更多信息
Maybe his room will tell us more.

233
00:10:02,520 --> 00:10:04,690
可能吧  但我認為需要對克麗·洛德爾
Maybe, but I really think we need to conduct

234
00:10:04,690 --> 00:10:06,860
進行更深入的受害者分析
a deeper victimology of Keri Lodel.

235
00:10:06,880 --> 00:10:08,160
你看看她的紀念物
If you look at her mementos,

236
00:10:08,160 --> 00:10:10,930
她顯然在不同的人中都很受歡迎
she's obviously very popular with lots of different people,

237
00:10:10,930 --> 00:10:12,400
他們中的任何人都能對她
any one of whom could have developed

238
00:10:12,400 --> 00:10:14,160
發展出扭曲的渴慕之情
some twisted sense of an attachment

239
00:10:14,160 --> 00:10:16,130
從而激發出這場暴力案件
that would have motivated this violence.

240
00:10:16,210 --> 00:10:19,220
讓蒙蒂跟進下
Okay. We'll have Monty follow up.

241
00:10:20,440 --> 00:10:22,740
這么說  你們調查的下一步行動
So to be clear, the next step in your investigation

242
00:10:22,740 --> 00:10:24,650
是根據塞格爾探員的建議來的
was based on Agent Seger's recommendation?

243
00:10:24,650 --> 00:10:28,810
不  進行受害者分析是我們側寫的一步
No. Conducting a victimology is part of our profile building.

244
00:10:28,810 --> 00:10:31,620
但根據你的描述  塞格爾探員說
But you just described how Agent Seger said

245
00:10:31,620 --> 00:10:34,200
深入的受害者分析能讓德爾加多洗掉嫌疑
a deeper victimology would help you move off Delgado.

246
00:10:34,200 --> 00:10:35,970
我才沒這么說  你一直都在
That's not what I said, and you keep trying

247
00:10:35,980 --> 00:10:37,290
扭曲我說過的話
to twist my words like that.

248
00:10:37,290 --> 00:10:38,330
我只想確認清楚
I'm only trying to clarify.

249
00:10:38,330 --> 00:10:39,910
你在有意整我們小組
You're trying to hang the IRT.

250
00:10:39,910 --> 00:10:41,300
你就是這么做的
That's what you're trying to do here.

251
00:10:41,300 --> 00:10:43,780
-可能我們該休息一下  -我認為不用
- Perhaps it's time we took a break. - I think we're fine.

252
00:10:43,780 --> 00:10:46,650
-我覺得需要休息了  -阿倫和克麗
- I think we're taking a break. - Aron Sabri and Keri Lodel

253
00:10:46,650 --> 00:10:49,210
不是這起案件僅有的受害人
are not the only victims of this case.

254
00:10:49,340 --> 00:10:51,800
一位平民嫌犯也死了
A civilian suspect lost his life

255
00:10:51,800 --> 00:10:54,650
就是因為國際反應小組的莽撞行為
because of the IRT's reckless actions.

256
00:10:55,140 --> 00:10:56,970
你認為我有意整國際反應小組
You think I want to hang the IRT?

257
00:10:57,750 --> 00:11:00,520
杰克·加勒特組長  我就跟你明說吧
Unit Chief Garrett, let me be crystal clear with you.

258
00:11:00,820 --> 00:11:02,120
等今天工作完成了
When we are all done here today,

259
00:11:02,120 --> 00:11:04,540
我會動用全部力量將國際反應小組
I will have everything I need to shatter the IRT

260
00:11:04,540 --> 00:11:06,020
徹底粉碎
into a thousand pieces

261
00:11:06,020 --> 00:11:08,150
并將灰燼四散入風
and scatter the remnants to the wind.

262
00:11:19,340 --> 00:11:22,930
其實可以  更好一點
Well, that could have gone... better.

263
00:11:23,860 --> 00:11:27,260
-進展挺順利  -因為你并不認為
- It's going fine. - Mm, 'cause you don't think

264
00:11:27,270 --> 00:11:30,450
那樣自揭底牌后  會很難證明
it's hard to prove bias when you lay your own cards

265
00:11:30,450 --> 00:11:32,160
存在偏見
out on the table like that?

266
00:11:32,560 --> 00:11:34,210
你應該輕聲而動
You need to tread lightly.

267
00:11:34,240 --> 00:11:35,270
是那樣嗎
Is that so?

268
00:11:35,270 --> 00:11:37,900
是的  這不僅是訊問
Yes, it is. This isn't just an inquiry.

269
00:11:37,900 --> 00:11:40,180
還是政治棋局
This is a political game of chess.

270
00:11:40,640 --> 00:11:41,600
你喜歡下棋嗎
You like chess?

271
00:11:42,010 --> 00:11:43,280
我喜歡拳擊
I like boxing.

272
00:11:43,780 --> 00:11:47,470
看出來了  我就很喜歡下棋
I see that. Now I love chess myself.

273
00:11:47,520 --> 00:11:51,300
需要沉得住氣  擅用策略
Requires patience and understanding strategy

274
00:11:51,300 --> 00:11:53,070
懂得人性的弱點
and of human weakness.

275
00:11:53,070 --> 00:11:55,670
再說總能驅王使后
Plus you always get to be king.

276
00:11:55,890 --> 00:11:57,410
我對你的打氣鼓勁并非不感激
Not that I don't appreciate the pep talk,

277
00:11:57,410 --> 00:11:58,720
但我不想要
but I don't.

278
00:11:58,720 --> 00:12:01,550
冷靜  我是想保護你
Settle down. I'm trying to protect you,

279
00:12:01,550 --> 00:12:04,560
而且如果你真的想實現公正
and if you really wanna see justice done,

280
00:12:04,560 --> 00:12:07,590
你要收集也只收集事實
you will gather the facts -- just the facts,

281
00:12:07,700 --> 00:12:10,260
剩下的就交給當權者
and let the powers that be do the rest.

282
00:12:29,030 --> 00:12:29,970
不用我提醒你
I shouldn't have to remind you

283
00:12:29,970 --> 00:12:32,160
房里沒人被捕吧
that no one in this room is under arrest.

284
00:12:32,160 --> 00:12:33,170
所以如果不介意
So if you don't mind,

285
00:12:33,170 --> 00:12:35,360
我要活動下腿腳  倒杯咖啡
I'm gonna go stretch my legs and get some coffee.

286
00:12:38,530 --> 00:12:39,580
誰有想要的嗎
Anybody want anything?

287
00:12:40,500 --> 00:12:41,920
太荒謬了
This is ridiculous.

288
00:12:42,650 --> 00:12:44,830
我想現在最好還是
Look, I think it's best if we avoid sharing

289
00:12:45,100 --> 00:12:46,070
不要交流
for the time being.

290
00:12:46,170 --> 00:12:47,510
他們在房間裝了竊聽器嗎
You think they wired the room?

291
00:12:47,960 --> 00:12:49,450
為什么要裝竊聽器呢
Why would they wire the room?

292
00:12:50,470 --> 00:12:52,950
因為盡管我們并沒有被捕
Because while we are not actually under arrest,

293
00:12:52,950 --> 00:12:55,260
但我們相互之間禁止討論
we're prohibited from discussing anything that has to do

294
00:12:55,260 --> 00:12:56,820
任何本案相關的事
with the case with each other.

295
00:12:56,820 --> 00:12:58,760
難以置信  我們能有什么打算
Unbelievable. What do they think that we're gonna do,

296
00:12:58,760 --> 00:13:00,610
坐在這兒合伙編故事嗎
sit in here and try to line our stories up?

297
00:13:00,610 --> 00:13:02,350
這正是他們的想法
That's exactly what they think,

298
00:13:02,350 --> 00:13:04,450
即使只是串供的表現
and even the mere appearance of collusion

299
00:13:04,450 --> 00:13:06,930
也可能導致停工  甚至是起訴
is cause for termination if not straight up prosecution.

300
00:13:14,730 --> 00:13:17,450
那么  凱倫和孩子們怎么樣
So... how are Karen and the kids?

301
00:13:17,450 --> 00:13:19,660
得了吧  別說廢話
Oh, come on, Walt. Cut the crap.

302
00:13:19,810 --> 00:13:22,700
抱歉  伙計  真是粗暴
I'm sorry, man. This is tough.

303
00:13:23,020 --> 00:13:25,050
但你要記住  有我支持你
But I want you to know I got your back.

304
00:13:25,060 --> 00:13:26,910
不需要你支持
I don't need you to have my back.

305
00:13:27,260 --> 00:13:29,360
杰克  你自己也聽到那女人的話了
Jack, you heard the woman yourself.

306
00:13:29,360 --> 00:13:32,290
關鍵不在于誰對誰錯
This is not about who is right or who is wrong.

307
00:13:32,510 --> 00:13:34,200
而是誰來擔罪
This is about who's to blame.

308
00:13:34,210 --> 00:13:36,650
沃爾特  我們所有行動都是照規定來的
Walt, we did everything by the book.

309
00:13:36,650 --> 00:13:40,090
我知道  杰克  但有人死了
I know you did, Jack, but we got a body count.

310
00:13:40,090 --> 00:13:43,900
所以不管有沒有照規定來  有人犯了錯
So book or no book, somebody screwed the pooch.

311
00:13:43,900 --> 00:13:46,080
我只希望那個人不是你
I just don't want that somebody to be you.

312
00:13:48,000 --> 00:13:49,490
對我的訊問還沒結束
You're not done with me yet.

313
00:13:49,740 --> 00:13:50,960
還沒有
No, we're not.

314
00:13:51,070 --> 00:13:54,180
但你和巴恩斯需要中場休息
But you and Barnes needed a time-out,

315
00:13:54,180 --> 00:13:56,380
所以  失陪
so...excuse me.

316
00:14:02,930 --> 00:14:05,950
塞格爾探員  三年前你曾請假
Agent Seger, three years ago, you took a leave of absence.

317
00:14:06,800 --> 00:14:08,750
-沒錯  -為什么
- Yes, I did. - Why?

318
00:14:10,350 --> 00:14:12,250
-為什么  -沒錯  那是個問題
- Why? - Yes, that's the question.

319
00:14:13,310 --> 00:14:14,590
我恐怕不明白你的意思
I'm not sure that I understand.

320
00:14:14,590 --> 00:14:17,520
你面前就是我的個人檔案
You have my personal file sitting right in front of you.

321
00:14:17,520 --> 00:14:19,860
你十分清楚我告假的原因
You know exactly why I took the time off.

322
00:14:20,740 --> 00:14:22,080
沒錯  我確實知道
Yes, I do know why.

323
00:14:22,870 --> 00:14:26,320
真可惜  我想自己這些審訊員的花招
Unfortunately, I suspect some of my tricks as an interrogator

324
00:14:26,320 --> 00:14:29,940
在你這種法醫心理學專家面前
are going to be transparent to an expert in forensic psychology

325
00:14:29,940 --> 00:14:31,510
根本玩不起來  是吧
such as yourself, am I right?

326
00:14:31,510 --> 00:14:33,400
請你一定要包容
I'd only ask your indulgence.

327
00:14:34,130 --> 00:14:36,110
或者你也可以選擇不回答該問題
Or you can choose to not answer the question,

328
00:14:36,180 --> 00:14:38,370
但那可能透露出你的心智狀況
but that might suggest something about your state of mind,

329
00:14:38,380 --> 00:14:39,160
你說呢
don't you think?

330
00:14:40,280 --> 00:14:43,540
你想玩游戲  我奉陪
You want to play games? I can play your game.

331
00:14:44,660 --> 00:14:45,860
三年前
Three years ago,

332
00:14:46,260 --> 00:14:49,820
我丈夫  特別督察探員布拉德·塞格爾
my husband, SSA Brad Seger --

333
00:14:49,900 --> 00:14:52,480
在執行公務時被害
he was killed in the line of duty,

334
00:14:53,520 --> 00:14:56,970
我因為喪夫而告假
and I took a leave of absence for bereavement.

335
00:14:59,740 --> 00:15:02,110
節哀順變
I'm very sorry for your loss.

336
00:15:03,310 --> 00:15:04,170
謝謝
Thank you.

337
00:15:05,720 --> 00:15:08,110
因喪夫休假期間  你去往世界各地
During your bereavement leave, you traveled extensively,

338
00:15:08,110 --> 00:15:10,860
但我想集中于三年前
but I'd like to focus on the time you spent in Myanmar

339
00:15:10,860 --> 00:15:12,760
你在緬甸那段
three years ago, during which time

340
00:15:12,760 --> 00:15:17,320
當時你和愛德華·德爾加多十分熟絡
you became...quite familiar with Edward Delgado,

341
00:15:17,320 --> 00:15:18,780
該男子后來也成為
the man who would later become

342
00:15:18,780 --> 00:15:20,620
卡利葉調查中的重點
the focus of the investigation in Qalea

343
00:15:20,620 --> 00:15:22,810
而他和你的復雜關系
and the man whose complicated connection to you

344
00:15:22,810 --> 00:15:24,990
-使貴團隊產生偏見  -這么說不對
- would prejudice your team. - That is not true.

345
00:15:25,160 --> 00:15:27,490
盡管我個人了解德爾加多
Regardless of my personal knowledge of Delgado,

346
00:15:27,500 --> 00:15:30,370
但我們團隊仍不含偏見將此人視為逃犯
my team, without prejudice, pursued this man as a fugitive

347
00:15:30,380 --> 00:15:31,160
進行追捕
from the law.

348
00:15:31,160 --> 00:15:33,910
而且蒙哥馬利探員還聯系了他的妻子
In fact, it was Agent Montgomery who reached out to his wife

349
00:15:33,910 --> 00:15:36,660
來多加了解他可能的逃亡去向
to get a better understanding of where he might seek refuge.

350
00:15:41,250 --> 00:15:44,740
蒙哥馬利探員  過去二十四小時
Agent Montgomery, I haven't been able to get ahold

351
00:15:44,740 --> 00:15:46,640
我都聯系不上我丈夫
of my husband in 24 hours.

352
00:15:46,640 --> 00:15:49,970
-德爾加多夫人  -請叫我阿米莉婭
- Mrs. Delgado -- - Please call me Amelia.

353
00:15:50,370 --> 00:15:52,150
阿米莉婭  請坐
Amelia, please.

354
00:15:56,640 --> 00:15:59,030
全球戰略開發的居住區發了生意外事件
There was an incident at the GSD housing compound.

355
00:15:59,030 --> 00:16:00,290
有兩人被害
Two people were killed.

356
00:16:00,290 --> 00:16:03,110
一位是你丈夫的女同事克麗·洛德爾
One was a woman who worked with your husband named Keri Lodel.

357
00:16:03,110 --> 00:16:06,440
另一位是叫阿倫·薩布里的保安
The other was a security guard named Aron Sabri.

358
00:16:08,760 --> 00:16:10,470
你丈夫也失蹤了
Your husband is also missing.

359
00:16:10,900 --> 00:16:11,670
失蹤
Missing?

360
00:16:13,000 --> 00:16:14,260
什么意思  失蹤
What do you mean, missing?

361
00:16:14,470 --> 00:16:15,640
阿米莉婭  你最近一次
Amelia, when was the last time

362
00:16:15,640 --> 00:16:17,090
和丈夫聯系是什么時候
you communicated with your husband?

363
00:16:17,090 --> 00:16:19,520
他昨天早上給我發了電子郵件
He E-mailed me yesterday morning.

364
00:16:19,590 --> 00:16:20,550
說了什么
What did he say?

365
00:16:20,550 --> 00:16:22,550
沒什么  只是幾張照片
Nothing. He just sent me photos.

366
00:16:22,550 --> 00:16:23,520
能給我看看嗎
May I see them?

367
00:16:34,100 --> 00:16:35,920
他在國外的時候
How often did the two of you communicate

368
00:16:35,920 --> 00:16:37,480
你們倆多久聯系一次
while he was overseas?

369
00:16:38,180 --> 00:16:40,180
每周一次  主要通過郵件
Once a week, mainly by e-mail.

370
00:16:40,640 --> 00:16:44,260
一定很難熬  對你們倆來說
Must have been tough... for both of you.

371
00:16:45,510 --> 00:16:47,830
我為什么感覺你真正想問的是
Why do I get the feeling that what you really wanna ask me

372
00:16:47,830 --> 00:16:50,390
我有沒有覺得丈夫跟克麗有染
is if I think my husband was sleeping with Keri.

373
00:16:52,510 --> 00:16:53,350
有這個可能嗎
Is it possible?

374
00:16:53,350 --> 00:16:55,450
不  沒可能
No, it isn't.

375
00:16:56,140 --> 00:16:58,790
他發照片給我以便我認識他的朋友
He sent me those photos so that I could see his friends,

376
00:16:58,790 --> 00:16:59,590
僅此而已
that's all.

377
00:17:00,940 --> 00:17:01,640
好吧
Okay.

378
00:17:02,920 --> 00:17:05,610
那你丈夫最近有承受不同尋常的壓力嗎
Well, was your husband under any unusual stress lately?

379
00:17:06,120 --> 00:17:08,040
沒  據我所知沒有
No, not that I know of.

380
00:17:08,570 --> 00:17:11,320
他是個好人  他跟所有人都相處融洽
He's a good man. He gets along with everyone.

381
00:17:12,550 --> 00:17:16,380
我發誓  他絕對不會傷害任何人
I swear, he'd never hurt anyone.

382
00:17:17,420 --> 00:17:18,770
德爾加多的妻子給了我權限
Delgado's wife gave me access

383
00:17:18,770 --> 00:17:20,000
登入她丈夫的社交媒體
to all of her husband's social media,

384
00:17:20,000 --> 00:17:22,000
我正在檢查當中  但老實說
and I'm going through it now, but I gotta be honest,

385
00:17:22,000 --> 00:17:24,090
阿米莉婭似乎非常了解她的丈夫
Amelia seemed to know her husband really well.

386
00:17:24,090 --> 00:17:26,000
所以如果他跟克麗沒有婚外情
So if he wasn't having an affair with Keri,

387
00:17:26,000 --> 00:17:27,690
那他的殺人動機是什么呢
then what would be his motive to kill her?

388
00:17:27,740 --> 00:17:29,360
要是德爾加多沒有殺害克麗
Well, if Delgado didn't kill Keri,

389
00:17:29,360 --> 00:17:30,640
那他為什么襲擊保安
then why does he attack the guard?

390
00:17:30,640 --> 00:17:31,740
他為什么逃跑
And why does he run?

391
00:17:31,740 --> 00:17:33,980
這帶來了一個更加迫切的問題
Which brings us to our more pressing question --

392
00:17:33,980 --> 00:17:36,260
愛德華·德爾加多到底在哪里
where is Edward Delgado?

393
00:17:36,420 --> 00:17:39,420
聽著  不管犯罪與否  他并非慣犯
Listen, guilty or not, he's not some hardened criminal.

394
00:17:39,420 --> 00:17:41,000
他人生地不熟
He is a stranger in a strange land,

395
00:17:41,010 --> 00:17:42,640
就像梅之前說的
and it's like Mae said before.

396
00:17:42,640 --> 00:17:44,940
如果他能夠逃出鋼圈
If he did manage to sneak out of the Steel Ring,

397
00:17:44,940 --> 00:17:46,940
是因為他知道在另一邊
it's because he knows someone on the other side

398
00:17:46,940 --> 00:17:48,170
也許有人能保護他
who might protect him.

399
00:17:48,860 --> 00:17:50,430
我好像有發現
I may have found something.

400
00:17:50,430 --> 00:17:52,320
德爾加多似乎跟
Looks like Delgado got pretty close

401
00:17:52,320 --> 00:17:54,370
他第一位翻譯的家人很親近
to the family of his first interpreter.

402
00:17:54,410 --> 00:17:56,590
年輕人名叫奧馬爾·塔汗
Young man's name is Omar Tahan.

403
00:17:55,330 --> 00:17:57,400
全球策略開發  奧馬爾·塔汗  翻譯

404
00:17:56,670 --> 00:17:58,090
抱歉  塞格爾探員
I apologize, Agent Seger.

405
00:17:58,090 --> 00:17:59,660
那個年輕人叫什么名字
What was the young man's name again?

406
00:17:59,660 --> 00:18:00,490
奧馬爾·塔汗
Omar Tahan.

407
00:18:00,840 --> 00:18:03,250
他給德爾加多當了兩周翻譯
He was Delgado's translator for two weeks

408
00:18:03,250 --> 00:18:04,280
直到把職責交給了
until those duties were transferred to

409
00:18:04,280 --> 00:18:06,080
可吉基國家警察的一名警官
an officer from the KNP.

410
00:18:06,080 --> 00:18:08,000
為什么移交工作呢
And why were those duties transferred?

411
00:18:08,000 --> 00:18:09,320
德爾加多的工作使他
Delgado's work exposed him

412
00:18:09,320 --> 00:18:11,800
接觸到可吉基國家警察的保密通訊
to confidential KNP communications,

413
00:18:11,800 --> 00:18:15,480
而塔汗先生沒有得到權限
and Mr. Tahan would have not been permitted access.

414
00:18:15,650 --> 00:18:17,780
你們確認了塔汗先生的身份后
Once you identified Mr. Tahan,

415
00:18:17,780 --> 00:18:19,670
你和你的團隊接著做了什么
what did you or your team do next?

416
00:18:19,670 --> 00:18:21,540
我們前往塔汗的家
We drove out to the Tahan house.

417
00:18:21,540 --> 00:18:24,900
距離鋼圈西北方一千六百米的地方
It was located 1 mile northwest of the Steel Ring,

418
00:18:24,900 --> 00:18:27,540
我們發現德爾加多先生就躲在了那里
and that's where we discovered Mr. Delgado hiding out.

419
00:18:27,720 --> 00:18:29,190
他有反抗嗎
Did he offer any resistance?

420
00:18:29,190 --> 00:18:32,440
不  他沒有  他毫無抵抗地接受拘留
No, he did not. He came into custody without incident.

421
00:18:32,440 --> 00:18:34,670
塞格爾探員  是誰決定
Agent Seger, whose decision was it

422
00:18:34,670 --> 00:18:36,260
把愛德華·德爾加多轉移
to transport Edward Delgado

423
00:18:36,260 --> 00:18:37,700
回國際反應小組的飛機
back to the IRT jet

424
00:18:37,700 --> 00:18:40,990
而非直接把他帶給可吉基國家警察拘留呢
rather than transfer him immediately into KNP custody?

425
00:18:40,990 --> 00:18:43,190
那是加勒特組長的決定
That was Unit Chief Garrett's decision.

426
00:18:43,190 --> 00:18:46,720
你記得自己質疑過那個決定嗎
And do you recall if you perhaps challenged that decision?

427
00:18:46,870 --> 00:18:48,980
-不  -你不記得  還是...
- No. - No, you don't recall, or...

428
00:18:48,980 --> 00:18:51,780
-不  我沒有質疑  -你支持嗎
- No, I did not challenge it. - Did you encourage it?

429
00:18:52,100 --> 00:18:53,700
聽著  當時德爾加多是
Look, at this point, Delgado was a suspect

430
00:18:53,700 --> 00:18:55,330
國際反應小組和可吉基國家警察
in a joint task force investigation

431
00:18:55,330 --> 00:18:57,490
聯合調查中的疑犯
between the IRT and the KNP.

432
00:18:57,490 --> 00:18:59,630
加勒特組長有權
It was well within Unit Chief Garrett's purview

433
00:18:59,630 --> 00:19:01,920
把疑犯帶到飛機中審訊
to bring a suspect onto the jet for questioning.

434
00:19:01,920 --> 00:19:05,230
-誰審訊他的  -是我
- And who questioned him? - I did.

435
00:19:18,590 --> 00:19:20,690
你得告訴我  愛德
You gotta talk to me, Ed.

436
00:19:22,250 --> 00:19:24,480
你得告訴我在公寓里
You have to tell me what happened

437
00:19:24,700 --> 00:19:26,590
跟保安發生了什么事
in the apartment with the guard.

438
00:19:27,840 --> 00:19:29,020
你為什么逃走
Why did you run?

439
00:19:31,630 --> 00:19:33,200
你跟她有發生關系嗎
Were you sleeping with her?

440
00:19:35,310 --> 00:19:36,480
你覺得呢
What do you think?

441
00:19:37,550 --> 00:19:40,780
老實說  我覺得你絕對不會背叛
Honestly, I don't think you'd ever betray

442
00:19:40,780 --> 00:19:42,170
你孩子的母親
the mother of your child.

443
00:19:43,980 --> 00:19:46,290
我只是想回家
I just...wanna go home,

444
00:19:46,590 --> 00:19:49,570
我對天發誓  不是我做的
and I swear to God I didn't do this.

445
00:19:49,790 --> 00:19:52,510
我知道  所以讓我幫你吧
I know, so let me help you.

446
00:19:52,510 --> 00:19:54,720
但你不懂  你幫不了的
But you don't understand. You can't.

447
00:19:57,950 --> 00:19:59,650
這太瘋狂了
This is insane.

448
00:20:01,120 --> 00:20:03,020
你在這里  走進我的生活
You being here, dropping into my life,

449
00:20:03,020 --> 00:20:04,540
就像你以前那樣
just like you did before.

450
00:20:06,570 --> 00:20:07,790
為了"拯救"我
To "Save" Me.

451
00:20:14,090 --> 00:20:18,030
不  我認為我們拯救了彼此
No, I think we saved each other.

452
00:20:19,920 --> 00:20:20,650
有嗎
Did we?

453
00:20:22,300 --> 00:20:25,630
我依然清楚記得  你告訴我
You know, I still remember exactly where we were

454
00:20:25,630 --> 00:20:27,220
我們在一起是個錯誤的時候
when you told me we were together

455
00:20:27,220 --> 00:20:29,040
我們的感情到了哪一步
for all the wrong reasons.

456
00:20:30,740 --> 00:20:32,350
但不可思議的是
But the crazy thing is,

457
00:20:32,590 --> 00:20:37,230
要是你沒有離開我  我就不會回家
if you don't leave me, then I don't go home.

458
00:20:37,810 --> 00:20:39,720
我就不會結婚  而且
I don't get married, and...

459
00:20:40,370 --> 00:20:43,190
在我生命里就不會有寶貝女兒  朱莉婭
I don't get my baby girl, Julia, in my life.

460
00:20:43,190 --> 00:20:47,280
對  我現在就不會在這里幫你
Yeah, and I don't get to be here with you right now to help you.

461
00:20:47,780 --> 00:20:49,580
你得相信我  愛德
You have to trust me, Ed.

462
00:20:50,090 --> 00:20:51,140
事實上
Truth is,

463
00:20:52,010 --> 00:20:55,730
世界上我只相信
there is only one person in the whole world

464
00:20:55,730 --> 00:20:57,180
一個人  克拉拉
that I trust, Clara.

465
00:20:58,560 --> 00:21:01,400
克拉拉  杰克剛和里法伊隊長通完電話
Clara, Jack just got off the phone with Captain Rifai.

466
00:21:01,740 --> 00:21:03,880
他要求我們把他轉送給可吉基國家警察拘留
He's asking us to transfer him to KNP custody.

467
00:21:03,880 --> 00:21:05,560
可吉基國家警察  不  慢著
KNP? No, hold on a second.

468
00:21:05,560 --> 00:21:08,440
我是被聯調局逮捕的美國公民
I'm an American citizen arrested by the FBI.

469
00:21:08,440 --> 00:21:09,860
你們為什么不能拘留我
Why can't you guys hold on to me?

470
00:21:09,860 --> 00:21:12,020
一切都會沒事的  愛德
Okay, everything is gonna be okay, Ed.

471
00:21:12,020 --> 00:21:14,290
我的團隊和我會一路陪著你
My team and I will be with you every step of the way.

472
00:21:14,300 --> 00:21:15,890
這是聯合調查
It's a joint investigation.

473
00:21:15,890 --> 00:21:17,260
其實  把他帶到這里
Actually, it was easier bringing him here

474
00:21:17,270 --> 00:21:19,130
比把他帶回鋼圈更方便
than it will be getting him back to the Steel Ring,

475
00:21:19,130 --> 00:21:21,170
不然我就得和里法伊隊長
so I'll need to coordinate security protocols

476
00:21:21,170 --> 00:21:22,220
協調安全協議
for Captain Rifai.

477
00:21:22,220 --> 00:21:23,890
好的  我幫他做準備
Okay, I'll get him ready.

478
00:21:26,020 --> 00:21:27,760
安全協議
Security protocols?

479
00:21:27,950 --> 00:21:29,920
這種加密通訊方式
Such as encrypting communications

480
00:21:29,920 --> 00:21:31,900
在可吉基國家警察和國際反應小組
between the KNP and the IRT

481
00:21:31,980 --> 00:21:34,570
轉交犯人之前  期間和之后使用
before, during, and after prisoner transfers.

482
00:21:34,570 --> 00:21:36,200
-我說得對嗎  -對
- Is that correct? - Yes.

483
00:21:36,610 --> 00:21:39,490
抱歉  特別督查探員西蒙斯
Excuse me, SSA Simmons.

484
00:21:39,490 --> 00:21:41,490
我們能倒回去嗎
Could we rewind a moment here?

485
00:21:41,770 --> 00:21:44,100
你接到里法伊隊長的電話
You get the call from Captain Rifai.

486
00:21:44,250 --> 00:21:45,910
他讓你把人交給他
He asks you to give him the guy.

487
00:21:46,250 --> 00:21:49,470
你能告訴我接下來本該發生什么嗎
Could you walk me through what should have happened next?

488
00:21:49,730 --> 00:21:52,240
原計劃是國際反應小組將犯人
The plan was for the IRT to convoy the prisoner

489
00:21:52,320 --> 00:21:55,050
押送回鋼圈內的可吉基國家警察總部
back to KNP headquarters inside the Steel Ring.

490
00:21:55,210 --> 00:21:56,830
我們本來要走由里法伊長官
We were to travel by way of secured route,

491
00:21:56,830 --> 00:21:58,440
安排的安全線路
mapped by Captain Rifai.

492
00:21:58,440 --> 00:22:00,070
行動的首要目標
The primary concern for the operation

493
00:22:00,070 --> 00:22:01,730
是避開機場
was to avoid the main road

494
00:22:01,730 --> 00:22:03,780
與鋼圈之間的主干道
between the airport and the Steel Ring.

495
00:22:03,910 --> 00:22:06,000
嗯  因為他們把那條路叫什么來著
Right, because what do they call that road --

496
00:22:06,000 --> 00:22:07,450
"詛咒之路"
"Damnation Alley"?

497
00:22:07,450 --> 00:22:08,150
西蒙斯探員
Agent Simmons,

498
00:22:08,150 --> 00:22:09,690
我們知道之后本該發生什么
we know what should have happened.

499
00:22:09,690 --> 00:22:12,220
-告訴我們實際是什么情況  -我們被
- Tell us what did happen. - We were ambushed

500
00:22:13,380 --> 00:22:15,830
忠于信念兄弟會的戰士伏擊了
by fighters loyal to the Brotherhood of Faith.

501
00:22:15,900 --> 00:22:17,170
你知道你們怎么成為攻擊目標的嗎
And do you know how you were targeted?

502
00:22:17,170 --> 00:22:18,180
怎么
How?

503
00:22:19,310 --> 00:22:21,900
不  這是隨機的攻擊
No. It was a random attack.

504
00:22:21,900 --> 00:22:22,750
隨機的
Random?

505
00:22:23,730 --> 00:22:25,560
并不是隨機的
It wasn't random.

506
00:22:25,560 --> 00:22:27,210
你們被發現是因為
You were found because you got caught

507
00:22:27,210 --> 00:22:29,610
你用公開線路進行通訊時暴露了
talking on open lines of communication.

508
00:22:29,610 --> 00:22:33,520
不可能  我親自加密了線路
That's impossible. I personally secured those lines.

509
00:22:37,940 --> 00:22:39,590
那你告訴我  先生
Well, you tell me, sir.

510
00:22:39,800 --> 00:22:42,990
你是失職  還是叛徒
Are you incompetent, or are you a traitor?

511
00:22:43,510 --> 00:22:47,570
因為電子記錄顯示并沒有加密
'Cause the digital evidence says no encryption.

512
00:22:52,610 --> 00:22:53,620
這些日志肯定不是真的
These logs can't be right.

513
00:22:53,620 --> 00:22:55,850
這些日志來自可吉基國家警察的服務器
Those logs are from the KNP server.

514
00:22:57,420 --> 00:22:59,760
伏擊過程中發生了什么
What happened during the ambush?

515
00:22:59,760 --> 00:23:01,480
我們采取了躲避策略
We engaged in evasive maneuvers.

516
00:23:01,480 --> 00:23:03,770
有一刻  我們被迫離開道路
At one point, we were forced off the road,

517
00:23:04,200 --> 00:23:05,890
緊接著發生了交火
and a gun battle ensued.

518
00:23:06,580 --> 00:23:08,240
犯人在交火時中槍
The prisoner was hit by gunfire.

519
00:23:08,240 --> 00:23:10,330
你害德爾加多中槍了
You got Delgado shot.

520
00:23:10,880 --> 00:23:12,660
就在那時我們作出決定
It was at that point the decision was made

521
00:23:12,660 --> 00:23:13,960
原路返回飛機
to double back to the jet.

522
00:23:13,960 --> 00:23:16,480
-誰做的決定  -加勒特組長
- Who made that decision? - Unit Chief Garrett.

523
00:23:17,160 --> 00:23:19,340
那是我們救德爾加多唯一的機會
It was the only chance we had to save Delgado's life.

524
00:23:19,340 --> 00:23:21,290
那是你們組長的醫療建議
Was that your unit chief's medical opinion

525
00:23:21,290 --> 00:23:24,550
還是他的外勤法醫  梅·賈維斯探員的建議
or that of his field medical examiner, Agent Mae Jarvis?

526
00:23:24,550 --> 00:23:25,730
我不知道
You know, I don't know.

527
00:23:25,740 --> 00:23:27,640
我當時忙著帶大家脫離險境
I was too busy getting us the hell out of there.

528
00:23:27,690 --> 00:23:29,770
告訴我們回飛機后發生了什么
Tell us what happened once you got back to the jet.

529
00:23:30,180 --> 00:23:32,070
德爾加多胸部中槍
Delgado had been shot in the chest.

530
00:23:33,000 --> 00:23:34,440
-這里  -我把他從車里拉出來
- Here, here. - I got him out of the SUV,

531
00:23:34,440 --> 00:23:36,520
我正準備幫忙將他搬進會議室
and I was gonna help carry him up to the conference room,

532
00:23:36,940 --> 00:23:38,730
就在那時他們試圖登機
and that's when they tried to board the plane.

533
00:23:39,650 --> 00:23:41,920
"他們"就是兄弟會的人
"They" being those Brotherhood boys.

534
00:23:41,920 --> 00:23:44,560
沒錯  克拉拉和梅以及其他機組成員
Yes. Clara and Mae and the rest of our flight crew

535
00:23:44,560 --> 00:23:46,030
將德爾加多帶離交火區
got Delgado out of the line of fire.

536
00:23:46,040 --> 00:23:47,180
好了  把他放在這里
All right, bring him right in here.

537
00:23:47,720 --> 00:23:48,620
好的
Okay.

538
00:23:49,660 --> 00:23:51,750
克拉拉  把他的防彈背心脫下來
Clara, can you get his vest off?

539
00:23:51,750 --> 00:23:52,520
好的
Okay.

540
00:23:53,430 --> 00:23:54,920
當時一片混亂
I mean, there was a lot of chaos.

541
00:23:59,760 --> 00:24:01,510
杰克和我抵擋住了他們的攻擊
Jack and I were able to hold them back

542
00:24:01,510 --> 00:24:03,510
克拉拉和梅搶救德爾加多
while Clara and Mae tended to Delgado.

543
00:24:03,510 --> 00:24:05,150
我們得給他供氧
We should get an oxygen line started.

544
00:24:06,670 --> 00:24:07,530
再緊點
Tighter.

545
00:24:08,620 --> 00:24:10,480
其他人都沒受傷嗎
And nobody else got injured?

546
00:24:10,490 --> 00:24:11,500
什么
I'm sorry?

547
00:24:11,750 --> 00:24:14,760
德爾加多是唯一一個中槍的人
Delgado was the only one who got shot.

548
00:24:14,850 --> 00:24:15,970
是的
Yes, he was.

549
00:24:16,870 --> 00:24:19,150
我們盡力關上了貨艙門
We were able to get the cargo bay doors closed.

550
00:24:24,870 --> 00:24:28,400
但你們沒能保住德爾加多的命  是不是
But you weren't able to save Delgado's life, were you?

551
00:24:28,400 --> 00:24:30,930
拜托  堅持住  拜托
Come on. Stay with me. Come on.

552
00:24:32,320 --> 00:24:33,220
梅
Mae.

553
00:24:33,440 --> 00:24:34,590
堅持住  愛德華
Come on, Edward!

554
00:24:38,640 --> 00:24:40,930
告訴我該怎么做  該怎么做
Okay, tell me what to do. What do I do?

555
00:24:44,180 --> 00:24:45,050
梅
Mae?

556
00:24:45,610 --> 00:24:46,730
他死了
He's gone.

557
00:24:55,160 --> 00:24:56,250
抱歉
I'm sorry.

558
00:25:02,540 --> 00:25:04,200
他們好像在重新集結  杰克
Looks like they're regrouping, Jack.

559
00:25:04,290 --> 00:25:06,040
可能在呼叫增援
Probably calling in reinforcements.

560
00:25:06,040 --> 00:25:07,160
你不會認為
Well, you don't think they're gonna try

561
00:25:07,160 --> 00:25:07,930
他們想要登機吧
and board the plane, do you?

562
00:25:07,930 --> 00:25:09,460
我也不想發生那種事
I don't want to have to find out.

563
00:25:10,120 --> 00:25:12,560
里法伊長官  你保證的增援呢
Captain Rifai, where's our backup you promised?

564
00:25:12,600 --> 00:25:14,660
他們現在正在路上
They are en route to you now.

565
00:25:14,660 --> 00:25:16,820
特別督查探員賈維斯  加勒特組長
SSA Jarvis, when Unit Chief Garrett

566
00:25:16,820 --> 00:25:18,320
命令小組返回飛機的時候
ordered the unit back to the jet,

567
00:25:18,320 --> 00:25:20,620
你知道德爾加多先生的全部傷勢狀況嗎
did you know the full extent of Mr. Delgado's injuries?

568
00:25:20,630 --> 00:25:22,990
我發現了一處槍傷
Um, I had identified an entry wound

569
00:25:22,990 --> 00:25:24,800
在他的右上側胸部
to his upper right thoracic region,

570
00:25:24,810 --> 00:25:28,000
我推測他的肺部受損
and I suspected that his lung had collapsed.

571
00:25:28,250 --> 00:25:29,810
那你對命令提出質疑了嗎
So did you challenge the order?

572
00:25:29,810 --> 00:25:33,080
-沒有  -你面前的傷者胸部中槍
- No. - You had a man with a gaping chest wound,

573
00:25:33,080 --> 00:25:36,210
你卻沒有堅持改道去擁有戰地醫院的
and you didn't insist on being rerouted to U.S. Camp Granato,

574
00:25:36,250 --> 00:25:37,720
美軍格拉納托駐地嗎
where they have a field hospital?

575
00:25:37,860 --> 00:25:39,860
不  我沒有  因為
No, I didn't, because

576
00:25:40,040 --> 00:25:42,390
事實上  我知道飛機上的設備
I mean, truth is, I knew that what I had on the plane

577
00:25:42,390 --> 00:25:45,730
能夠穩定他的情況  而其他選擇
could stabilize him, and everything else

578
00:25:45,730 --> 00:25:47,360
都是未知且充滿變數的
was just an unknown variable,

579
00:25:47,360 --> 00:25:49,900
而且這一切是我們被敵人攻擊時發生的
and it was all happening while we were under enemy fire.

580
00:25:50,660 --> 00:25:52,130
我知道  當時情況很危急
I get it. It was tough out there.

581
00:25:52,130 --> 00:25:54,970
-是的  -也許這就能解釋為什么
- Yeah, it was. - Maybe that speaks to why,

582
00:25:54,970 --> 00:25:58,010
從醫學院畢業后  你沒有做外科醫生
after medical school, you became a medical examiner

583
00:25:58,010 --> 00:26:00,140
而是成為了一名法醫
instead of continuing in trauma medicine.

584
00:26:01,160 --> 00:26:02,300
什么
Excuse me?

585
00:26:02,910 --> 00:26:05,650
你記得一位
Do you recall a young man

586
00:26:05,660 --> 00:26:08,380
叫迪倫·雅各布斯的年輕人嗎
by the name of Dylan Jacobs?

587
00:26:09,680 --> 00:26:12,730
記得  我記得迪倫
Yeah. Yeah, I remember Dylan.

588
00:26:12,770 --> 00:26:16,450
他入院的那晚  你是圣柯萊特
You were a resident at St. Colette's Trauma Center

589
00:26:16,450 --> 00:26:17,500
外傷治療中心的住院醫生
the night he was brought in.

590
00:26:17,500 --> 00:26:19,080
你記得他發生了什么事嗎
Do you recall what happened to him?

591
00:26:19,890 --> 00:26:21,430
記得  他死在了手術臺上
Yeah, he died on the table.

592
00:26:22,250 --> 00:26:25,110
他的家人認為是你和賈斯汀·懷亞特醫生
And his family felt that you and Dr. Justin Wyatt

593
00:26:25,110 --> 00:26:26,840
以及醫院的疏忽大意造成他死亡
and the hospital were negligent.

594
00:26:26,840 --> 00:26:28,280
他們提起了訴訟
They filed a lawsuit.

595
00:26:28,570 --> 00:26:30,790
那起訴訟庭外和解了
Uh, that was settled out of court

596
00:26:31,450 --> 00:26:33,160
簽訂了保密協議
with a nondisclosure agreement.

597
00:26:33,170 --> 00:26:36,960
意思是你無法透露你是否覺得
So are you saying you can't disclose whether or not

598
00:26:36,960 --> 00:26:39,430
自己應該對雅各布斯的死負責嗎
you feel responsible for Mr. Jacobs' death?

599
00:26:47,900 --> 00:26:50,820
杰克  我很抱歉
Jack, I am so sorry.

600
00:26:50,990 --> 00:26:52,380
我本該把一切都告訴你的
I-I should have told you everything.

601
00:26:52,380 --> 00:26:54,050
沒事的  克拉拉
No, it's all right, Clara.

602
00:26:54,050 --> 00:26:55,780
你把該告訴的都告訴我了
You told me everything you needed to.

603
00:26:58,460 --> 00:26:59,510
兩位  聽著
Hey, guys, listen.

604
00:26:59,510 --> 00:27:01,200
我知道我們不該交談
I-I know we're not supposed to talk,

605
00:27:01,750 --> 00:27:03,560
但事情有點不對勁
but there is something else going on here.

606
00:27:03,630 --> 00:27:06,380
巴恩斯和阿特伍德基本上把伏擊的事
Barnes and Atwood basically blamed me

607
00:27:06,480 --> 00:27:07,840
都怪在我頭上
for the entire ambush.

608
00:27:08,060 --> 00:27:10,920
他們說我沒有加密通訊線路
They said that I didn't encrypt the lines of communications,

609
00:27:10,990 --> 00:27:12,320
他們還提供了證據
and what they offered as proof

610
00:27:12,320 --> 00:27:15,080
來自可吉基國家警察指揮所的電子日志
were the digital log books from the KNP command post.

611
00:27:15,410 --> 00:27:17,100
相信我  那些日志肯定被篡改了
I'm telling you, those logs were doctored.

612
00:27:17,650 --> 00:27:18,370
但按理來說
But, presumably,

613
00:27:18,370 --> 00:27:20,010
只有可吉基國家警察內部的人
only somebody who works for the KNP

614
00:27:20,010 --> 00:27:21,420
-才能做到  -沒錯
- could have done that. - Right.

615
00:27:21,760 --> 00:27:23,880
克拉拉  我覺得你一開始就是對的
Clara, I think you were right from the start.

616
00:27:23,990 --> 00:27:26,920
德爾加多從來都不符合克麗兇手的側寫
Delgado never fit the profile of Keri's killer.

617
00:27:28,250 --> 00:27:30,710
問題是  他為什么要跑
Question is, why did he run?

618
00:27:31,050 --> 00:27:32,940
也許他不相信當地警方
Maybe he didn't trust the local cops.

619
00:27:33,090 --> 00:27:37,470
也許吧  德爾加多的工作重點是提高
Maybe. Delgado's job focused primarily on improving

620
00:27:37,470 --> 00:27:39,520
可吉基國家警察的網絡安全
cybersecurity for the KNP,

621
00:27:39,520 --> 00:27:41,330
所以如果他無意中發現了一些
so what if he came across something

622
00:27:41,330 --> 00:27:42,780
不該發現的東西呢
that he shouldn't have?

623
00:27:43,000 --> 00:27:45,420
一個秘密  一個如此危險的秘密
A secret, something so compromising

624
00:27:45,420 --> 00:27:47,250
以至于可吉基國家警察內部的人
that someone inside the KNP would be

625
00:27:47,250 --> 00:27:49,300
不惜將謀殺案嫁禍給他
willing to frame him for murder.

626
00:27:49,960 --> 00:27:51,750
好吧  還有一件事
Okay, but consider this.

627
00:27:51,750 --> 00:27:54,240
你知道那個保安  阿倫·薩布里嗎
You know that security guard, Aron Sabri?

628
00:27:54,240 --> 00:27:57,070
阿倫·薩布里
安保團隊

629
00:27:54,280 --> 00:27:56,290
在全球策略開發做保安只是他的副業
he was only moonlighting at the GSD compound.

630
00:27:56,290 --> 00:27:59,350
他的主要工作是可吉基國家警察的巡警
His primary job was patrol officer for the KNP.

631
00:27:59,440 --> 00:28:00,710
記得他手上的擦傷嗎
Remember the abrasions on his hands?

632
00:28:00,930 --> 00:28:02,580
那些梅無法解釋的擦傷
the ones that Mae really couldn't explain?

633
00:28:01,090 --> 00:28:02,600
尸檢報告

634
00:28:03,260 --> 00:28:05,460
如果擦傷不是因為和德爾加多扭打呢
What if they hadn't come from a struggle with Delgado?

635
00:28:05,460 --> 00:28:07,430
如果那是在一遍又一遍
What if they were a result of stabbing Keri

636
00:28:07,440 --> 00:28:08,580
刺傷克麗時產生的呢
over and over again?

637
00:28:08,580 --> 00:28:11,810
所以你認為最初的計劃是保安殺死克麗
So you think the original plan was the guard kills Keri,

638
00:28:11,810 --> 00:28:15,090
然后在德爾加多企圖逃跑時殺了他
then he kills Delgado as he tries to escape.

639
00:28:15,370 --> 00:28:17,240
不過德爾加多沒讓他得逞
Only Delgado got the better of him.

640
00:28:17,660 --> 00:28:19,930
很可惜  雖然聽起來很合理
Unfortunately, as good as this sounds,

641
00:28:19,940 --> 00:28:21,430
這仍然只是推測
it's pure speculation.

642
00:28:21,430 --> 00:28:23,320
是啊  鑒于我們現在的狀態
Yeah, and given our current status,

643
00:28:23,320 --> 00:28:24,660
我們需要確鑿的證據證明
we need some hard evidence to prove

644
00:28:24,660 --> 00:28:27,670
可吉基國家警察內部的人是幕后黑手
that someone from the KNP was behind all of this.

645
00:28:27,670 --> 00:28:29,860
我不確定在被剝奪一切的情況下
And I'm not sure we're gonna be able to prove anything

646
00:28:29,870 --> 00:28:32,030
我們還能證明什么
when we've been stripped of everything.

647
00:28:33,200 --> 00:28:34,480
也許并不是一切
Maybe not everything.

648
00:28:35,290 --> 00:28:36,880
如果德爾加多的事我們沒猜錯
Look, if we're right about Delgado,

649
00:28:36,880 --> 00:28:38,840
他確實發現了可吉基國家警察的骯臟秘密
and he did discover the KNP's dirty little secret,

650
00:28:38,840 --> 00:28:40,800
如果他還是我印象中的那個人
if he's the man that I remember,

651
00:28:40,940 --> 00:28:42,970
他會將證據藏起來
he would have hedged his bets on the evidence.

652
00:28:43,000 --> 00:28:44,000
什么意思
What do you mean?

653
00:28:44,200 --> 00:28:46,200
他有可能將發現的證據
I think that he would have sent his proof

654
00:28:46,210 --> 00:28:48,080
發給了這世上他唯一信任的人
to the only person in the world that he trusts.

655
00:29:02,490 --> 00:29:04,770
-你還好嗎  -還好
- You okay? - Sure.

656
00:29:11,080 --> 00:29:12,920
他們只是和我們玩心理游戲
Look, you know they're just playing these mind games

657
00:29:12,920 --> 00:29:14,640
想要摧毀我們的意志
in order to try to break you.

658
00:29:15,490 --> 00:29:17,090
是啊  那他們真的很厲害
Yeah, well, they're ballers at it,

659
00:29:17,090 --> 00:29:19,810
因為我已經無力招架了
'cause I feel pretty broken.

660
00:29:20,970 --> 00:29:22,250
一切都會沒事的
It'll be all right.

661
00:29:24,060 --> 00:29:25,460
我不在乎別人怎么說
I mean, I don't care what anybody says.

662
00:29:25,460 --> 00:29:29,660
但當別人的性命在你手上
When you have someone's life in your hands,

663
00:29:30,070 --> 00:29:32,960
你就能感受到責任的重量
you feel the weight of that responsibility.

664
00:29:34,230 --> 00:29:37,180
當然  你表面上能裝作很堅強
And, yeah, you can -- you can put on a brave face,

665
00:29:38,060 --> 00:29:41,950
但我覺得我永遠都學不會如何
but I don't think you ever really learn how to...

666
00:29:42,350 --> 00:29:44,110
能將自己的情感控制自如
turn your emotions on and off.

667
00:29:45,810 --> 00:29:47,520
如果那個人最終沒活下來
And if you lose that person,

668
00:29:49,920 --> 00:29:51,950
你永遠都會質疑自己
you never stop second-guessing yourself.

669
00:30:00,310 --> 00:30:02,920
蒙哥馬利探員  請你回想一下
Agent Montgomery, I'd like to direct your attention

670
00:30:02,920 --> 00:30:07,590
德爾加多先生死后發生的事情
to the events that took place after Mr. Delgado's death.

671
00:30:07,880 --> 00:30:11,500
你記不記得接到了前方的求救電話
You recall receiving a distress call from Betsy Ross?

672
00:30:11,740 --> 00:30:12,760
記得
Yes, I do.

673
00:30:12,760 --> 00:30:14,180
老大  怎么了
Hey, boss, what's going on?

674
00:30:14,180 --> 00:30:15,130
我們有麻煩了
We're in trouble.

675
00:30:15,140 --> 00:30:16,890
我們被兄弟會伏擊了
We got ambushed by the Brotherhood.

676
00:30:16,890 --> 00:30:18,850
一人遇難  看起來
We sustained a casualty. It looks like

677
00:30:18,850 --> 00:30:20,170
他們想要登機
they're gonna try to board the plane.

678
00:30:20,170 --> 00:30:21,690
好的  我立刻聯系可吉基國家警察
Okay, I'll call the KNP right now.

679
00:30:21,690 --> 00:30:23,240
我試過了  他們鞭長莫及
I tried that. They're too far away.

680
00:30:23,240 --> 00:30:24,670
你現在得立刻聯系
I need you to call in the cavalry

681
00:30:24,670 --> 00:30:26,600
美軍格拉納托駐地的裝甲部隊
from U.S. Camp Granato right now.

682
00:30:28,570 --> 00:30:32,020
你為什么無視加勒特組長的直接命令
Why did you ignore Unit Chief Garrett's direct order?

683
00:30:32,020 --> 00:30:34,340
我沒有無視  我評估了局勢
I didn't ignore it. I assessed the situation.

684
00:30:34,340 --> 00:30:36,490
查看了地圖  他們也太遠了
I looked at the map. They were too far away.

685
00:30:36,650 --> 00:30:39,200
也許你可以告訴我們
Perhaps you would be willing to tell us

686
00:30:39,230 --> 00:30:42,100
你是什么時候知道
when you first became aware of the existence

687
00:30:42,100 --> 00:30:45,090
Z-TAC夜鷹S-2的存在的
of the Z-TAC Nighthawk S-2.

688
00:30:45,640 --> 00:30:49,090
我不能告訴你一個不存在的項目  對吧
I can't tell you about a program that doesn't exist, now, can I?

689
00:30:49,150 --> 00:30:50,580
你肯定覺得自己聰明極了
You must think you're pretty smart.

690
00:30:50,580 --> 00:30:53,270
我認為夜鷹S-2是美國情報界
I think the Nighthawk S-2 is the worst kept secret

691
00:30:53,270 --> 00:30:54,810
人盡皆知的秘密
in the U.S. Intelligence community.

692
00:30:55,090 --> 00:30:57,690
是杰克·加勒特命令你黑進
Did Jack Garrett direct you to compromise

693
00:30:57,690 --> 00:30:58,930
夜鷹系統的嗎
the Nighthawk system?

694
00:30:58,980 --> 00:31:00,090
不是
No, he did not.

695
00:31:00,480 --> 00:31:02,560
-現在什么情況  -他們在撞門
- What's going on? - They're knocking at the door.

696
00:31:02,560 --> 00:31:03,930
杰克  依我看來
Okay, Jack, the way I see it,

697
00:31:03,930 --> 00:31:06,040
你唯一的選擇就是立刻起飛
your only option is to take off right now.

698
00:31:06,040 --> 00:31:07,580
這我可能無法做到
I'm not sure how that's gonna happen.

699
00:31:07,580 --> 00:31:09,540
-他們把我們包圍了  -不會很久
- They've got us surrounded. - Not for long.

700
00:31:15,110 --> 00:31:16,450
蒙哥馬利探員
Agent Montgomery,

701
00:31:15,230 --> 00:31:16,890
全球無人機控制系統

702
00:31:16,450 --> 00:31:18,950
你知道盜用并損毀
do you know what it means to misappropriate

703
00:31:18,950 --> 00:31:24,450
一架1.64億美元的無人機是什么后果嗎
and destroy a $164 million unmanned aerial vehicle?

704
00:31:24,450 --> 00:31:26,190
無意冒犯  1.64億美元
With all due respect, $164 million

705
00:31:26,190 --> 00:31:28,260
是包括項目的研發費用
suggests that you're including the R&D on the project.

706
00:31:28,260 --> 00:31:31,980
一架無人機的價格是374萬美元
The price tag for a single drone is $3.74 million.

707
00:31:31,980 --> 00:31:34,130
你覺得這是開玩笑嗎
Do you honestly think this is a joke?

708
00:31:34,130 --> 00:31:36,890
是的  你想知道我有沒有偷無人機
Yes. Do you wanna know if I stole the drone?

709
00:31:37,020 --> 00:31:40,160
我偷了  我偷無人機是因為有武裝分子
Yes, I stole the drone because there were men with guns

710
00:31:40,160 --> 00:31:42,610
追殺我的隊友  所以我黑進了
going after my team, so I hacked

711
00:31:42,610 --> 00:31:44,540
附近正在飛行的最近的監控無人機
the nearest surveillance drone in flight

712
00:31:44,540 --> 00:31:48,870
用其掃射了飛機場  好幾遍
and I strafed the airfield with it...several times.

713
00:31:51,250 --> 00:31:52,240
還好那些信念兄弟會的人
Thank God those boys over at the Brotherhood of Faith

714
00:31:52,240 --> 00:31:53,590
非常不擅長射飛靶
are really bad at skeet shooting,

715
00:31:53,590 --> 00:31:54,770
因為這樣會
because that gave them time

716
00:31:54,770 --> 00:31:56,860
把他們的注意力從飛機那里吸引過來
to draw away from the plane

717
00:31:56,860 --> 00:32:01,120
而我則是制造了一個374萬美金的燈光秀
and for me to create a $3.74 million light show,

718
00:32:02,260 --> 00:32:03,960
來讓我的隊友駕駛飛機起飛
which allowed my team to get off the tarmac

719
00:32:03,960 --> 00:32:05,110
逃出生天
and get out of harm's way.

720
00:32:05,120 --> 00:32:06,960
你知道敵方的傷亡嗎
Were you aware of enemy casualties?

721
00:32:06,960 --> 00:32:10,290
-沒有傷亡  -當時你并不知道
- There were none. - You didn't know that at the time.

722
00:32:10,330 --> 00:32:11,890
我明白這事到頭來
I understand at the end of all this,

723
00:32:11,890 --> 00:32:13,120
必須要有人來擔責
there has to be a blame game,

724
00:32:13,230 --> 00:32:14,900
但是事實是
but the truth of the matter is

725
00:32:15,310 --> 00:32:19,190
只有極少數的一部分被選中的人
there's only a chosen few who will ever be qualified

726
00:32:19,230 --> 00:32:20,490
是有資格在前線工作的
to work in the field.

727
00:32:21,370 --> 00:32:22,970
這是無可辯駁的
There's no other way to say it.

728
00:32:23,460 --> 00:32:26,260
他們有更好的直覺  判斷
Their instincts, their judgment,

729
00:32:27,730 --> 00:32:29,740
勇氣
their courage --

730
00:32:29,800 --> 00:32:33,710
因為這是必需的
it's better... because it has to be.

731
00:32:34,040 --> 00:32:35,800
因為在情急之下
Because in the heat of the moment,

732
00:32:36,100 --> 00:32:37,980
他們要做出艱難的選擇
they make the hard choices.

733
00:32:38,770 --> 00:32:42,830
你覺得你是那少數被選中人之一嗎
And do you think that you are one of those chosen few?

734
00:32:45,260 --> 00:32:46,380
我不是覺得
I don't think it.

735
00:32:48,000 --> 00:32:50,170
我是清楚知道  所以我做了那些事
I know, so I did what I did.

736
00:32:50,170 --> 00:32:51,220
下次我還會這么做
I'd do it again,

737
00:32:51,220 --> 00:32:53,860
現在我準備接受我的行為所帶來的后果
and I'm now prepared to accept the consequences of my actions.

738
00:32:54,390 --> 00:32:57,810
很好  蒙哥馬利探員  因為
Good, because, Agent Montgomery...

739
00:32:58,130 --> 00:32:59,430
你由于故意盜竊
...you're under arrest,

740
00:32:59,640 --> 00:33:01,940
玩忽職守
for willful theft, malfeasance,

741
00:33:01,940 --> 00:33:03,980
和破壞政府財物而被捕了
and destruction of government property.

742
00:33:04,100 --> 00:33:05,250
交出你的警徽
I need your badge.

743
00:33:21,120 --> 00:33:22,200
你好  阿米莉亞
Hello, Amelia.

744
00:33:24,010 --> 00:33:26,280
謝謝你來見我
Thank you for, for meeting me.

745
00:33:29,720 --> 00:33:31,820
我和愛德之間無所不談  克拉拉
Ed and I had no secrets, Clara.

746
00:33:32,890 --> 00:33:34,810
今天我來是因為我知道
I came here today because I know

747
00:33:34,810 --> 00:33:36,460
你是他的生命中很重要的一個人
that you were important to his life,

748
00:33:36,460 --> 00:33:39,010
而我真的需要有人能為他
and I really need someone to get justice for him

749
00:33:39,020 --> 00:33:40,110
還有克麗伸張正義
and for Keri.

750
00:33:41,150 --> 00:33:42,890
這正是我想要做的
That's exactly what I intend to do.

751
00:33:44,590 --> 00:33:47,520
我可以看看他給你發的照片嗎
May I see the photos that he e-mailed you?

752
00:33:56,630 --> 00:33:57,890
愛德有這種習慣嗎
Did Ed have a habit

753
00:33:57,890 --> 00:34:00,340
會經常給你發他偷拍的快照
of sending you candid snapshots like these?

754
00:34:00,350 --> 00:34:02,740
沒有  不過還好他發了
No. But I'm glad he did.

755
00:34:06,240 --> 00:34:08,490
你能把這些也給我發一份嗎
Do you mind e-mailing me copies of these?

756
00:34:09,380 --> 00:34:10,330
為什么
Why?

757
00:34:10,790 --> 00:34:12,400
阿米莉亞  我和我的隊友認為
Amelia, my team and I believe

758
00:34:12,400 --> 00:34:14,280
愛德是因為發現了一個秘密
that Ed was framed for Keri's murder

759
00:34:14,280 --> 00:34:16,300
而被陷害謀殺了克麗
because of a secret that he discovered,

760
00:34:16,300 --> 00:34:18,930
而我認為這些照片能告訴我
and I think these photos will tell me

761
00:34:18,930 --> 00:34:20,350
秘密到底是什么
exactly what that secret is.

762
00:34:24,810 --> 00:34:26,450
這怎么回事
Hey, what's going on here?

763
00:34:27,590 --> 00:34:29,760
-沒事的  杰克  -不  有事
- It's all right, Jack. - No, it's not all right.

764
00:34:29,760 --> 00:34:33,090
別插手  朋友  隨它去吧
Let it go, my friend. Let it play out.

765
00:34:33,090 --> 00:34:34,330
都是按規章走的流程
It's all part of the process.

766
00:34:34,330 --> 00:34:35,260
罪名是什么
What's the charge?

767
00:34:35,260 --> 00:34:36,420
這重要嗎  杰克
What does it matter, Jack?

768
00:34:36,420 --> 00:34:38,170
這已經是最糟的情況了
This is the worst of it.

769
00:34:38,170 --> 00:34:39,270
沃爾特  聽我說
Walter, listen to me.

770
00:34:39,270 --> 00:34:40,780
德爾加多是被陷害的
Delgado was set up.

771
00:34:40,860 --> 00:34:42,610
我或許有辦法拿到證據
I may have a way to get the evidence.

772
00:34:42,610 --> 00:34:44,770
西格爾和西蒙斯探員正在...
Agent Seger and Simmons are working on --

773
00:34:45,700 --> 00:34:47,740
西格爾和西蒙斯不能參與任何工作
Seger and Simmons can't be working on anything.

774
00:34:47,750 --> 00:34:48,870
你知道的
You know that.

775
00:34:49,480 --> 00:34:50,570
該死的  杰克
Oh, damn it, Jack.

776
00:34:50,570 --> 00:34:52,670
你又把你自己陷于不利
You have just opened yourself right back up.

777
00:34:52,670 --> 00:34:54,520
你這可是違抗命令
We're talking insubordination.

778
00:34:54,520 --> 00:34:56,590
是是  更不用說
Yeah, yeah, not to mention

779
00:34:56,590 --> 00:34:59,010
有失聯邦政府官員身份的行為了
conduct unbecoming a federal officer.

780
00:34:59,600 --> 00:35:01,050
把他帶回樓上
Take him back upstairs.

781
00:35:17,690 --> 00:35:20,060
請坐
Please, take a seat.

782
00:35:22,100 --> 00:35:23,200
加勒特組長
Unit Chief Garrett,

783
00:35:23,200 --> 00:35:25,150
在今天的會談過程中
during the course of the proceedings today,

784
00:35:25,150 --> 00:35:27,050
你是否與你的國際反應小組成員
did you or did you not communicate

785
00:35:27,050 --> 00:35:28,810
有過交流
with members of your IRT unit?

786
00:35:28,810 --> 00:35:30,720
-是的  -你是什么時候
- I did. - Where and when did

787
00:35:30,720 --> 00:35:33,030
在什么地方與他們進行的違規交流
these prohibited communications take place?

788
00:35:33,030 --> 00:35:34,210
和我小組里的其他成員一樣
Like the rest of my team,

789
00:35:34,210 --> 00:35:37,040
我要對德爾加多先生的死負責
I feel responsible for Mr. Delgado's death.

790
00:35:37,050 --> 00:35:38,090
我問的不是這個
That wasn't the question.

791
00:35:38,090 --> 00:35:39,240
這是我們在這里的原因
It's the reason we're here.

792
00:35:39,240 --> 00:35:40,030
加勒特組長
Unit Chief Garrett.

793
00:35:40,030 --> 00:35:42,470
造成德爾加多先生死亡的真正原因
The real reason that Mr. Delgado is dead

794
00:35:43,300 --> 00:35:44,470
是背叛
is betrayal.

795
00:35:45,730 --> 00:35:46,940
你在說什么
What are you talking about?

796
00:35:47,050 --> 00:35:48,870
他是個好人  盡忠職守
He was a good man doing good work,

797
00:35:48,870 --> 00:35:51,280
只不過碰巧發現了一個秘密
who, by chance, uncovered a secret.

798
00:35:51,500 --> 00:35:53,630
他發現了可吉基國家警察
He found out about a deal between the KNP

799
00:35:53,630 --> 00:35:55,550
和信念兄弟會首腦之間的交易
and the leader of the Brotherhood of Faith,

800
00:35:55,560 --> 00:35:56,850
也就是拉尚·努里
Rashan Noori.

801
00:35:57,760 --> 00:35:59,830
他們出賣恐怖分子的名單
In exchange for ratting out terrorist cells,

802
00:35:59,830 --> 00:36:01,690
作為交換  可吉基國家警察向努里保證
Noori was guaranteed that the KNP

803
00:36:01,690 --> 00:36:02,620
會對他們的犯罪行為
would turn a blind eye

804
00:36:02,620 --> 00:36:04,460
睜一只眼閉一只眼
toward its own criminal activities

805
00:36:04,460 --> 00:36:07,930
這其中包括買賣可吉基兒童
which include the trafficking of Kurjik children.

806
00:36:08,060 --> 00:36:10,190
你怎么知道這些的
You know all this how?

807
00:36:10,190 --> 00:36:12,010
德爾加多遵循了規章制度
Delgado followed the protocol.

808
00:36:12,010 --> 00:36:14,280
他在卡利葉見了美國反貪調查員
He met with the U.S. Ombudsman in Qalea.

809
00:36:14,280 --> 00:36:17,230
提供了證據  不過為了回答你的問題
He offered evidence, but to answer your question,

810
00:36:17,230 --> 00:36:21,260
我知道這一切是由于德爾加多先生
I know about all this because Mr. Delgado

811
00:36:21,260 --> 00:36:23,460
還違反了規章
also violated protocol.

812
00:36:23,700 --> 00:36:26,330
他還把一份證據副本用加密信息
He sent copies of the same evidence to his wife

813
00:36:26,870 --> 00:36:29,710
藏在照片里發給了他的妻子
in encrypted messages in photos.

814
00:36:30,950 --> 00:36:32,150
就是這一份
Like this one.

815
00:36:36,140 --> 00:36:39,130
你是說愛德華·德爾加多用了隱寫術嗎
Saying that Edward Delgado used steganography?

816
00:36:39,130 --> 00:36:43,000
對  他用一份電子檔案作為另一份的偽裝
Yes. He was able to camouflage one digital file within another,

817
00:36:43,000 --> 00:36:45,390
如果你繼續翻后面那些圖片
and if you continue to swipe past those images,

818
00:36:45,390 --> 00:36:47,720
你會找到行為分析部的技術分析員
you'll find the encryption that was provided to me

819
00:36:47,720 --> 00:36:51,050
佩內洛普·加西亞提供給我的加密信息
by BAU Technical Analyst, Penelope Garcia.

820
00:36:51,320 --> 00:36:52,550
讓我看看
Let me see that.

821
00:36:54,680 --> 00:36:57,310
拋開這份證據不談  你的行為...
Despite this evidence, your conduct --

822
00:36:57,310 --> 00:36:59,670
這份證據證明了國際行動小組
This evidence helps to prove that the IRT

823
00:36:59,670 --> 00:37:01,900
和德爾加多一樣是被陷害的
was also set up, just like Delgado.

824
00:37:02,010 --> 00:37:02,990
被陷害
Set up?

825
00:37:02,990 --> 00:37:05,800
對  因為這份與魔鬼的協議
Yes, because the most compromising part

826
00:37:05,800 --> 00:37:07,500
最有損名譽的部分是
of this deal with the devil is that

827
00:37:07,500 --> 00:37:10,710
這一切都是在一位美國情報部門官員的
it was all illegally sanctioned

828
00:37:10,710 --> 00:37:12,220
非法批準下進行的
by a U.S. Intelligence officer.

829
00:37:12,410 --> 00:37:14,270
這就是必須要陷害德爾加多的原因
That's why Delgado had to be framed.

830
00:37:14,270 --> 00:37:16,500
這就是必須要伏擊我的團隊的原因
That's why my team had to be ambushed --

831
00:37:16,510 --> 00:37:19,060
為了保護這位代號為"象"的
to protect the identity of the officer,

832
00:37:20,230 --> 00:37:21,680
官員的身份
code-named "Bishop."

833
00:37:22,180 --> 00:37:24,920
我必須要告訴你如果你指控
I have an obligation to tell you that if you accuse

834
00:37:24,990 --> 00:37:26,850
一位情報部門官員
an Intelligence officer of a crime

835
00:37:26,850 --> 00:37:28,270
而沒有足夠證據的話...
without sufficient evidence...

836
00:37:28,270 --> 00:37:30,030
這才是關鍵所在  對吧
That's the real trick, isn't it?

837
00:37:30,460 --> 00:37:32,930
如果你生活在一個被謊言籠罩的世界
How do you get to the truth in a shadow world

838
00:37:32,930 --> 00:37:34,350
又何從找到真相
defended by lies?

839
00:37:35,690 --> 00:37:38,820
我想這就是檔案派上用場的時候了
I like to think that's where profiling comes in handy.

840
00:37:39,240 --> 00:37:43,140
能找到行為背后的動機
The ability to decipher motive behind behavior,

841
00:37:43,360 --> 00:37:45,690
謊言背后的始作俑者
the liar behind the lie.

842
00:37:47,350 --> 00:37:48,880
我覺得你已經知道了
Something tells me you think

843
00:37:48,880 --> 00:37:50,260
這些問題的答案  杰克
you already know the answer to that, Jack.

844
00:37:50,260 --> 00:37:52,010
我的確是知道的  琳達
I think I do, Linda.

845
00:37:52,460 --> 00:37:55,470
首先要好好想想誰會從中獲益
First, you have to ask yourself who benefits?

846
00:37:56,530 --> 00:37:59,110
利用像努里這樣現成的資源
Who would be best served by taking advantage

847
00:37:59,110 --> 00:38:00,990
誰是最大的受益者
of an off-the-shelf resource like Noori?

848
00:38:00,990 --> 00:38:03,500
更重要的是  誰有這個膽量
But more importantly, who would have the nerve

849
00:38:03,500 --> 00:38:05,530
敢和魔鬼做交易
to make that deal with the devil?

850
00:38:07,590 --> 00:38:09,990
這個人肯定是心安理得地
It would have to be somebody who felt comfortable

851
00:38:09,990 --> 00:38:13,000
將必要采取的惡行合理化
rationalizing all those necessary evils

852
00:38:13,000 --> 00:38:15,940
來保護更大的利益
in order to protect the greater good.

853
00:38:16,340 --> 00:38:17,790
這個人一定是認為
It'd have to be somebody who believes that

854
00:38:17,790 --> 00:38:19,360
結果比過程更重要
the ends always justify the means.

855
00:38:19,360 --> 00:38:20,270
沒錯
Right.

856
00:38:21,480 --> 00:38:22,910
你明白我在說什么吧
You see what I'm saying?

857
00:38:23,900 --> 00:38:28,870
象  所以這個人
Bishop. So maybe even someone who enjoys

858
00:38:28,870 --> 00:38:30,060
可能也很喜歡國際象棋吧
the game of chess?

859
00:38:30,370 --> 00:38:33,260
因為在國際象棋中  象這個角色
Because in chess, the Bishop's personality

860
00:38:33,260 --> 00:38:36,020
往往被視為陰險  狡猾
is often considered sly, cunning...

861
00:38:37,860 --> 00:38:39,140
并且墮落
and corrupt.

862
00:38:39,520 --> 00:38:41,550
而你總能驅王使后
Plus you always get to be king.

863
00:38:43,690 --> 00:38:45,200
巴恩斯助理主任
Assistant Director Barnes,

864
00:38:45,200 --> 00:38:48,870
要是我是你  我接下來會謹言慎行的
I would consider your next move carefully.

865
00:38:49,020 --> 00:38:51,340
我就是這么打算的
Oh. I am.

866
00:38:52,260 --> 00:38:54,200
阿特伍德副主任  你被捕了
Deputy Director Atwood, you're under arrest.

867
00:38:54,210 --> 00:38:55,980
你有權保持沉默
You have the right to remain silent.

868
00:38:55,980 --> 00:38:57,750
你不是來真的吧
You can't be serious.

869
00:38:58,300 --> 00:38:59,980
杰克的那套心理側寫
Jack's psycho profile

870
00:38:59,980 --> 00:39:01,550
就是一派胡言  算不上證據
B.S. isn't evidence.

871
00:39:01,550 --> 00:39:03,330
但是加西亞探員在你的私人服務器上
But the e-mails that Agent Garcia

872
00:39:03,330 --> 00:39:06,110
發現的郵件是證據  沃爾特
found on your private server are, Walter.

873
00:39:07,560 --> 00:39:10,590
你根本不知道你做了什么
You have no idea what you've done.

874
00:39:10,590 --> 00:39:12,030
你這個混蛋
You son of a bitch.

875
00:39:12,840 --> 00:39:14,550
你害死了德爾加多
You had Delgado killed.

876
00:39:14,710 --> 00:39:16,280
你讓我的團隊處于險境
You put my team in the line of fire

877
00:39:16,280 --> 00:39:17,350
把我們當成犧牲品
like we were expendable.

878
00:39:17,350 --> 00:39:19,070
你們就是犧牲品
You are expendable!

879
00:39:19,600 --> 00:39:22,050
因為你們是士兵  杰克  我也是
Because you're soldiers, Jack, just like I am.

880
00:39:22,130 --> 00:39:24,540
士兵們會犧牲自己
And soldiers sacrifice themselves

881
00:39:24,540 --> 00:39:26,190
來保護其他人
so others won't have to.

882
00:39:26,450 --> 00:39:29,570
你以為我喜歡和努里這種混蛋同流合污嗎
You think I like lying down with dogs like Noori?

883
00:39:29,800 --> 00:39:32,520
你說得對  這就是必須采取的惡行
You're damn right it's a necessary evil.

884
00:39:32,680 --> 00:39:33,280
知道為什么嗎
You know why?

885
00:39:33,280 --> 00:39:36,010
因為我們正處在戰爭中  朋友們
Because we're at war, my friends.

886
00:39:36,060 --> 00:39:38,120
別搞錯了  就是因為我們告訴大家
Make no mistake, just because we're telling people

887
00:39:38,120 --> 00:39:40,190
可以一如既往地安居樂業
to keep streaming and shopping,

888
00:39:40,470 --> 00:39:43,530
我們為了實現這些理想才進行骯臟的斗爭
we're in a dog fight for everything we hold to be true.

889
00:39:43,980 --> 00:39:45,320
如果沒有我這種人
And without men like me,

890
00:39:45,680 --> 00:39:48,680
沒有我這種采取必要惡行的人
without men willing to do what is necessary,

891
00:39:48,780 --> 00:39:50,590
我們就會輸
we will lose!

892
00:39:50,610 --> 00:39:52,600
少擺出這副自以為是的樣子
Spare me the self-righteousness,

893
00:39:52,600 --> 00:39:55,730
你怎么好意思把自己
and don't you dare compare yourself

894
00:39:55,730 --> 00:39:57,430
和那些士兵們相提并論
to the men and women in uniform.

895
00:39:58,580 --> 00:39:59,680
你就是個小辦事員
You're a clerk

896
00:40:00,390 --> 00:40:01,540
還是名罪犯
and a criminal.

897
00:40:02,300 --> 00:40:03,460
帶他出去
Get him outta here.

898
00:40:20,280 --> 00:40:21,340
你怎么樣
How you doing?

899
00:40:22,210 --> 00:40:24,140
好多了  畢竟現在沒帶著手銬了
Better, now that I got the handcuffs off.

900
00:40:24,140 --> 00:40:26,390
但到底是怎么回事
But...what's going on?

901
00:40:30,630 --> 00:40:32,310
鑒于我們目前的情況
Given our current state of affairs,

902
00:40:32,310 --> 00:40:34,440
我對這個結果沒意見
I've agreed to this little tite-e-tite.

903
00:40:35,030 --> 00:40:36,040
謝謝
Thank you.

904
00:40:36,380 --> 00:40:37,720
顯然  我沒有隱瞞自己的想法
Obviously, I've made no secret

905
00:40:37,720 --> 00:40:39,970
我想削弱國際反應小組的作用
about my desire to diminish the IRT's role.

906
00:40:39,970 --> 00:40:41,590
你想擺脫我們
You'd like to get rid of us.

907
00:40:41,660 --> 00:40:42,840
我想要你們能負起責任
I'd like you to be accountable.

908
00:40:42,840 --> 00:40:45,510
我們是負責的  一直如此
We are. We always have been.

909
00:40:45,700 --> 00:40:47,510
那你叫我來干什么呢  杰克
Then why did you ask me here, Jack?

910
00:40:47,600 --> 00:40:50,420
不是來要求對蒙哥馬利探員寬大處理的嗎
If not to ask for leniency for Agent Montgomery?

911
00:40:50,550 --> 00:40:52,050
這正是我想說的
And this is what I'm talking about.

912
00:40:52,050 --> 00:40:54,970
盡管他意圖是好的  結果也不壞
The fact remains that in spite of his good intentions

913
00:40:54,970 --> 00:40:57,260
但蒙哥馬利探員
or the positive results, Agent Montgomery

914
00:40:57,260 --> 00:40:59,350
必須為他自己的行為負責
must be held accountable for his actions.

915
00:40:59,680 --> 00:41:01,090
就算我同意
And even if I were to recommend

916
00:41:01,150 --> 00:41:02,970
不提起刑事訴訟
not seeking criminal prosecution,

917
00:41:03,250 --> 00:41:06,110
但最起碼局里必須要辭退他
at the very least, the Bureau must terminate his employment.

918
00:41:06,900 --> 00:41:07,960
她說得對  杰克
She's right, Jack.

919
00:41:08,270 --> 00:41:09,520
我不認同
No, I don't think so.

920
00:41:10,290 --> 00:41:12,310
因為蒙哥馬利探員的行為
Because Agent Montgomery's actions

921
00:41:12,310 --> 00:41:14,900
和我團隊中任何人所做的任何行為
or any actions taken by a member of my team

922
00:41:15,140 --> 00:41:16,190
都是基于我的命令
are done on my orders,

923
00:41:16,190 --> 00:41:18,580
無論是直接下達的還是暗示的
whether directly stated or implied.

924
00:41:18,580 --> 00:41:20,170
一切責任都應該由我承擔
The buck stops with me, always,

925
00:41:20,170 --> 00:41:23,750
就算有人要被開除  那也該是我
so if anyone's gonna get fired, it's me.

926
00:41:24,790 --> 00:41:26,120
我認真的  琳達
I'm serious, Linda.

927
00:41:26,130 --> 00:41:28,470
我知道你是認真的  杰克  但你可能
I know you are, Jack, but I'm not sure

928
00:41:28,470 --> 00:41:30,640
還不清楚現在的情況
you appreciate the scope of the situation here.

929
00:41:30,770 --> 00:41:31,550
你剛剛扳倒了
You just took down

930
00:41:31,550 --> 00:41:33,320
國家情報局的副主任
the Deputy Director of National Intelligence.

931
00:41:33,320 --> 00:41:35,360
現在要我來停你的職嗎
Now I'm gonna be the one to take your badge?

932
00:41:35,360 --> 00:41:37,970
沒錯啊  因為就該如此
Yes, because that's how it works.

933
00:41:37,970 --> 00:41:39,370
這就是責任
That's accountability.

934
00:41:44,520 --> 00:41:47,400
杰克·加勒特組長  我先跟你說清楚
Unit Chief Jack Garrett, let me be crystal clear.

935
00:41:47,860 --> 00:41:50,960
我會盯著你和你的小組
You and your unit are on notice.

936
00:41:50,960 --> 00:41:52,560
你可以把這當成是第一振
You may consider this your first strike,

937
00:41:52,560 --> 00:41:55,390
在這場博弈中  第二振你就會出局
and in this game, a second strike means you are out.

938
00:42:08,140 --> 00:42:09,090
你還好嗎
You good?

939
00:42:09,380 --> 00:42:12,470
別提我了  他們都準備把你關起來了
Me? Forget about me. They were about to lock you up.

940
00:42:12,470 --> 00:42:14,500
嗯  但我知道你們會來救我的  對吧
Yeah, but I knew you guys would come break me out, right?

941
00:42:14,530 --> 00:42:16,010
也可能是和你關在一起
Or share a cell with you.

942
00:42:16,330 --> 00:42:17,850
我們是彼此的堅強后盾
We had each other's backs.

943
00:42:18,060 --> 00:42:22,160
的確  我們回家吧  休息一下
Yes, we did. Let's go home, get some rest.

944
00:42:23,450 --> 00:42:24,720
各位
Uh, guys?

945
00:42:28,960 --> 00:42:31,070
壞蛋們可從不休息
Well... no rest for the wicked.

946
00:42:34,420 --> 00:42:35,340
確實
No.

947
00:42:36,940 --> 00:42:38,600
看來我們又有工作了
'Cause we got a job to do.

948
00:42:39,460 --> 00:42:43,070
聯邦調查局國際反應小組

