[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: DBfansub
ScriptType: v4.00+
PlayResX: 1280
PlayResY: 720
YCbCr Matrix: TV.601

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,58,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00030304,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,0
Style: Image,Arial,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,7,0,0,0,0
Style: 工作表,Arial,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 背景,Arial,20,&HA0FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 片尾,方正喵呜体,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 注释,微软雅黑,38,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00030304,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,8,5,5,2,0
Style: 片头,微软雅黑,100,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00030304,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,15,0,2,5,5,2,1
Style: 白字,微软雅黑,50,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00030304,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,5,5,2,0

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:05.00,工作表,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\fs32\fad(800,800)\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H666562&\b1}{\fn时尚中黑简体}翻译: 牙牙 何佩仪
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.00,0:00:10.00,工作表,NTP,0,0,0,,{\c&HFFFFFF&\b1\3c&H666562&}{\an8\fs32\fad(800,800)}{\fn时尚中黑简体}校对: 墩子 XLX
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.00,0:00:15.00,工作表,NTP,0,0,0,,{\c&HFFFFFF&}{\an8\fs32\fad(800,800)\b1\3c&H666562&}{\fn时尚中黑简体}后期: 秋小豚
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.00,0:00:20.00,工作表,NTP,0,0,0,,{\c&HFFFFFF&\an8}{\fs32\fad(800,800)\b1\3c&H666562&}{\fn时尚中黑简体\b1}压制: 怪查理
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:20.70,背景,,0,0,0,,{\fs34}{\p1\c&H96955E&\fscx4200\fscy410\an8\fad(800,800)\pos(642,0)}m 0 0 b 0 0 0 0 0 0 b 0 0 0 0 0 0 b 0 4 0 9 0 13 b 4 13 9 13 13 13 b 13 9 13 4 13 0 {\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:36:43.48,0:45:00.00,片尾,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正喵呜体}{\fs70\c&H20F0FF&\b1}电波字幕组 欢迎您的加入\N{\fs34}\N{\fs65\b0}官方网站:www.dbfansub.com\N{\fs34}\N{\fs65\b0}新浪微博:@电波字幕组
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.18,0:03:25.18,片头,,0,0,0,,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.18,0:03:28.70,片头,,0,0,0,,{\fsp0\t(0,3000,\fsp50)\fscx1\t(0,200,\fscx101\t(50,100\fscx1))\fn迷你简毡笔黑\pos(627.734,569.2)}致幻旅行
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.18,0:03:28.70,片头,,0,0,0,,{\fsp0\t(0,3000,\fsp10)\fscx1\t(0,200,\fscx101\t(50,100\fscx1))\fn迷你简毡笔黑\pos(610.134,662)}\N{\fs40\bord5}第一季       第一集\N电波诚译
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.78,0:03:30.98,白字,,0,0,0,,{\fad(1000,500)\fs80\move(570.667,379.334,730.667,395.334,20,2180)\org(784,552.666)\frx10\fry14\b1}2小时前{\b0}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.66,0:01:08.35,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Danny\N{\fs38}Danny?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.37,0:01:10.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们得谈谈\N{\fs38}We need to talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.91,0:01:13.10,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这不是唯一的世界 世界有数百万个\N{\fs38}This is not the only world, there are millions of them
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.13,0:01:14.73,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在每一个世界里\N{\fs38}and in every single one...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.32,0:01:23.47,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他从那时开始追捕我们\N{\fs38}He's been hunting us ever since...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.30,0:01:29.79,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,也就是说在每一个世界里 他都要杀死我们\N{\fs38}..That means in every single one he's trying to kill us.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.12,0:01:31.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杀死我们 杀死我们\N{\fs38}Kill us, kill us...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.75,0:01:35.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对不起 Danny 你得倒回去再说一遍\N{\fs38}Sorry, Danny, you're going to have to back that up.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.06,0:01:36.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 我刚才脑子一片空白  - 啥\N{\fs38}- I zoned out for a second. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.86,0:01:39.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 从哪里开始说  - 噢\N{\fs38}- How far? - Oh...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.02,0:01:41.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,从头 嗯 我之前嗑了点药\N{\fs38}the beginning. Yeah, I took some killer mushrooms earlier.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.26,0:01:42.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没时间了 你得跟我走\N{\fs38}There's no time. You have to come with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.80,0:01:45.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,老实说 你现在跟好多其他东西混在一起\N{\fs38}Honestly, you are competing with a lot of other stuff right now,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.64,0:01:46.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有些在那儿 有些不在那儿\N{\fs38}which may or may not be there
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.92,0:01:48.86,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,比如你身后挥着剑的家伙\N{\fs38}like the guy behind you with a sword
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.90,0:01:50.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我真心希望他不是真的\N{\fs38}who I really hope isn't real...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.68,0:02:07.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,哇\N{\fs38}Whoa!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.99,0:02:15.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,跑呀 Milo\N{\fs38}Run, Milo!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.30,0:02:37.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好 好\N{\fs38}OK, OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.71,0:02:38.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,柜子\N{\fs38}Cupboard.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.66,0:02:45.94,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这不是真的 这只是个可怕的幻觉 一定是这样\N{\fs38}This isn't real. This is just a bad trip, is all this is.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.98,0:02:48.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 好吧 这感觉倒很真实  - Milo 闭嘴\N{\fs38}- OK, that does actually feel very real. - Milo, shut up.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.98,0:02:50.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道我叫啥 这是好事吗 我们见过吗\N{\fs38}You know my name. Is that good? Have we met?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.43,0:02:51.94,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不好意思 我们见过吗 啊\N{\fs38}I'm sorry. Am I supposed to know your name? Ah!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.19,0:02:54.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道我弄死过多少个版本的你吗\N{\fs38}Do you know how many versions of you I've killed?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.00,0:02:58.38,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,多到都烦了\N{\fs38}Enough to get bored with it?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.15,0:03:00.28,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,每次结局都一样\N{\fs38}It always ends like this.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.06,0:03:04.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,困惑\N{\fs38}Confused.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.72,0:03:05.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,无助\N{\fs38}Helpless.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.99,0:03:08.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你的遗言我听了太多次\N{\fs38}I've heard your last words so many times,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.32,0:03:11.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道这有多无聊么 非常无聊\N{\fs38}do you know how boring that is? It's very boring.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.18,0:03:13.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以 来吧\N{\fs38}So, go on,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.44,0:03:16.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,来点儿新鲜的\N{\fs38}surprise me.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.09,0:03:45.18,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,嘿 哥们 这是你的订婚礼物\N{\fs38}Hey, buddy! Here is your engagement present.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.20,0:03:46.54,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这些会让你嗨到飞起\N{\fs38}These will blow your nuts off.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.68,0:03:48.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Milo 这是Kate的爷爷\N{\fs38}Milo, this is Kate's grandfather.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.15,0:03:51.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,噢 嗑点儿迷幻蘑菇\N{\fs38}Oh, mushroom?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.39,0:03:53.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让你嗨起来 来点儿\N{\fs38}They'll blow your nuts off, yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.18,0:03:54.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 他在开玩笑啦  - 我没有\N{\fs38}- He's joking. - I'm not.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.48,0:03:56.62,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- Milo 你来啦  - 是啊\N{\fs38}- Milo! You're here. - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.20,0:03:59.42,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还给我爷爷迷幻蘑菇呢\N{\fs38}Offering magic mushrooms to my grandad.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.46,0:04:01.39,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,活到老 嗨到老\N{\fs38}You're never too old to have your nuts blown off.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.40,0:04:04.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 妈在找你呢 去吧  - 等会儿见\N{\fs38}- Mum was looking for you. OK? - See you later.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.22,0:04:06.32,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等会儿见\N{\fs38}See you in a bit.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.57,0:04:08.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 我们还以为你来不了了呢\N{\fs38}- We started to think you couldn't make it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.70,0:04:10.01,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 不好意思让你失望了\N{\fs38}- Sorry to disappoint you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.24,0:04:14.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧 我可不想让憋着的怨气发散出来\N{\fs38}OK, I hate to tear myself away from all the simmering resentment.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.36,0:04:19.36,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 嗯哼  - 我们能不能起码试着不要搞那么尴尬\N{\fs38}- Well, well. - Can we at least try not to let this be weird?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.16,0:04:24.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,嗨 大家好啊\N{\fs38}Hi! Hi everyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.30,0:04:28.62,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想感谢所有人的到来 也谢谢你 Danny\N{\fs38}I just wanted to thank everyone for coming and thank you, Danny,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.67,0:04:30.42,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢你向我求婚\N{\fs38}for asking me to be your wife.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.83,0:04:33.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 噢  - 没事啦  - 我知道这难为你了\N{\fs38}- Aw! - That's all right. - I know, it makes you sick.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.68,0:04:35.87,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,噢 还要谢谢Paul Danny的伴郎\N{\fs38}Oh, and thank you to Paul, Danny's best man
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.88,0:04:38.54,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,今晚费心帮我张罗\N{\fs38}who's been such a help in organising tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.64,0:04:41.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有比你更好的伴郎啦\N{\fs38}We really couldn't have hoped for a better best man so...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.82,0:04:43.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大家今晚要喝的尽兴 玩得开心啊\N{\fs38}Everyone have a drink and I hope you have a good night.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.00,0:04:44.96,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不好意思\N{\fs38}Excuse me a moment.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.89,0:04:53.95,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,嘿 小子\N{\fs38}Hi, sausage.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.53,0:05:02.40,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 噢 又来了  - 天国的阶梯\N{\fs38}- Oh, here we go. - Stairway to heaven.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.43,0:05:03.96,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他肯定得\N{\fs38}It's got to be...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.81,0:05:09.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,嗷 他是不是 他没事儿吧\N{\fs38}Oh! Is it, is he all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.47,0:05:11.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果哪天有人真的摔断了脖子\N{\fs38}You know, that is actually going to stop being funny one day
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.86,0:05:13.39,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这事儿就不好笑了\N{\fs38}when someone actually breaks their neck.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.40,0:05:14.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那个台阶真该修修了\N{\fs38}Someone really ought to fix that step.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.66,0:05:21.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那个 伴郎的事 嗯\N{\fs38}So, the best man thing... Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.08,0:05:25.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 我本来是要跟你说的  - 好\N{\fs38}- I was going to speak to you about it. - Fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.16,0:05:27.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对不起 Milo 这事儿\N{\fs38}I'm sorry, Milo, it's...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.35,0:05:31.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Paul真的很努力地跟Kate搞好关系 而你\N{\fs38}Paul has really made an effort with Kate and you...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.86,0:05:34.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你却没有 我们还是朋友啊 Milo\N{\fs38}You really haven't. We're still mates, Milo,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.96,0:05:38.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只是现在我们处在人生中的不同阶段\N{\fs38}but right now we're just at very different places in our lives.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.89,0:05:40.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不可能永远是"危险Danny"啊\N{\fs38}I can't be Dangerous Dan forever, you know.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.04,0:05:44.74,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,尽管你确实纹了个"永远的危险Danny"\N{\fs38}Even though you literally had "Dangerous Dan forever"
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.96,0:05:46.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在你的屁股蛋子上 在法里拉基的时候\N{\fs38}tattooed on your arse cheek in Faliraki.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.96,0:05:46.51,注释,NTP,0,0,0,,爱琴海罗德岛上的海滩度假村
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.54,0:05:47.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我已经长大了\N{\fs38}I'm getting my big boy on.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.80,0:05:50.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会戴袖扣 我还要结婚了\N{\fs38}You know, I'm wearing cuff links, getting married.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.61,0:05:54.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 前几天我还升职了  - 升啥职\N{\fs38}- I even got promoted the other day. - Promoted?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.18,0:05:56.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你是做猫咪保险的 你能升到哪儿去\N{\fs38}You work in cat insurance, what can you get promoted to?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.28,0:06:00.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,狮子保险\N{\fs38}Lion insurers?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.38,0:06:03.74,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那是宠物保险 事实上我现在管理着\N{\fs38}It is PET insurance and I'm actually covering all of the
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.76,0:06:05.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,整个西南地区的大型哺乳动物呢\N{\fs38}large mammals in the south west now, so...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.34,0:06:08.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 做的不错  - 对我来说是件大事\N{\fs38}- Well done you. - It's a big deal for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.86,0:06:10.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,兄弟 拜托 别走啊\N{\fs38}Mate, come on, don't go.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.99,0:06:14.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你就再喝几杯或者啥的\N{\fs38}Just, like, have a couple more drinks or something.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.51,0:06:19.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们为什么要拥抱\N{\fs38}Why are we hugging?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.02,0:06:22.62,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为就这样了 就此别过\N{\fs38}Cos this is it. This is goodbye.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.62,0:06:26.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不会再见到你了 和你的猫咪保险工作\N{\fs38}I'm never going to see you again with your new cat insurance job
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.17,0:06:28.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,以及你的新婚媳妇 还有你的\N{\fs38}and your new wife and your...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.47,0:06:31.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你会见我的 你喝多了\N{\fs38}You will. You're drunk.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.87,0:06:32.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不\N{\fs38}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.58,0:06:36.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,再见了Danny 好好过日子\N{\fs38}I'll see you around, Danny, you have a good life.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.82,0:06:40.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,噢\N{\fs38}Whoa!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.47,0:06:43.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Milo 我是Paul 记得吗\N{\fs38}Milo! Paul, remember.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.16,0:06:44.91,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 哦 是啊 Paul  - 嗯\N{\fs38}- Oh, yeah, Paul. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.96,0:06:47.58,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,提醒一下 今晚就我一个人\N{\fs38}Word of warning, I am tout seul tonight,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.58,0:06:50.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我媳妇感觉有点不舒服 所以\N{\fs38}the missus was feeling a bit rough so
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.32,0:06:53.71,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我浑身上下都是啤酒 可以这么说么\N{\fs38}I am on the beers, so to speak.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.31,0:07:16.32,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,晚上好 奶奶\N{\fs38}Evening, Gran.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.55,0:07:27.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- Danny  - 啊\N{\fs38}- Danny? - Argh!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.30,0:07:30.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧\N{\fs38}OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.90,0:07:32.99,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 啊  - 你的遗言我听了太多次\N{\fs38}- Ah! - I've heard your last words so many times,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.00,0:07:35.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道这有多无聊么\N{\fs38}do you know how boring that is?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.66,0:07:36.57,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,非常无聊\N{\fs38}It's very boring.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.82,0:07:38.46,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以 来吧\N{\fs38}So, go on,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.08,0:07:41.20,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,来点儿新鲜的\N{\fs38}surprise me.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.22,0:07:44.99,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这压力真够大的\N{\fs38}Well, that is a lot of pressure, I mean...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.90,0:07:58.96,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这事儿没完\N{\fs38}This isn't the end.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.62,0:08:01.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还会有其他人的\N{\fs38}There will be others...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.71,0:08:02.67,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还会再有人\N{\fs38}And others...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.51,0:08:05.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你会死的\N{\fs38}And you'll die.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.70,0:08:07.74,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还是你先吧\N{\fs38}You first.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.10,0:08:18.18,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,真及时 真及时 我还以为你死了\N{\fs38}Good timing. Good timing, I thought you were dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.24,0:08:21.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 这没有看上去那么糟  - 是 好的 好\N{\fs38}- It's not as bad as it looks. - Yeah, good, good.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.34,0:08:23.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,貌似你的胸膛上被穿了个大窟窿\N{\fs38}Cos it looks like you've got a massive hole in your chest.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.69,0:08:29.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,操 不不不 记得我告诉你的\N{\fs38}Shit. No, no, no, remember what I told you.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.31,0:08:31.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吗 你和Danny与众不同\N{\fs38}OK, you and Danny are special.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.32,0:08:34.46,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 你得过来找到我  - 怎么找到你\N{\fs38}- You need to come find me. - Find you, how?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.50,0:08:36.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,用腕带 找金泥\N{\fs38}Look for Goldenmire, use the wristband.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.43,0:08:38.89,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,记得我告诉你的 你就会没事\N{\fs38}Remember what I told you and you'll be fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.76,0:08:41.18,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Milo 告诉我你还记得\N{\fs38}Milo, tell me remember,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.18,0:08:41.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉我你\N{\fs38}tell me you...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.62,0:08:48.99,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,也许我应该用笔记下来 呃\N{\fs38}Maybe I should've got a pen. Um...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.61,0:08:54.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 早啊 猪头  - 早 拍屁屁\N{\fs38}- Morning, dickhead. - Morning, arse flaps.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.86,0:08:57.10,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,噢 我的小二货脸\N{\fs38}Oh, my little twatface.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.14,0:08:59.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的唯一小笨蛋\N{\fs38}My one true shit-for-brains.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.21,0:09:02.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你得起床换衣服\N{\fs38}You need to get up and get changed
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.92,0:09:05.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为我们要去花店啦\N{\fs38}because we are going to the florist.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.24,0:09:08.42,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,今天吗 我不舒服 我们不能改天去吗\N{\fs38}Today? I feel rough. Can't we go another day?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.46,0:09:11.47,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你已经改期三次啦\N{\fs38}You already cancelled three times.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.58,0:09:12.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你是不是想暗示我什么\N{\fs38}You trying to tell me something?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.36,0:09:15.05,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当然不是 只是\N{\fs38}Of course not, it's just...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.06,0:09:18.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你头发里有东西 只是\N{\fs38}You've got something in your hair. It's just...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.92,0:09:23.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在你是我的人啦 准备好接受蹂躏吧\N{\fs38}Now you are mine, prepare to be ravaged.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.92,0:09:26.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 换衣服啦 你个二货  - 就不\N{\fs38}- Get changed, you twat! - Never!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.26,0:09:28.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你得跟我干点儿什么先\N{\fs38}Not until you have done stuff with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.26,0:09:37.18,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 喂  - Danny 我有麻烦了\N{\fs38}- Hello. - 'Danny, I am in trouble,'
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.22,0:09:39.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要你现在就过来一趟\N{\fs38}I need you to come over right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.66,0:09:42.62,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- Milo 你是不是还嗨着呢  - 真希望是这样 Dan\N{\fs38}- Milo, are you still high? - 'Really hope so, Dan.'
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.66,0:09:45.61,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拜托你就过来吧 就当这是你为我做的最后一件事\N{\fs38}Just please come over if it's the last thing you ever do for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.94,0:09:51.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这回又是什么事\N{\fs38}What is it this time?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.43,0:09:54.57,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想他是嗑药后产生幻觉了\N{\fs38}I think he's just having a bad trip.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.46,0:09:57.13,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道 我知道\N{\fs38}I know, I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.78,0:09:59.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他没有别的朋友了\N{\fs38}He hasn't got any one else.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.69,0:10:03.05,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是啊 我也觉得他挺可怜的 我真这么觉得 但是\N{\fs38}Yes, and I feel sorry for him, I really do but,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.04,0:10:06.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他可能就是想你过去跟他耍而已\N{\fs38}he probably just wants you to go and hang out with him.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.06,0:10:07.86,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他听起来是真的吓坏了\N{\fs38}He sounded genuinely freaked out.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.43,0:10:10.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那我取消花店的安排喽\N{\fs38}I will cancel the florist, then.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.44,0:10:11.18,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对不起\N{\fs38}I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.34,0:10:22.99,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是Kate的\N{\fs38}Kate's.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.78,0:10:25.32,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,穿的内裤也是她的吧\N{\fs38}You wearing her knickers too, are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.20,0:10:28.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我穿的是男士内裤 Pete 敬请知悉\N{\fs38}I'm wearing man's pants, Pete. FYI.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.50,0:10:36.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,男士内裤\N{\fs38}Man's pants.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.56,0:10:39.56,注释,NTP,0,0,0,,背景音乐 Fad Gadget <Collapsing New People>
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.93,0:11:04.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Danny Danny Danny Danny\N{\fs38}Danny, Danny, Danny, Danny.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.26,0:11:10.58,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 你还好吗  - 嗯\N{\fs38}- You OK? - Mmm.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.91,0:11:13.53,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后你就消失了 但是在此之前\N{\fs38}And then you disappeared, but before that,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.19,0:11:15.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看那儿\N{\fs38}that.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.86,0:11:28.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我去 他是真死了\N{\fs38}Shit! He's really dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.06,0:11:33.15,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- Milo 你做了什么  - 我 不不不 那是你干的\N{\fs38}- Milo, what have you done? - Me? No, no, no, this was you.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.66,0:11:35.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是另一个你干的\N{\fs38}This was the other you.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.88,0:11:40.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,腕带 腕带 另一个你有这么个东西\N{\fs38}The wristband, the wristband! The other you had one of these things
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.03,0:11:42.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那时他就受伤了 然后他就消失了\N{\fs38}and that's when he got damaged and that's when he disappeared.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.20,0:11:44.54,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对不起 兄弟 我管不了这事 太疯狂了\N{\fs38}Sorry, mate, I can't do this, this is crazy school.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.57,0:11:45.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Danny 等等\N{\fs38}Danny, wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.40,0:11:51.96,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我去 你刚做了什么\N{\fs38}Shit! What did you just do?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.98,0:11:54.54,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 我什么都没做啊  - 信息量太大了 Milo\N{\fs38}- I didn't do anything. - This is too much, Milo.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.28,0:11:56.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 你篓子捅大发了  - Danny 等等\N{\fs38}- You've gone too far. - Danny, wait!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.38,0:11:59.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Dan 拜托\N{\fs38}Dan, come on!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.86,0:12:03.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- Dan 你必须帮帮我  - 这是你的烂摊子 Milo\N{\fs38}- Dan, you've got to help me here. - This is YOUR mess, Milo.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.34,0:12:05.61,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是啊 见死不救 你总这么对我\N{\fs38}Yeah, leave me in the shit, like you always do.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.01,0:12:09.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你猜怎么着 我就不管你 因为这是你惹出的麻烦\N{\fs38}Do you know what, I will, because this IS your shit,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.69,0:12:11.07,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你一直就这德行\N{\fs38}just like it always is.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.13,0:12:20.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,操\N{\fs38}Fuck!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.69,0:12:33.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这他妈什么鬼\N{\fs38}What the actual fuck?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.88,0:13:09.58,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Kate\N{\fs38}Kate?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.09,0:13:12.86,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Kate\N{\fs38}Kate?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.74,0:13:31.74,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,噢 天呐 对 对 对 对\N{\fs38}Oh, God. Yes, yes, yes, yes!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.77,0:13:32.36,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fs38}Kate\NKate!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.10,0:13:34.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在干什么\N{\fs38}What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.52,0:13:37.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你又在干嘛\N{\fs38}What are YOU doing?!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.48,0:13:44.40,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还好吗 Milo\N{\fs38}All right, Milo?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.90,0:13:48.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,奶奶\N{\fs38}Gran.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.64,0:13:59.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,嘿 你给我过来\N{\fs38}Hey, come back here!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.16,0:14:00.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我说什么呢\N{\fs38}What did I say?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.96,0:14:02.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我怎么说的 哼\N{\fs38}What did I tell you, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.20,0:14:04.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,给我过来 小样\N{\fs38}Come here, you!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.28,0:14:12.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Milo Milo 开门呀 Milo\N{\fs38}Milo. Milo, open up. Milo!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.83,0:14:13.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Danny\N{\fs38}Danny!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.77,0:14:15.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Milo Milo Milo Milo Milo\N{\fs38}Milo, Milo, Milo, Milo, Milo.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.26,0:14:17.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Danny Danny 说起来好笑\N{\fs38}Danny, Danny. Funny story.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.96,0:14:18.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Milo 你确实做了点儿啥\N{\fs38}Milo, you did something.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.99,0:14:21.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你确实做了 因为我回到家发现Kate\N{\fs38}You did this because I went home and Kate,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.29,0:14:24.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,跟Pete在床上 光着身子 然后\N{\fs38}she was in bed with Pete and they were naked and then...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.88,0:14:26.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们这是在哪儿\N{\fs38}Where are we?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.12,0:14:30.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对吧\N{\fs38}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.72,0:14:36.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,嗯 这肯定是个平行世界 对吧 就像你说的\N{\fs38}Yeah, it must be like a parallel world, yeah? Like you said.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.92,0:14:38.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,另一个你说的\N{\fs38}The other you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.44,0:14:40.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 怎么会 我们怎么会  - 腕带\N{\fs38}- How...? How did we...? - The wristband.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.39,0:14:42.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当我摁下按钮 感觉就好像\N{\fs38}When I pressed the button and it felt like
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.52,0:14:44.47,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,被电击了 肯定是这样的\N{\fs38}we got electrocuted, must've been it.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.47,0:14:46.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你昨晚是不是在我的酒里下了迷幻药\N{\fs38}Did you drop LSD in my drink last night?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.04,0:14:48.35,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,噢 天呐 Danny 我就干了那么一次\N{\fs38}Oh, my God, Danny. I did that one time.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.40,0:14:49.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你能不能别再提了\N{\fs38}Will you shut up about it?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.24,0:14:53.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 那是谁  - 你过来看看\N{\fs38}- Who the hell was that? - Check this out.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.24,0:15:04.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,哎呀 这不是Danny Gates小朋友嘛\N{\fs38}My word, is that little Danny Gates?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.32,0:15:06.83,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,哇好久不见了 你怎么样啊\N{\fs38}Oh, it's been awhile. How are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.00,0:15:10.54,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我很好 谢谢 Milo的奶奶\N{\fs38}Fine, thank you, Milo's gran.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.08,0:15:14.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你还好吗 你看起来真不错 考虑到某事的话\N{\fs38}How are you? You're looking well...considering.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.94,0:15:16.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,噢 我好着呢 谢谢\N{\fs38}Oh, I'm fine, thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.64,0:15:18.28,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她可好着呢\N{\fs38}She is great.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.32,0:15:19.74,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还在烤蛋糕呢\N{\fs38}And baking a cake.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.90,0:15:23.37,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 但是会跟以前一样难吃  - Milo\N{\fs38}- But that'll be shit, like it always is. - Milo.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.00,0:15:26.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你难道不应该正在教堂排练合唱吗\N{\fs38}Well, shouldn't you be at choir practice at the church?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.68,0:15:31.32,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 排练取消了 嗯  - 哦 好吧\N{\fs38}- Got cancelled. Yeah. - Oh, OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.44,0:15:33.50,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 朋友 借一步说话 好吗  - 好\N{\fs38}- Mate, quick word, yeah? - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.74,0:15:35.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,来亲一个 这就对啦\N{\fs38}Hey, stick it. There we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.19,0:15:42.83,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 好 好 就是为了澄清一下 那是你奶奶  - 是啊\N{\fs38}- OK, OK. Just so we're clear, that's your gran? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.86,0:15:46.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 那个七年前过世的奶奶  - 我知道 很棒吧\N{\fs38}- The one that died seven years ago? - I know, it's amazing.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.48,0:15:49.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Danny 我不知道这是怎么回事 也不知道为什么 但确实是她\N{\fs38}I don't know how or why, Danny, but that is her.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.79,0:15:50.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么可能呢\N{\fs38}How is this possible?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.84,0:15:52.36,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一分钟前我还在你家\N{\fs38}One minute we're at your place
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.40,0:15:54.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后你摁下不知什么该死的腕带\N{\fs38}and then you press some bloody wristband and...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.68,0:15:57.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 那个腕带  - 哦不\N{\fs38}- The wristband. - Well, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.44,0:15:59.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Danny Danny\N{\fs38}Danny. Danny.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.62,0:16:02.35,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我过世的奶奶才刚复活呀\N{\fs38}My dead gran just came back to life!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.36,0:16:03.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你就不能\N{\fs38}Can you please just...?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.55,0:16:04.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你干啥\N{\fs38}What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.14,0:16:07.58,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 你走开  - 啊\N{\fs38}- Get off me! - Ah!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.44,0:16:10.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快点\N{\fs38}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.20,0:16:11.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,启动\N{\fs38}Run.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.36,0:16:18.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那可是我们回去的路呀\N{\fs38}That was our way back!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.43,0:16:21.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没信号\N{\fs38}No signal.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.16,0:16:23.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想我的手机套餐服务区\N{\fs38}I guess they don't have a plan that includes
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.68,0:16:25.47,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不在多重现实里 对吧 嗯\N{\fs38}multiple realities, do they? Hmm?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.83,0:16:29.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不行 我们回到家以前你不可以吃饼干\N{\fs38}No. You don't get a biscuit until we get home,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.74,0:16:30.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,尽管我也不知道\N{\fs38}although how the hell we
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.46,0:16:32.25,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有了腕带我们该怎么回家\N{\fs38}do that without the wristband I have no idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.33,0:16:33.20,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以你现在信我了\N{\fs38}So you believe me now?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.56,0:16:35.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你死去的奶奶刚才想塞给我一块消化饼干\N{\fs38}Your dead granny just tried to give me a fucking digestive.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.74,0:16:36.67,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我当然信你了\N{\fs38}Of course I believe you.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.04,0:16:42.91,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以我们是被困在了平行世界\N{\fs38}So we are stuck in a parallel world
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.91,0:16:46.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这里一切事情都变得不同了\N{\fs38}where things have worked out differently.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.88,0:16:48.83,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,嘿\N{\fs38}Hey!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.00,0:16:51.20,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,另一个我有没有恰好提到为什么有人要追杀我们\N{\fs38}Did the other me happen to say why someone's trying to kill us?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.23,0:16:53.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不是特指我俩 是所有的我们\N{\fs38}Not us, specifically. Us, generally.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.92,0:16:56.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,每一个平行世界里的每个我俩\N{\fs38}Every us in every parallel world.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.22,0:16:57.36,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,噢 真令人感到欣慰\N{\fs38}Oh, well, that's reassuring.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.12,0:16:59.61,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,噢 那个杀手 他死之前\N{\fs38}Oh, and then the killer, before he died,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.64,0:17:01.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,说道 "还会有其他人的"\N{\fs38}he said, "There will be others."
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.32,0:17:03.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那就是他的临终遗言\N{\fs38}Those were his last words?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.24,0:17:05.20,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,嗯哼 牛逼的遗言\N{\fs38}Yep. Pretty fucking cool last words.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.24,0:17:06.11,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而我呢 就像这样\N{\fs38}Me, I'd just been like...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.44,0:17:09.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别啊 别 求求你\N{\fs38}Don't, no. Please.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.16,0:17:10.86,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你内心某处还挺享受这一切的 是不是\N{\fs38}Some part of you is enjoying this, isn't it?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.21,0:17:12.49,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还要茶吗\N{\fs38}More tea?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.42,0:17:14.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,奶奶\N{\fs38}Gran...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.92,0:17:18.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你记不记得七年前\N{\fs38}Do you remember, seven years ago,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.06,0:17:19.74,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那次你本来要去一个游轮旅行\N{\fs38}when you were supposed to go on that cruise?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.80,0:17:22.25,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,哦天呐 我怎么会不记得\N{\fs38}Oh, God, do I remember?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.76,0:17:26.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,错过那趟游轮是我这辈子遇到最好的事情\N{\fs38}Missing that cruise was the best thing that ever happened to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.56,0:17:29.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果我的闹钟真的按时响了 \N{\fs38}If my alarm had gone off like it was meant to,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.72,0:17:31.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我今天就不会坐在这儿了\N{\fs38}I wouldn't be here today.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.80,0:17:35.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那谁来照顾我的小抱抱先生呢\N{\fs38}And then who'd look after my little Mr Cuddles?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.74,0:17:37.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,噢 奶奶\N{\fs38}Oh, Gran.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.42,0:17:39.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抱抱先生 哇哦\N{\fs38}Mr Cuddles? Wow.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.76,0:17:41.87,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Danny 你过得怎么样啊\N{\fs38}So, how are you, Danny?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.96,0:17:44.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我几个月前碰见了你妈妈\N{\fs38}I saw your mum a few months ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.04,0:17:46.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她说你在拉克汉姆保险工作\N{\fs38}She said you were at Larkham's Insurance?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.51,0:17:47.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是啊\N{\fs38}Yeah, I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.69,0:17:51.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是喔 我在那里工作\N{\fs38}Yes...I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.62,0:17:55.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我肯定在那里工作啊 因为如果这是平行世界\N{\fs38}Of course I am because if this is a parallel world
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.66,0:17:58.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这里应该有另一个我 另一对我俩\N{\fs38}then there is another me, another us.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.41,0:18:00.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对啊 对啊 这就是我们离开的办法\N{\fs38}Yes, yes! That's our way out of here!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.80,0:18:03.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我还是跟着他吧\N{\fs38}I better go after him.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.15,0:18:06.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 你要想开我的车就去开吧  - 谢谢\N{\fs38}- You can take my car if you want. - Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.40,0:18:10.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,奶奶 能再见到你真的太好了\N{\fs38}It's really good to see you again, Gran.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.07,0:18:13.07,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亲爱的 我每天都见你啊\N{\fs38}I see you every day, love.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.18,0:18:19.10,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你看 另一个我说有人要追杀我们\N{\fs38}Look, other me said that people were trying to kill us
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.13,0:18:19.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而且还有其他人\N{\fs38}and there will be others.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.95,0:18:22.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果有人要追杀这个世界里的我们呢\N{\fs38}What if someone comes for the versions of us in this reality?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.48,0:18:23.58,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们或许会有那个腕带\N{\fs38}They might have those wristband things.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.58,0:18:25.40,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拿到他们的腕带 我们就能回家\N{\fs38}We grab their wristbands, we go home.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.84,0:18:27.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,从挥着巨剑的家伙手里逃出来\N{\fs38}Off the guys with the big swords?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.88,0:18:38.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我在那儿 还活着\N{\fs38}There I am, still alive.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.32,0:18:50.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 太奇怪了  - 是啊\N{\fs38}- This is so weird. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.16,0:18:54.67,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是我的原因 还是这个你看起来有点二逼\N{\fs38}Is it just me or does other you look like a bit of a twat?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.64,0:18:57.74,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道啥呀 保险业可是高风险工种\N{\fs38}Do you know what? Insurance is high-stakes stuff.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.76,0:18:59.08,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他压力很大的\N{\fs38}He's under a lot of pressure.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.12,0:19:02.86,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 猫咪保险  - 宠物保险\N{\fs38}- Cat insurance. - Pet insurance.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.40,0:19:07.37,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,噢 傻逼Paul\N{\fs38}Oh, fucking Paul.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.28,0:19:13.20,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那是什么鬼\N{\fs38}What is that?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.15,0:19:16.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们的计划是什么\N{\fs38}So what is the plan here?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.91,0:19:19.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们告诉另一个我 出了什么事 将要出什么事 \N{\fs38}We tell the other me what's going on, what's about to happen,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.20,0:19:20.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后我们三个去找另一个你\N{\fs38}then the three of us go and find the other you.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.84,0:19:23.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后 如果有人出现要杀我们 嘭\N{\fs38}Then, if someone turns up trying to kill us, bam.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.80,0:19:25.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 嘭  - 对啊\N{\fs38}- Bam? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.23,0:19:26.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 什么意思  - 就是\N{\fs38}- What does that mean? - You know,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.56,0:19:29.98,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,嘭的一声 拿下他 之类的\N{\fs38}bam. Take him out, kind of thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.01,0:19:32.20,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凭借我们多年来的近身格斗训练 当然\N{\fs38}With the aid of our years of close combat training, of course!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.24,0:19:34.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,至少我还在这里想办法让我们回去\N{\fs38}At least I'm trying to do something to get us back.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.03,0:19:35.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而且都怪你我们才会在这\N{\fs38}And since it's your fault
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.04,0:19:36.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这样如何 你端正态度\N{\fs38}that we're even here, how about you lose
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.46,0:19:39.37,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,给我协助 而不是当个窝囊废\N{\fs38}the attitude and help me, instead of being a useless bastard?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.39,0:19:42.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,窝囊废 噢 真抱歉我不像Paul一样\N{\fs38}Useless. Oh, I'm sorry I'm not like Paul.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.24,0:19:43.47,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不是吧 你还在生气伴郎的事\N{\fs38}Really, the best man thing?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.50,0:19:44.83,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你现在想跟我吵那事 是吗\N{\fs38}You want to get into that now, do you?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.84,0:19:46.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是啊 Paul不会把你困在平行世界里\N{\fs38}Yeah, Paul wouldn't strand you in a parallel universe.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.72,0:19:47.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Paul能当伴郎是因为\N{\fs38}Paul is my best man because
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.88,0:19:50.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他真心喜欢Kate而且Kate也喜欢他\N{\fs38}he actually likes Kate and she likes him.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.08,0:19:52.96,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,跟他聊个五分钟 我就想去上吊了\N{\fs38}Five minutes talking to him and I literally want to hang myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.00,0:19:55.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我现在跟你说话 就让我想去上吊\N{\fs38}This conversation makes me want to hang myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.36,0:19:59.50,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你真的\N{\fs38}I mean, are you actually
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.52,0:20:01.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,愿意起身为我和Kate致辞\N{\fs38}saying to me that you would like to get up
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.08,0:20:03.87,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,表达你为我们感到开心吗\N{\fs38}and do a speech about how happy you are for me and Kate?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.83,0:20:07.55,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 这不是关键  - Milo 这就是关键 因为\N{\fs38}- That is not the point. - Yes, Milo, it actually is because...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.26,0:20:12.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,老天爷\N{\fs38}Sweet Jesus.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.96,0:20:14.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,噢 天呐\N{\fs38}Oh, God.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.24,0:20:19.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,噢 操 操 操 操\N{\fs38}Oh, fuck. Fuck, fuck, fuck.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.24,0:20:22.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,嘿\N{\fs38}Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.32,0:20:24.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,嘿 我\N{\fs38}Hey...me.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.48,0:20:26.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我现在是灵魂出窍了吗\N{\fs38}Am I having an out-of-body experience?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.84,0:20:28.86,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我 我是死了吗\N{\fs38}Am...? Am I dead?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.04,0:20:33.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道这他妈非常诡异\N{\fs38}I know this is really fucking weird.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.04,0:20:37.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是你 但是来自另一个现实\N{\fs38}I'm you, but from an alternate reality.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.71,0:20:39.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你是来带我去来世的吗\N{\fs38}Are you here to take me to the afterlife?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.19,0:20:41.28,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是这样吗\N{\fs38}Is that what's happening?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.99,0:20:46.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,嗯 是啊\N{\fs38}Yeah, why not?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.48,0:20:49.79,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉Kate我爱她\N{\fs38}Tell Kate I love her.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.85,0:20:56.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,噢 天呐 我 我死了\N{\fs38}Oh, God. I'm I'm dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.48,0:20:59.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么有人想杀掉每一个版本的我们\N{\fs38}Why would someone want to kill every version of us?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.08,0:21:00.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们到底有什么特别之处\N{\fs38}What is so special about us?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.00,0:21:03.71,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 抓住他的腿  - 什么\N{\fs38}- Take his legs. - Excuse me?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.82,0:21:05.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抬起他的腿 好吗 我们得把他塞进后备箱\N{\fs38}Take his legs, yeah? We need to put him in the boot.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.22,0:21:07.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果有人发现了他的尸体 然后又看见你走来走去\N{\fs38}If someone finds his body and then sees you walking around
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.85,0:21:08.91,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大活人一个\N{\fs38}being all alive and shit,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.91,0:21:10.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,人们就会开始问问题了\N{\fs38}people are going to start asking questions.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.14,0:21:11.40,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抬起他的腿\N{\fs38}Take the legs.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.40,0:21:16.54,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 你为什么这么冷静  - 如果这是嗑药后的幻觉\N{\fs38}- Why are you so calm? - If this is a trip,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.56,0:21:18.28,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那就是史上最糟糕的一次\N{\fs38}this is the worst one ever.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.48,0:21:20.25,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在不是开玩笑的时候 Milo\N{\fs38}This is not the time for jokes, Milo.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.88,0:21:28.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我还那么年轻\N{\fs38}I was so young.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.64,0:21:41.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,行了 总会想出办法的\N{\fs38}It's all right. We'll sort something out.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.20,0:21:44.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还有更糟糕的地方被困住呢\N{\fs38}There are worse places to be stuck.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.20,0:21:47.61,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,比方说伊拉克 多糟糕\N{\fs38}I mean, Iraq. That's supposed to be pretty shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.19,0:21:50.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我肯定它也有好的地方 但是整体来说不怎么样\N{\fs38}I'm sure it has its nice parts but, overall, not great.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.84,0:21:54.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 闭嘴吧 Milo 你就闭嘴吧  - 你这人怎么回事\N{\fs38}- Shut up, Milo. Please just shut up. - What is up with you?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.24,0:21:55.38,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你这人怎么回事 你\N{\fs38}What is up with you?! You...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.58,0:21:57.07,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你说得好像想留在这儿一样\N{\fs38}You're talking like you want to stay here.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.32,0:21:59.95,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这可不是做梦啊 Milo 我们可能永远回不了家了\N{\fs38}This is real, Milo. We might never get home.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.40,0:22:01.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要见Kate\N{\fs38}I need to see Kate.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.17,0:22:03.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 为什么  - 另一个我的\N{\fs38}- But why? - The other me's
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.45,0:22:05.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,临终遗愿就是告诉Kate他爱她\N{\fs38}last wishes was to tell Kate that he loved her--
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.50,0:22:07.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 我应该尊重他的遗愿  - 这是疯子言论\N{\fs38}- I should honor that. - That's crazy talking.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.16,0:22:09.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你吓坏了只是因为你看着自己死掉了\N{\fs38}You're just freaked out because you saw yourself die.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.80,0:22:11.85,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Milo 我要去 这是我欠自己的\N{\fs38}I'm going, Milo. I owe it to myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.90,0:22:13.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果我最终被捅死在这里\N{\fs38}If I end up getting stabbed here,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.56,0:22:14.36,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我希望\N{\fs38}I'd like to think that
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.40,0:22:16.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,另一个版本的我将会尊重我的意思\N{\fs38}another version of me would do me the respect
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.72,0:22:18.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉我这个版本的Kate 我\N{\fs38}of telling my version of Kate that I,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.67,0:22:20.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,也就是这个版本的Danny 很爱她\N{\fs38}this version of Danny, loved her.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.08,0:22:24.41,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 完全晕了 朋友 你在说啥\N{\fs38}- Completely lost me, mate. What are you saying?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.84,0:22:26.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 谢谢你毁掉我的人生\N{\fs38}- Thanks for ruining my life.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.24,0:22:30.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,计划怎么办 救另外一个我怎么办\N{\fs38}What about the plan? What about saving the other me?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.45,0:22:33.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧 去变你的帽子戏法吧 朋友\N{\fs38}Fine. Yeah, go for the hat-trick, mate.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.00,0:22:35.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一天死三个Danny\N{\fs38}Three Dannys dying in one day.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.84,0:22:36.46,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,加油啊\N{\fs38}Go for it.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.32,0:22:39.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看我在不在乎\N{\fs38}See if I care.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.20,0:22:42.40,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那就我自己去救自己喽\N{\fs38}I'll go and save myself then.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.05,0:23:07.47,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,*神造七彩羽翼衣裳*\N{\fs38}*Glowing colors*
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.04,0:23:07.47,注释,NTP,0,0,0,,赞美诗 <神造万物美丽>
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.47,0:23:11.98,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,*随意翱翔乘风飞*\N{\fs38}*He made their tiny wings*
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.41,0:23:16.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,*人世中万物美丽*\N{\fs38}*All things bright and beautiful*
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.24,0:23:20.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,*大小生物尽见珍奇*\N{\fs38}*All creatures great and small*
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.07,0:23:24.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,*人世中设计精美*\N{\fs38}*All things wise and wonderful*
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.90,0:23:28.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,*神创造世尘所有*\N{\fs38}*The Lord God made them all*
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.40,0:23:30.41,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢大家\N{\fs38}Thank you, everyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.24,0:23:50.20,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,嘘 别喊了\N{\fs38}Shh. Stop it.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.88,0:23:51.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,冷静点\N{\fs38}Just calm down.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.08,0:23:56.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,嘘 镇定一点 没事儿的\N{\fs38}Shh. Just calm down. It's nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.52,0:23:58.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不用害怕\N{\fs38}It's nothing to worry about.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.28,0:24:02.41,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别喊了 停下来 别喊了\N{\fs38}Stop it. Stop that! Stop it.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.60,0:24:11.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,打住 打住\N{\fs38}Stop it. Stop it.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.28,0:24:14.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,冷静一点 帅 衰哥\N{\fs38}Just calm down, handsome...ish.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.44,0:24:16.94,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,上帝行事神秘\N{\fs38}God works in mysterious ways.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.96,0:24:18.67,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,必定是他派你考验我\N{\fs38}He sent you here to test me.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.72,0:24:21.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,老兄 我知道这事儿很诡异\N{\fs38}Dude, I know how weird this all is.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:21.34,0:24:22.32,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但你看 我现在在这儿\N{\fs38}But look, now I'm here,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:22.62,0:24:25.42,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我觉得我应该警告你 你有危险\N{\fs38}I feel like it's only right to warn you that you are in danger.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:25.85,0:24:27.58,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么样的危险\N{\fs38}What kind of danger?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:28.72,0:24:30.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那样的危险 跑啊\N{\fs38}That danger! Run!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:36.46,0:24:37.20,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快点\N{\fs38}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:40.59,0:24:41.42,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,跟上\N{\fs38}Come on!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:48.27,0:24:49.32,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快啊 上车\N{\fs38}Quick, get in!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:49.80,0:24:51.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他要干什么\N{\fs38}What is he doing?!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:52.33,0:24:53.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,真是伟大的计划啊 Danny\N{\fs38}Great plan, Danny!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:56.62,0:24:59.18,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们应该怎么从他那里拿到腕带啊朋友\N{\fs38}How are we supposed to get the wristband from that, mate?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:00.06,0:25:03.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别哭啦 老实说 你很丢我们的脸诶\N{\fs38}Stop crying. Honestly, you're embarrassing us.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:17.44,0:25:18.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Kate 你好\N{\fs38}Kate, hi.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:19.36,0:25:22.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- Danny  - 早上的事我真的 很抱歉\N{\fs38}- Danny. - I'm really...sorry about this morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:22.49,0:25:24.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道一时半会解释不完\N{\fs38}I know it's a lot to explain
Dialogue: 0,0:25:24.09,0:25:26.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而且你可能不会相信我\N{\fs38}and you probably wouldn't believe me if I did...
Dialogue: 0,0:25:26.12,0:25:29.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是 我需要和你谈谈\N{\fs38}but...I need to speak to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:30.82,0:25:31.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你当然得谈\N{\fs38}Of course you do.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:37.29,0:25:41.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Danny 今天早上你的确 做得挺不对的\N{\fs38}Danny, this morning was really quite inappropriate.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:41.26,0:25:42.40,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我 我很抱歉\N{\fs38}I'm...I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:42.45,0:25:43.53,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只是\N{\fs38}Er...j-just...
Dialogue: 0,0:25:44.80,0:25:47.05,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我必须得说 我爱你\N{\fs38}I had to say that I love you.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.06,0:25:50.50,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,实际上 说出来感觉真好\N{\fs38}Feels good, actually.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:50.64,0:25:51.98,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当我知道自己发生了什么事情之后\N{\fs38}Knowing that if anything happens to me,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:52.03,0:25:54.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,起码其他几个版本的你知道\N{\fs38}at least some version of you knows...
Dialogue: 0,0:25:57.28,0:25:59.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Danny 我知道\N{\fs38}Danny, I know...
Dialogue: 0,0:25:59.93,0:26:00.89,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你爱我\N{\fs38}that you love me.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:01.64,0:26:04.95,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你每个星期都给我寄卡片 上面写着"我爱你"\N{\fs38}You send me a card every week that says, "I love you."
Dialogue: 0,0:26:06.10,0:26:09.39,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我已经想不出别的办法告诉你 你不是我的菜\N{\fs38}And I'm running out of ways to tell you that I am not interested.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:11.12,0:26:13.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Pete是我老公\N{\fs38}Pete is my husband.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:13.83,0:26:16.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 我真的很开心 行吗  - 真的假的 和Pete\N{\fs38}- I'm happy. OK? - Really? With Pete?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:16.67,0:26:19.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总有一天 你也会找到你自己的"Pete"\N{\fs38}One day, maybe you'll find a Pete of your own.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:19.80,0:26:22.83,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 一个让你生命完整的人  - 但你就是我的"Pete"啊\N{\fs38}- Someone to make you whole. - But you are my Pete.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:22.92,0:26:23.79,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我很抱歉\N{\fs38}I'm sorry...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:24.03,0:26:24.79,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你的人生没有\N{\fs38}that your life hasn't
Dialogue: 0,0:26:24.79,0:26:27.36,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,和你预想的轨迹一致 但是\N{\fs38}panned out the way you thought it would. But...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:27.58,0:26:29.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你个死变态\N{\fs38}You fucking pervert!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:30.21,0:26:31.05,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等等 等等 等等 我\N{\fs38}Wait, wait, wait! I...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:34.11,0:26:34.87,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,啊\N{\fs38}Ah!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:36.19,0:26:36.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,给我回来\N{\fs38}Come back!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:37.43,0:26:40.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,过来啊 过来和我打一架\N{\fs38}Come 'ere! I want it out with you!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:40.76,0:26:43.95,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,都三次了 你个死变态\N{\fs38}Three timing...pervert!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:46.11,0:26:47.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我跟着你 这样行了吧\N{\fs38}I'm going to stick with you, OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:47.77,0:26:50.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你只要解释清楚为什么会有两个我\N{\fs38}You just have to explain why there's two of us.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:52.33,0:26:53.91,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧 行\N{\fs38}OK. Right.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:54.53,0:26:55.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要和奶奶谈一谈\N{\fs38}I'm going to go and have a chat with Gran,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:55.76,0:26:58.62,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,试这把平行宇宙这事讲清楚\N{\fs38}try and lay the ground for this whole parallel universe thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:58.67,0:26:59.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,行了 行了 我知道了\N{\fs38}OK, OK, I get you.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:59.61,0:27:03.55,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不要去太久 因为 我 我 害怕\N{\fs38}Don't be long because I'm... I'm...scared.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:04.41,0:27:07.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 这 你父母也走了吗  - 嗯\N{\fs38}- Did... Did your parents leave, too? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:08.52,0:27:11.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们之前说一周之后就会回来 最后还是没回来\N{\fs38}They said they'd come back in a week but they never did.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:11.87,0:27:14.85,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后奶奶错过了闹钟 是神的旨意吧\N{\fs38}And when Gran missed that alarm, it was an act of God.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:16.54,0:27:18.01,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 是闹钟设计有问题吧  - 嗯\N{\fs38}- Or bad alarm clock design. - Erm...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:18.36,0:27:20.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢天谢地 她没有到赶上那个游轮\N{\fs38}Thanks to Jesus, she never got on that cruise.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:21.32,0:27:22.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后我就是这样找到了我的信仰\N{\fs38}And that's how I found my faith.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:23.72,0:27:25.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为了感谢上帝饶她一命\N{\fs38}To thank him for sparing her.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:26.62,0:27:27.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当然了\N{\fs38}Of Course you did.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:40.41,0:27:43.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 嗯 噢  - 干嘛呀这是\N{\fs38}- Mmm. Ooh. What's all this?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:43.53,0:27:45.06,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 你一直都对我这么好 奶奶\N{\fs38}- You've always been so good to me, Gran.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:45.81,0:27:47.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在我需要你的时候你都在我身边\N{\fs38}Always there when I needed you.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:47.71,0:27:49.83,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你也一样啊\N{\fs38}And so have you for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:50.60,0:27:53.89,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们只需要彼此就够了 小抱抱先生\N{\fs38}All we need is each other, Mr Cuddles.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:54.23,0:27:56.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这就是为什么我心里觉得很奇怪\N{\fs38}Which is why I'm a bit confused,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:56.12,0:27:59.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当我看见你和小Danny又走在一起的时候\N{\fs38}seeing you take up again with little Danny Gates.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:59.17,0:28:01.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那 他是我朋友嘛\N{\fs38}Well, he's my friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:03.26,0:28:07.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,曾经是吧 不管怎么样 他现在有Paul了 天知道还有谁呢\N{\fs38}He was, anyway. Now he's got Paul, so who knows any more?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:08.78,0:28:11.87,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 不管了  - 你什么时候开始需要朋友的\N{\fs38}- Anyway... - Since when did you need friends?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:12.38,0:28:14.94,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这么多年以来 只有我和你而已\N{\fs38}All these years, just you and me.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:15.73,0:28:17.39,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,难道我还不能满足你吗\N{\fs38}Am I not enough for you?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:18.67,0:28:21.15,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,额 我听不懂 你在说什么\N{\fs38}Erm, I don't understand. What are you talking about?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:21.15,0:28:23.91,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,得了吧 还有谁 小抱抱先生\N{\fs38}Well, who else is there, Mr Cuddles?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:25.51,0:28:27.74,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还有谁会对你这样做啊\N{\fs38}Who else does this to you?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:28.28,0:28:30.38,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,奶奶 你在干什么 奶奶\N{\fs38}Gran! What are you doing? Gran!
Dialogue: 0,0:28:30.48,0:28:32.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,过来\N{\fs38}Come here!
Dialogue: 0,0:28:36.75,0:28:39.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我觉得我现在就想回家 就想现在回\N{\fs38}I think I want to go home now. I think I want to go home now.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:39.24,0:28:41.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不 不 不 不啊\N{\fs38}No, no, no. NO!
Dialogue: 0,0:28:53.38,0:28:54.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,哪 你去那里\N{\fs38} Where... Where you going?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:54.97,0:28:56.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要离开这个鬼地方\N{\fs38} I'm getting the hell out of Chinatown.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:56.43,0:28:58.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,里面那个女人不是我奶奶\N{\fs38}That woman in there is not my gran.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:58.20,0:29:00.25,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她还想跟我舌吻\N{\fs38}She tried to stick her tongue down my throat.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:00.25,0:29:02.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,想起她说的话 我一辈子都得做噩梦\N{\fs38}She said things to me that are going to haunt me for ever.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:02.19,0:29:05.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她只是糊涂了而已 以为我是小抱抱先生\N{\fs38}She gets confused. She thinks I'm Mr Cuddles.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:05.09,0:29:06.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 她就是这样叫爷爷的  - 啥时候开始的\N{\fs38}- That's what she used to call Grandad. - Since when?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:06.84,0:29:08.40,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我奶奶从来都不说什么小抱抱先生\N{\fs38}My grandma never said anything about Mr Cuddles.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:08.40,0:29:09.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,性伴称呼而已\N{\fs38}It's a sex name.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:09.63,0:29:10.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,啥\N{\fs38}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:11.46,0:29:12.86,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 我觉得我要吐了  - 我们没搞过全套\N{\fs38}- I think I'm going to be sick. - We don't go all the way!
Dialogue: 0,0:29:12.86,0:29:15.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 醒醒吧  - 说好你要保护我的\N{\fs38}- Get a grip, man! - You've got to protect me.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:16.51,0:29:19.85,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 你要自己振作起来  - 好\N{\fs38}- You need to...stand up for yourself. - OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:19.87,0:29:21.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,像个男子汉一样 Milo 天哪\N{\fs38}Be a man, Milo. God.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:21.63,0:29:23.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,老爸老妈死的时候 我身边没有别人\N{\fs38}When Mum and Dad left, I didn't have anyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:23.21,0:29:23.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只有奶奶\N{\fs38}Grandma was it.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:23.68,0:29:25.86,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 我没有朋友  - 那Danny呢\N{\fs38}- I didn't have any friends. - What about Danny?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:26.04,0:29:27.71,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Gates 我们有段时间是最好的朋友\N{\fs38}Gates? We were BFFs for a while,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:27.77,0:29:30.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 但是之后他就和Paul玩了  - Paul\N{\fs38}- but then he started hanging out with this kid Paul. - Paul!
Dialogue: 0,0:29:30.04,0:29:31.98,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所有Danny现在只想和Paul一样\N{\fs38}And Now Danny just wants to be like Paul.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:31.98,0:29:33.32,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以你很孤独\N{\fs38}So, so you're lonely.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:33.32,0:29:34.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你和你唯一的亲人\N{\fs38}You get in a co-dependent relationship
Dialogue: 0,0:29:34.65,0:29:35.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,孤苦相依\N{\fs38}with the only living relative,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:35.81,0:29:38.36,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当知道她死里逃生后 你就投奔了上帝\N{\fs38}then you find Jesus when said relative fails to die
Dialogue: 0,0:29:38.38,0:29:40.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有时她会把你错认成她死去的老公\N{\fs38}and sometimes she confuses you for her dead husband.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:40.65,0:29:41.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不明白的是为什么\N{\fs38}What I don't get is is why,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:41.64,0:29:43.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么会 你怎么会任由她对你这样做\N{\fs38}how? How do you let her do that to you?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:45.04,0:29:47.18,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 这很好啊  - 我擦 你说什么\N{\fs38}- It's nice. - Fuck me! What?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:47.84,0:29:48.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们没有搞过全套啊\N{\fs38}We don't go all the way.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:48.97,0:29:51.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,操你大爷 真是日了狗了\N{\fs38}Fuck you, Jesus Christ!
Dialogue: 0,0:29:52.99,0:29:54.35,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,去你妈的平行宇宙\N{\fs38}Damn parallel universes.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:54.36,0:29:55.98,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我告诉你 等我回家了 Milo\N{\fs38}I tell you what, when I get home, Milo,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:56.05,0:29:57.41,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我就把运营商换掉\N{\fs38}I'm changing my provider.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:57.60,0:30:00.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 你想要打给谁  - 我死党\N{\fs38}- Who are you trying to get hold of? - My best friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:00.94,0:30:01.98,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不能没有他来帮我\N{\fs38}I can't do this without him.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:08.04,0:30:09.05,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,站直走\N{\fs38}Walk upright!
Dialogue: 0,0:30:24.14,0:30:27.54,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 喂喂 你干嘛  - 我拿外套 有点冷\N{\fs38}- Whoa! What are you doing? - I need my coat. I'm chilly.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:27.93,0:30:29.18,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,奶奶不想我感冒\N{\fs38}Grandma wouldn't want me catching cold.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:29.68,0:30:31.20,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你会宁愿得感冒也不想看见里面有啥\N{\fs38}You'd rather catch a cold than see what's in there.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:31.20,0:30:32.40,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,相信我 走吧\N{\fs38}Trust me. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:33.02,0:30:34.86,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你还想活着 那就跟我来\N{\fs38}If you want to stay alive, come with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:57.58,0:30:58.32,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拿点啤酒来\N{\fs38}Get the beers in.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:03.42,0:31:06.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,给你一个好消息 我现在也想回去了\N{\fs38}Well, you'll be happy to know that I also want to go home now.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:06.41,0:31:06.99,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么了\N{\fs38}What's up?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:08.82,0:31:10.36,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在这个时空 Kate和我是没有结果的\N{\fs38}In this one, Kate and me never went out.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:10.77,0:31:11.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,唉\N{\fs38}Ah!
Dialogue: 0,0:31:11.83,0:31:13.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,另一个我感觉像个混球\N{\fs38}The other me sounds like a total dickhead.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:13.32,0:31:15.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Kate超级喜欢Pete\N{\fs38}Kate's so happy with Pete.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:15.45,0:31:16.71,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她好像换了个人似的\N{\fs38}It's like she was a different woman.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:18.67,0:31:21.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道 我只是 我老觉得我们会\N{\fs38}I don't know... I just... I always thought that we would...
Dialogue: 0,0:31:23.60,0:31:24.32,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我也不知道\N{\fs38}I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:25.60,0:31:29.10,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 想知道为什么一切都不一样吗  - 说\N{\fs38}- Want to know why everything turned out so differently? - Go on.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:29.86,0:31:32.18,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我和你 从来不是朋友\N{\fs38}Me and you. Never friends.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:32.59,0:31:34.46,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在这个空间 你和Paul是死党\N{\fs38}Not here. You were best mates with Paul.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:34.63,0:31:36.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以 我是没和你做朋友才让我\N{\fs38}So you're saying, not being friends with you turned me
Dialogue: 0,0:31:36.24,0:31:38.86,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 变成一个自私又无聊的混蛋  - 正确\N{\fs38}- into a selfish, boring arsehole? - Correct.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:39.01,0:31:41.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我就变成了那个人\N{\fs38}And me into that guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:42.33,0:31:43.49,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 看见他了吗  - 哇哦 \N{\fs38}- See him? - Wow
Dialogue: 0,0:31:43.51,0:31:46.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,面对现实吧 哥们 我们天生一对\N{\fs38}Yeah. Face it, pal, we are good for each other.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:46.57,0:31:50.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你可能会说 来摸摸看 当伴郎的材料啊\N{\fs38}You might say feel that, feel it, feel it best man material.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:50.63,0:31:51.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,噢 你滚吧\N{\fs38}Oh, fuck off.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:51.45,0:31:52.99,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 哈哈  - 滚\N{\fs38}- Haha! - Fuck off!
Dialogue: 0,0:32:01.81,0:32:03.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,噢 我的\N{\fs38}Oh! Ma...
Dialogue: 0,0:32:05.35,0:32:06.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,噢 妈呀\N{\fs38}Oh, my word!
Dialogue: 0,0:32:07.01,0:32:09.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,噢 见 鬼 啦\N{\fs38}Oh, bloody...hell!
Dialogue: 0,0:32:19.72,0:32:23.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,呃 警察同志 我有 额 噢 麻烦了\N{\fs38}Er, police. I've got...er... Oh, crumbs.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:24.10,0:32:27.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我朋友 我基友 我的 额 \N{\fs38}My buddy, my main man, my er...
Dialogue: 0,0:32:27.65,0:32:31.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我老友 额 我的得力助手\N{\fs38}My homie... Er, my right-hand pal.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:31.07,0:32:33.74,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他 他 死了 他死了\N{\fs38}He's... Well...he's dead. He's dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:43.69,0:32:46.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 放开他们  - 他干嘛呀  - 他要变男子汉了\N{\fs38}- Leave them alone! - What's he doing? - Standing up for himself.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:46.78,0:32:47.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我教他的\N{\fs38}I taught him that.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:49.55,0:32:52.40,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 噢 那不是我教的  - 行了 跑跑跑跑跑\N{\fs38}- Oh! I didn't teach him that! - OK, go, go, go, go, go!
Dialogue: 0,0:32:59.13,0:33:00.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天国的阶梯\N{\fs38}Stairway To Heaven!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:19.32,0:33:21.39,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 哈 哈  - 我去\N{\fs38}- Ha-ha! - Damn!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:21.56,0:33:23.36,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,耶 谢谢你 谢谢你\N{\fs38}Yes! Thank you! Thank you,
Dialogue: 0,0:33:23.36,0:33:26.50,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你这个连楼梯都修不起的破酒吧\N{\fs38}you shitty local pub for being too cheap to fix your steps.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:26.50,0:33:29.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我找到一条腕带 这个或许更好使\N{\fs38}I have got a wristand. Maybe this one'll work better.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:29.53,0:33:31.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我很肯定他进来的时候 按了这个按钮\N{\fs38}I'm sure he came in, he was pressing that button.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:31.56,0:33:33.40,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 不是 是这个  - 他按了绿色那个  - Danny\N{\fs38}- No... It's this one. - He pressed the green one. - Danny...
Dialogue: 0,0:33:37.57,0:33:39.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这特么是闹哪样\N{\fs38}What... What the f....flipping hell's going on, man?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:40.62,0:33:44.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是 是 逼真的恶作剧吗\N{\fs38}Is this, like, some kind of like weirdly convincing gag?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:45.00,0:33:48.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 操你个Paul  - 我刚刚才报了警 朋友\N{\fs38}- Fucking Paul! - I just called the police, amigo.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:48.49,0:33:49.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我意思是 警察快来了\N{\fs38}I mean, the rozzers are en route.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:49.93,0:33:52.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以 如果你们要这么搞 多半应该先让我知道\N{\fs38}So, if you guys could tell us... you should probably let me know
Dialogue: 0,0:33:52.64,0:33:53.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 噢 我的天\N{\fs38}- OH! My God!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:55.36,0:33:58.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,啊 啊 天哪 救命啊\N{\fs38}Oh, Oh, my God! Help!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:06.22,0:34:08.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,第一条 一定要确认他们真死了\N{\fs38}Rule number one. Always check they're actually dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:09.47,0:34:10.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这个不是这里的Kate吧\N{\fs38}This isn't the Kate from here?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:10.78,0:34:13.07,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 不是  - 所以是另一个kate咯\N{\fs38}- No. - So, it's like another Kate?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:13.61,0:34:14.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她穿皮衣真好看\N{\fs38}She looks nice in leather.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:15.19,0:34:16.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 你有没有见过我的Danny  - 哪一个\N{\fs38}- Have you seen my Danny? - Which one?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:16.68,0:34:18.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 他带着这样的腕带  - 你的Danny 对 对\N{\fs38}- He's wearing a wristband like this. - Your Danny! Yes! Yes!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:18.91,0:34:21.85,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他 他被人捅了之后就消失了\N{\fs38}He...got stabbed and then he disappeared.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:21.87,0:34:24.06,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 那 他还活着吗  - 我不知道啊 不知道\N{\fs38}- Well, is he still alive? - I don't know. I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:25.28,0:34:26.11,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,"谢谢"你啥也不知道\N{\fs38}Thanks for nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:27.17,0:34:28.74,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,慢着 慢着 你可以帮我们离开吗\N{\fs38}Wait, wait. Can you help us get home?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:28.96,0:34:29.58,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不是我要找的人\N{\fs38}You're not my problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:29.58,0:34:32.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拜托了 告诉我们这是什么情况就行\N{\fs38}Please, just tell us what the hell is going on here.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:32.17,0:34:34.39,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这个想杀我们的疯子是谁\N{\fs38}Who is this crazy bastard trying to kill us?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:35.85,0:34:37.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亲爱的 是我啊\N{\fs38}Baby...it's me.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:37.93,0:34:42.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 噢 噢  - 我不是你家Kate\N{\fs38}- Ooh. Oooh. - I'm not your Kate.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:42.88,0:34:44.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有一件事你们两个都要知道\N{\fs38}There's something you both need to understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:44.36,0:34:45.47,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们不是独一无二的\N{\fs38}You're not special.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:45.69,0:34:47.20,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,实际上 有成千上亿个\N{\fs38}There are literally millions
Dialogue: 0,0:34:47.24,0:34:49.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,其他的你们在别的世界\N{\fs38}of other worlds with millions of other yous.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:49.48,0:34:51.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们是特别的 你的Danny告诉我们的\N{\fs38}We are special. Your Danny told us
Dialogue: 0,0:34:51.65,0:34:54.49,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而且这个人一直追杀我们 所以\N{\fs38}we were and this guy keeps trying to kill us, so...
Dialogue: 0,0:34:54.60,0:34:57.53,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你最好低下你的狗头\N{\fs38}The best you can do is keep your fucking heads down
Dialogue: 0,0:34:57.65,0:34:59.36,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,祈祷没人发现你们吧\N{\fs38}and hope to hell that nobody notices you.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:01.19,0:35:02.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,母老虎啊\N{\fs38}So rude.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:03.14,0:35:04.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她穿皮衣真的很好看\N{\fs38}She looked really good in leather.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:04.84,0:35:05.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,兄弟 不是我说\N{\fs38}Mate, not to hammer the point home
Dialogue: 0,0:35:05.88,0:35:07.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是你未婚妻真混蛋啊\N{\fs38}but your fiancee is kind of a dick.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:07.66,0:35:11.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她不是我的Kate 我的现在在家等我们\N{\fs38}She's not my Kate. My Kate is at home waiting for us.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:11.16,0:35:14.06,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以 赶紧离开然后回到我们的世界吧\N{\fs38}So, let's just get out of here and get back to our lives.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:14.87,0:35:16.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你干嘛呢 我们拿着腕带了\N{\fs38}What are you doing? We've got the wristband.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:16.71,0:35:18.85,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这人身上也许有任务指示什么的\N{\fs38}Maybe this guy has got some instructions on him, or something.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:19.61,0:35:21.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,嗯 因为那个满宇宙跑的家伙\N{\fs38}Yeah. Because the guy travelling through alternate universes
Dialogue: 0,0:35:21.70,0:35:23.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,随时带着任务手册 好想法\N{\fs38}has the instruction manual on him. Good one.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:24.06,0:35:24.57,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,嘿 \N{\fs38}Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:26.21,0:35:26.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,金泥\N{\fs38}Goldenmire?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:28.09,0:35:30.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他说过金泥 这个一定很重要\N{\fs38}He mentioned Goldenmire. That has to be important somehow.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:32.07,0:35:33.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,算了 走吧 \N{\fs38}Come on. Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:33.70,0:35:35.41,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们终于可以离开这个鬼地方了\N{\fs38}We can finally leave this nightmare.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:36.30,0:35:38.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,假设这个东西能送我们回去\N{\fs38}Assuming this thing gets us home
Dialogue: 0,0:35:38.09,0:35:40.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为我们不知道这个怎么用 拜托\N{\fs38}because we have no idea how this thing works. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:41.99,0:35:42.83,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 你准备好了吗  - 准备好了吗\N{\fs38}- You ready? - Ready?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:44.84,0:35:45.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我去\N{\fs38}Fuck's sake!
Dialogue: 0,0:36:16.48,0:36:17.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很糟吗\N{\fs38}It's bad?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:17.54,0:36:20.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,嗯 我打算拿冰敷\N{\fs38}Yeah. I tried putting some ice on it.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:21.11,0:36:22.28,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我来扶你\N{\fs38}Let's get you fixed up.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:28.65,0:36:29.85,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在其他时空里找到别的我们了吗\N{\fs38}Did you find the other us in time?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:30.88,0:36:32.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我找不到我 但是我找到你了\N{\fs38}I couldn't get to me, but I found you.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:33.43,0:36:34.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我叫他去找金泥\N{\fs38}I told him to look for Goldenmire.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:36.23,0:36:37.11,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只希望他听见\N{\fs38} I just hope he listened.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:37.11,0:36:39.71,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 他真是嗨过头了  - 噢 我也是\N{\fs38}- He was really off his face. - Oh, so do I.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:40.30,0:36:43.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为 现在 这两个蠢才是我们最后的希望了\N{\fs38}Because, right now, those two idiots are our last hope.
