[Script Info]
由101eagle合成

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,华文楷体,19,&H00E0E0E0,&HF0000000,&H000D0500,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,0,0,3,1


[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.06,0:00:09.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,字幕來源：奇遇電影字幕組
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.39,0:00:20.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,字幕特效：101eagle
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.68,0:00:31.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,壓制：101eagle
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.72,0:00:43.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上傳UP：101eagle
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.06,0:01:05.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,露絲?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.40,0:01:16.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,露絲?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.69,0:01:48.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我妻子在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.31,0:01:51.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,古特曼先生 你可不能這樣偷偷在背後嚇我一跳
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.48,0:01:54.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我太太呢 露絲在哪裏
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.15,0:01:57.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很抱歉 古特曼先生
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.16,0:02:01.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你太太大約一周前過世了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.54,0:02:05.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.72,0:02:19.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 請問你是?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.59,0:02:21.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫保拉
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.55,0:02:23.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾是古特曼太太的護理
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.56,0:02:27.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們家請我再多待一兩周
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.23,0:02:30.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去吃點早餐吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.23,0:02:33.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃完早餐你會感覺好些的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.65,0:02:34.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的鞋在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.53,0:02:37.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 我去給你拿拖鞋
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.82,0:02:39.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用你的帽子去換雙拖鞋 可以嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.66,0:02:41.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 進來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.79,0:02:46.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 早安 澤夫 - 早安
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.54,0:02:49.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但願你沒有很餓 早餐和往常一樣少得可憐
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.50,0:02:51.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係 我不是很餓
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.42,0:02:54.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是塞萊 你太太以前的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.88,0:02:57.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道她是誰 我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.39,0:03:08.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能給我們私聊的時間嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.60,0:03:10.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 沒問題
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.52,0:03:12.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是馬克斯
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.60,0:03:14.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你沒必要告訴我所有人的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.28,0:03:25.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚是為露絲服喪的最後一晚對嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.62,0:03:30.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你還記不記得你說過露絲死後
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.91,0:03:32.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要做什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.30,0:03:37.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不記得了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.80,0:03:40.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事 沒事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.72,0:03:42.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.55,0:03:44.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,記下了所有事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.64,0:03:46.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.97,0:03:48.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會記起來的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.81,0:03:57.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我來 勞森鮑姆先生
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.38,0:04:16.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,親愛的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.34,0:04:19.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道這張照片什麼時候照的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.84,0:04:24.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們結婚的時候照的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.43,0:04:26.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,1946年
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.01,0:04:29.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是在德國遇見奶奶的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.35,0:04:31.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 不 不是
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.60,0:04:36.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在美國遇見她的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.90,0:04:38.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在康尼
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.61,0:04:41.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 在康尼島 - 對
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.44,0:04:44.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 為什麼不拿給你哥哥看看呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.03,0:04:48.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亞當 快看這個
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.58,0:04:54.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給 把這個放口袋裏
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.42,0:04:57.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.04,0:04:59.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站起來
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.50,0:05:01.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告訴所有人你累了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.55,0:05:06.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後獨自一人看完
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.34,0:05:08.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,獨自一人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.97,0:05:10.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你累了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.76,0:05:11.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對 對
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.06,0:05:13.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就這樣 好的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.82,0:05:22.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原諒我 我
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.53,0:05:25.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有點累 我想我該去睡覺了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.03,0:05:28.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.70,0:05:30.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是漫長的一周
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.33,0:05:33.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.47,0:06:34.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 佩恩車站 對嗎 - 是的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.03,0:06:55.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最後通知
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.54,0:06:57.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,49號湖濱列車要發車了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.75,0:06:59.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最後通知
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.08,0:07:03.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最後通知 要開車了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.01,0:07:09.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是你媽媽嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.55,0:07:11.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.10,0:07:14.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不和你一起嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.85,0:07:17.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我去找我爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.98,0:07:20.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.52,0:07:23.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你是一個人咯
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.11,0:07:26.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是一個人 我的兄弟們在那呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.53,0:07:29.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.03,0:07:31.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 我看見了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.78,0:07:36.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也是去克利夫蘭嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.62,0:07:37.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.74,0:07:39.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼不坐飛機呢 那樣更快
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.12,0:07:43.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.50,0:07:45.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這可不是個好理由
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.21,0:07:49.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這個不知天高地厚的小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.71,0:07:51.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你為什麼不坐飛機去克利夫蘭呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.80,0:07:53.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三張飛機票太貴了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.09,0:07:55.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我爸媽說的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.22,0:07:57.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 這是個好理由
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.89,0:08:03.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不坐飛機是因為我朋友在他寫給我的信裏
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.15,0:08:06.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告訴我要坐火車
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.11,0:08:11.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想這也是個好理由
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.95,0:08:13.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫泰勒
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.91,0:08:16.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很高興認識你 泰勒
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.08,0:08:18.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫澤夫
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.54,0:08:20.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是個奇怪的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.95,0:08:23.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在希伯來語裏 它的意思是"狼"
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.87,0:08:26.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真酷
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.97,0:08:36.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我為你計劃了所有事項
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.51,0:08:40.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你必須精準地執行這些步驟
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.18,0:08:44.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每做完一項就劃掉一項
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.86,0:08:49.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們已經通知過警方 他們向社區發出了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.90,0:08:52.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,銀色警報並啟動反911系統
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.82,0:08:55.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們...我們這邊會竭盡全力
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.57,0:08:57.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 確實難以接受... - 我只是不敢相信
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.91,0:09:00.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,發生的這一切
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.20,0:09:02.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們感到萬分的抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.79,0:09:05.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們會密切留意每個人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.92,0:09:07.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但...我相信你能理解的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.88,0:09:09.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們能幫到什麼嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.59,0:09:12.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了付錢讓你們看丟人還有別的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.30,0:09:14.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你父親有信用卡嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.09,0:09:17.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他一旦使用你可以讓銀行聯繫你
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.64,0:09:22.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽著
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.81,0:09:25.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你母親的護工告訴我
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.73,0:09:28.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你父親最近特別糊塗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.31,0:09:30.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 他患有癡呆
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.82,0:09:33.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而這也是起初我母親把父親一起帶到這來的原因
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.74,0:09:34.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白 但是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.65,0:09:37.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通常在配偶死亡後
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.66,0:09:40.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會出現更多認知障礙
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.99,0:09:44.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有沒有注意到你父親的情緒波動
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.33,0:09:47.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且他幾乎不再彈鋼琴了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.92,0:09:52.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我察覺到了一些 查爾斯
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.30,0:09:56.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想那時我們
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.84,0:10:00.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在你母親的事情上太操勞了以至於我沒有理會這些
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.93,0:10:05.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安心吧 我們會讓他在你知曉前平安回來的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.81,0:10:07.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在這些情況下
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.35,0:10:09.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人不會走太遠
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.11,0:10:16.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,露絲?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.20,0:10:20.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,露絲?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.04,0:10:25.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亞當?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.37,0:10:27.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你奶奶在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.37,0:10:30.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亞當?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.92,0:10:32.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你奶奶呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.21,0:10:34.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在跟我說話嗎 澤夫
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.13,0:10:36.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我問你奶奶在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.38,0:10:41.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一個在紐約州 一個在俄亥俄州
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.76,0:10:45.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你妹妹呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.18,0:10:47.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我沒有妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.02,0:10:50.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別玩那玩意兒了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.23,0:10:52.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回答我
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.27,0:10:56.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你...還好嗎 澤夫
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.28,0:10:59.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.82,0:11:01.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在火車上
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.87,0:11:03.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去哪
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.28,0:11:04.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克利夫蘭
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.91,0:11:06.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克利夫蘭?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.16,0:11:09.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要去見一個朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.00,0:11:11.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.38,0:11:14.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給你寫了你口袋裏那封信的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.17,0:11:21.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能把我的遊戲機還給我了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.15,0:11:41.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,露絲死了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.45,0:11:49.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,澤夫
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.79,0:11:52.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要去和我兄弟們坐一會
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.50,0:12:33.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你好 - 嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.29,0:12:35.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨 我... 我兒子在火車上時你和他挨著
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.08,0:12:38.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你看起來有些糊塗了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.84,0:12:40.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 是的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.80,0:12:42.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我對此感到很抱歉 - 噢 不會不會
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.84,0:12:44.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不需要道歉 我們...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.88,0:12:47.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 只是想確認你沒事 - 噢我沒事的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.76,0:12:49.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你 我很好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.06,0:12:51.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,額...你要去哪需要幫忙嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.02,0:12:54.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用 會有人來接我的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.81,0:12:57.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我朋友說他會舉一個
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.02,0:12:59.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寫有我姓名的牌子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.98,0:13:02.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 我們會幫你找
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.86,0:13:05.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這些車剛到
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.78,0:13:11.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是姓古特曼嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.49,0:13:12.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.33,0:13:14.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你坐的車看起來很時髦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.42,0:13:18.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再見 澤夫
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.29,0:13:20.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再見 再見
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.21,0:13:22.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧 孩子們
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.46,0:13:24.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 古特曼先生? - 是的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.92,0:13:26.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.19,0:13:40.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 下午好 - 下午好
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.36,0:13:42.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎樣幫到你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.86,0:13:46.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我朋友向我推薦了你的店
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.40,0:13:48.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 請轉告你的朋友我們很感謝他的推薦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.03,0:13:51.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你想要拿哪種呢 - 噢...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.91,0:13:53.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小一點的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.91,0:13:55.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當然有
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.91,0:13:57.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 能給我看看你的駕駛證嗎 - 好的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.05,0:14:07.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這兒...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.18,0:14:09.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.97,0:14:12.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比奇伍德 很棒的小鎮
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.26,0:14:13.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 但...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.18,0:14:15.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們搬走了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.39,0:14:18.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們搬去離我兒子更近的住處了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.36,0:14:21.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你拿我的駕駛證幹什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.98,0:14:25.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在把你的信息輸入FBI的背景調查數據庫
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.07,0:14:27.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.36,0:14:29.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們在調查什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.57,0:14:31.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一大堆資料 看你是否為已被定罪的重刑犯
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.91,0:14:33.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,涉嫌暴力犯罪
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.62,0:14:35.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被軍隊懲戒免職
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.33,0:14:38.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是否智力健全 或者是否過去五年內
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.41,0:14:40.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不止一次酒駕 是否是個逃犯
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.46,0:14:42.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 或者最近被指控重罪 - 逃犯?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.21,0:14:44.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 比如你在逃脫法律的制裁
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.96,0:14:47.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你覺得我看起來逃得動嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.34,0:14:54.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 給你看些小一點的手槍
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.26,0:14:57.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們應有盡有 西格紹爾 M1911 格洛克（均為手槍型號）
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.39,0:14:58.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,單動槍 雙動槍
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.06,0:15:01.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 先生 你懂槍嗎 - 額...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.36,0:15:04.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 不懂 怎麼了 - 那沒關係
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.65,0:15:06.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們這什麼類型的都有
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.65,0:15:08.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 新手的話...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.99,0:15:10.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通常是用點22口徑的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.49,0:15:12.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它很輕 易上手 後坐力很小
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.29,0:15:17.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得這就是我朋友建議的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.66,0:15:19.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 依我來看
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.50,0:15:22.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你買點22就相當於擁有了一把氣槍
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.13,0:15:27.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 我不是在強行推銷 但多花500塊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.21,0:15:30.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能擁有一把真正有制動能力的槍
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.38,0:15:34.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個是格洛克17 9mm手槍
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.68,0:15:36.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,格洛克? 這是德國槍 對嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.06,0:15:39.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接近正確答案了 它產自奧地利
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.31,0:15:43.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是世界上最流行的執法手槍 不錯吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.40,0:15:45.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它的後坐力非常小 所以應該不會傷到手
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.98,0:15:47.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但它肯定會傷到入侵者
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.94,0:15:50.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個好用嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.61,0:15:52.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但願
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.49,0:15:53.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 它很簡易
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.37,0:15:55.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 但是...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.03,0:15:58.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知你介不介意 可不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.29,0:16:00.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幫我寫個使用說明書
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.37,0:16:04.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當然可以 我的意思是 我可以示範給你看怎麼使用
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.04,0:16:08.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不了 那是很好 但拜託了 幫我寫下來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.71,0:16:11.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有時候會健忘
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.39,0:16:21.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顧客至上 這沒問題
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.68,0:16:23.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 一切都妥當了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.56,0:16:25.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去拿支筆 然後
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.52,0:16:27.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幫你寫下使用說明
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.99,0:16:38.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 古特曼先生嗎 - 對 古特曼
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.41,0:16:39.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎麼知道
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.62,0:16:42.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你朋友早些時候打過電話說你快到了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.41,0:16:44.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,房間已經為你準備好了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.25,0:16:46.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,房間號是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.17,0:16:49.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,125 就順著走廊走
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.51,0:16:53.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我該付多少錢 - 已經付過了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.63,0:16:55.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,包括附加費
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.09,0:16:58.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了 應你朋友的要求 我們為你訂了明天早上的出租車
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.06,0:17:00.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.57,0:17:18.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 喂? - 喂
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.33,0:17:20.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 澤夫嗎 - 是我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.79,0:17:22.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是馬克斯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.29,0:17:25.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我指示了酒店一些事項
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.08,0:17:29.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你還好嗎 - 是的我還好 馬克斯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.30,0:17:33.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你拿到槍了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.30,0:17:35.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 拿到了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.38,0:17:37.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好 很好
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.14,0:17:40.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道該做什麼的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.81,0:17:44.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照顧好自己 知道嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.64,0:17:48.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安好夢 馬克斯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.35,0:17:49.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安 澤夫
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.19,0:18:30.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,露絲?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.15,0:18:33.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,露絲?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.20,0:18:39.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,露絲?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.57,0:18:42.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把燈打開好嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.24,0:18:45.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太黑了 我看不...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.58,0:18:47.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看不清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.79,0:20:11.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你好 - 嗨
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.62,0:20:14.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請問魯迪·庫蘭德在家嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.63,0:20:16.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在家 他在樓下
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.58,0:20:54.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.33,0:20:55.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魯迪·庫蘭德?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.50,0:20:57.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.67,0:20:59.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是魯迪·庫蘭德
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.84,0:21:01.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.26,0:21:02.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以...呃...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.84,0:21:03.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把電視關掉嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.51,0:21:11.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我認識你嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.02,0:21:20.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在 請你...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.61,0:21:24.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站到窗戶旁邊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.70,0:21:27.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是誰
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.70,0:21:31.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站到窗戶旁邊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.33,0:21:34.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你不告訴我你是誰還有你來這兒的原因
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.54,0:21:36.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我什麼都不會做
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.29,0:21:38.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咱們還是別爭了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.29,0:21:41.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站到窗邊去
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.33,0:22:14.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在又要做什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.54,0:22:22.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得亮堂些我才能看清你的臉
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.96,0:22:25.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 把頭轉過去 - 你是誰
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.92,0:22:27.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別吼
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.55,0:22:28.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜託 不要吼
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.34,0:22:31.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,按我說的做 抬起頭來
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.10,0:22:37.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是德國人嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.10,0:22:39.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.40,0:22:42.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你也是德國人? (德語) - 是
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.57,0:22:45.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你多少歲了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.11,0:22:51.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你曾在德軍服役嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.58,0:22:53.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在軍隊裏做什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.70,0:22:57.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 那都過去了 - 英語 請說英語
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.87,0:23:01.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我不喜歡說德語 - 那都是70年前了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.67,0:23:03.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我那時太年輕
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.13,0:23:04.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回答我的問題
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.09,0:23:08.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是猶太人?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.97,0:23:11.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.97,0:23:14.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你當時在奧斯維辛集中營嗎 - 我不在
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.14,0:23:16.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們都這個歲數了 還有必要撒謊嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.44,0:23:21.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在戰爭結束前
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.48,0:23:24.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都不知道奧斯維辛集中營的事
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.48,0:23:26.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我當時在北非
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.48,0:23:29.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和隆美爾元帥一起
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.99,0:23:33.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你有證據嗎 - 有
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.53,0:23:36.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在那邊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.00,0:23:50.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當我成為美國公民的時候 移民局的官員問我
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.09,0:23:53.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是否曾和納粹政府
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.59,0:23:55.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有關聯
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.93,0:23:58.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者是否曾在集中營工作
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.02,0:24:03.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的回答說
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.94,0:24:07.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 我效忠於我的國家 我是一名軍人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.78,0:24:11.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我為自己身為德國人而自豪 所有人都為自己的國家而自豪
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.53,0:24:15.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我仍然為我為國家作出的貢獻感到自豪
Dialogue: 0,0:24:22.79,0:24:24.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是隆美爾元帥
Dialogue: 0,0:24:26.75,0:24:28.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至於猶太人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:32.59,0:24:36.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我並不關心猶太人 我認為希特勒是對的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:37.76,0:24:40.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猶太人給我們國家帶來了太多麻煩
Dialogue: 0,0:24:41.48,0:24:46.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我認為我們是在驅逐他們 或是把他們安置在勞動營裏...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:47.15,0:24:48.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而不是像他們所做的那樣
Dialogue: 0,0:24:52.11,0:24:53.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那太可恥了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:54.53,0:24:55.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我沒有做那些事
Dialogue: 0,0:25:08.92,0:25:12.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 喂? - 是馬克斯嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:25:12.92,0:25:13.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.63,0:25:15.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是澤夫
Dialogue: 0,0:25:16.01,0:25:17.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃... 不是...
Dialogue: 0,0:25:18.22,0:25:19.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是他
Dialogue: 0,0:25:20.85,0:25:23.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你確定嗎 - 我確定
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.52,0:25:26.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你必須要繼續
Dialogue: 0,0:25:27.73,0:25:29.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必須履行
Dialogue: 0,0:25:30.19,0:25:31.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你曾經承諾過的
Dialogue: 0,0:25:47.00,0:25:49.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近些年來一直有傳聞
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.13,0:25:53.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一些奧斯維辛集中營裏的黨衛隊軍官
Dialogue: 0,0:25:53.13,0:25:56.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在戰爭接近尾聲的時候
Dialogue: 0,0:25:57.09,0:25:58.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冒名頂替了被處死的猶太人的身份
Dialogue: 0,0:25:59.76,0:26:02.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我中風後不久
Dialogue: 0,0:26:02.64,0:26:06.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有證據表明 一名奧斯維辛集中營軍官
Dialogue: 0,0:26:06.77,0:26:10.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,於19世紀40年代從德國移民
Dialogue: 0,0:26:10.31,0:26:14.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,並且最可能用假名魯迪·庫蘭德
Dialogue: 0,0:26:14.28,0:26:16.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續生活
Dialogue: 0,0:26:17.20,0:26:19.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西蒙·維森塔爾中心(西蒙·維森塔爾中心是一個國際猶太人權組織 這組織是為了紀念納粹在二次世界大戰中被殺的猶太人而成立的)
Dialogue: 0,0:26:19.62,0:26:22.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到了四名在那個時期移民至此的
Dialogue: 0,0:26:22.95,0:26:25.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魯迪·庫蘭德
Dialogue: 0,0:26:26.04,0:26:28.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然而 沒有足夠的證據
Dialogue: 0,0:26:28.67,0:26:30.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逮捕他們其中任何一人
Dialogue: 0,0:26:34.00,0:26:38.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的真名是奧托·瓦利施
Dialogue: 0,0:26:40.72,0:26:43.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你必須要找到他
Dialogue: 0,0:26:48.73,0:26:52.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我正在尋找我父親 他已經將近90歲了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:53.86,0:26:56.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的名字叫澤夫
Dialogue: 0,0:26:56.19,0:26:57.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在尋找我的父親
Dialogue: 0,0:26:58.36,0:26:59.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他90歲了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:00.03,0:27:02.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他幾天前外出閒逛
Dialogue: 0,0:27:03.08,0:27:05.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的名字是澤夫·古特曼
Dialogue: 0,0:27:05.66,0:27:08.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道他是否隨身攜帶了可以證明身份的證件
Dialogue: 0,0:27:09.00,0:27:11.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我甚至不確定他是否還記得自己的姓名
Dialogue: 0,0:27:11.96,0:27:15.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想知道有沒有人被送進醫院
Dialogue: 0,0:27:17.88,0:27:21.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你覺得我還沒報警嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:27:28.14,0:27:29.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女士們先生們
Dialogue: 0,0:27:29.94,0:27:31.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們快到加拿大邊境了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:31.40,0:27:34.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到時候大家都需要下車接受檢查
Dialogue: 0,0:27:34.65,0:27:36.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果您能提前準備好您的護照或其他旅行證件
Dialogue: 0,0:27:37.07,0:27:39.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,將節省不少時間 謝謝合作
Dialogue: 0,0:28:03.76,0:28:04.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請出示申報單
Dialogue: 0,0:28:07.26,0:28:08.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您此行的目的是?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:08.93,0:28:11.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜訪一位朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:28:11.77,0:28:12.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您朋友的姓名是?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:12.85,0:28:14.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 魯迪·庫蘭德 - 他住哪
Dialogue: 0,0:28:15.06,0:28:18.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,福伊爾·德斯...福伊爾...
Dialogue: 0,0:28:25.12,0:28:27.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我能看看嗎 - 當然可以
Dialogue: 0,0:28:29.45,0:28:32.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 福伊爾·德斯先驅者養老院? - 是的
Dialogue: 0,0:28:32.37,0:28:34.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您將入住安大略省赫斯特的皇后汽車旅館?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:34.79,0:28:35.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯
Dialogue: 0,0:28:36.17,0:28:37.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您將在加拿大停留多久
Dialogue: 0,0:28:38.13,0:28:40.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概兩晚吧
Dialogue: 0,0:28:41.97,0:28:43.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,護照
Dialogue: 0,0:29:02.32,0:29:03.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生 您的護照過期了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:05.36,0:29:07.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 過期了? - 對
Dialogue: 0,0:29:10.33,0:29:12.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您有駕照嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:29:12.16,0:29:13.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 當然有
Dialogue: 0,0:29:18.92,0:29:20.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍等
Dialogue: 0,0:29:37.90,0:29:39.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 您可以走了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:40.02,0:29:41.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過請您將護照延期
Dialogue: 0,0:29:43.24,0:29:46.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都這個歲數了 用不著了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:47.91,0:29:49.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祝您與朋友相聚愉快
Dialogue: 0,0:29:49.16,0:29:50.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:30:24.40,0:30:25.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打擾一下
Dialogue: 0,0:30:25.82,0:30:26.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,需要什麼幫助嗎 先生
Dialogue: 0,0:30:27.03,0:30:30.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魯迪·庫蘭德在哪個房間
Dialogue: 0,0:30:30.91,0:30:32.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,庫蘭德?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:32.53,0:30:34.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對 庫蘭德 他在238房
Dialogue: 0,0:30:35.04,0:30:38.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沿著這條走廊走 坐電梯
Dialogue: 0,0:30:38.29,0:30:41.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出電梯後 左轉 再右轉
Dialogue: 0,0:30:42.04,0:30:43.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,238號房就在你的左手邊
Dialogue: 0,0:30:45.26,0:30:46.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:30:47.84,0:30:49.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我直接帶您去您朋友的房間吧
Dialogue: 0,0:30:50.09,0:30:51.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:31:20.42,0:31:22.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是魯迪·庫蘭德嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:31:25.00,0:31:26.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魯迪·庫蘭德?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:26.88,0:31:28.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是
Dialogue: 0,0:31:54.37,0:31:58.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你是魯迪·庫蘭德? - 是的
Dialogue: 0,0:32:01.04,0:32:02.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是德國人嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:32:03.00,0:32:04.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:32:07.50,0:32:10.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以前在奧斯維辛集中營嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:32:14.14,0:32:15.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:32:19.22,0:32:22.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去過奧斯維辛集中營
Dialogue: 0,0:32:24.15,0:32:27.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我全家人都在
Dialogue: 0,0:32:28.69,0:32:30.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奧斯維辛集中營
Dialogue: 0,0:32:30.94,0:32:32.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被殺了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:35.03,0:32:36.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我感到很抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:32:38.45,0:32:40.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很...很抱歉?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:41.96,0:32:43.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯
Dialogue: 0,0:32:46.29,0:32:51.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的所作所為不是道個歉就足夠的
Dialogue: 0,0:32:56.22,0:32:59.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我發過誓我會殺死
Dialogue: 0,0:32:59.18,0:33:01.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,殺害我全家性命的那個人
Dialogue: 0,0:33:11.57,0:33:13.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是猶太人?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:14.11,0:33:15.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是同性戀
Dialogue: 0,0:33:21.16,0:33:23.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,應該是我道歉才對
Dialogue: 0,0:33:28.21,0:33:32.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起 真的很抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:34:51.54,0:34:53.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莫什科夫斯基
Dialogue: 0,0:34:54.17,0:34:55.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道莫什科夫斯基?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:56.17,0:34:59.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以前的鋼琴老師曾說
Dialogue: 0,0:34:59.13,0:35:01.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三位最偉大的作曲家分別是
Dialogue: 0,0:35:02.51,0:35:04.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,門德爾松 梅耶貝爾
Dialogue: 0,0:35:05.35,0:35:06.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及莫什科夫斯基
Dialogue: 0,0:35:07.18,0:35:09.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你現在還彈嗎 - 噢...
Dialogue: 0,0:35:10.52,0:35:12.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:35:12.36,0:35:14.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我不知道 我不確定
Dialogue: 0,0:35:14.57,0:35:15.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼...
Dialogue: 0,0:35:16.69,0:35:19.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼不試試呢
Dialogue: 0,0:35:20.45,0:35:22.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢... 好吧...
Dialogue: 0,0:35:25.87,0:35:27.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,門德爾松
Dialogue: 0,0:35:27.54,0:35:28.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概吧
Dialogue: 0,0:37:16.98,0:37:19.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好 先生 歡迎來到博伊西
Dialogue: 0,0:37:20.61,0:37:21.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您預定過了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:37:22.40,0:37:25.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我這邊有記錄您早上8點需要出租車服務
Dialogue: 0,0:37:25.49,0:37:30.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們將於6點起供應免費早餐
Dialogue: 0,0:37:32.62,0:37:35.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果您徑直穿過左手邊的大廳...
Dialogue: 0,0:37:43.01,0:37:44.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我來幫助您 好嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:37:51.89,0:37:55.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有件事 我忘了帶衣服了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:55.52,0:37:56.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 換洗的衣服 - 噢
Dialogue: 0,0:37:57.02,0:37:59.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個完全不是問題
Dialogue: 0,0:37:59.65,0:38:02.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每整點都有一趟公共汽車從我們這裏發往市中心
Dialogue: 0,0:38:02.53,0:38:06.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這趟車會將您送到北密爾沃基路的商場
Dialogue: 0,0:38:07.49,0:38:09.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您可以在那買到您需要的所有東西
Dialogue: 0,0:38:15.58,0:38:18.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生 你需要我幫您預訂嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:38:19.50,0:38:20.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生 您還好嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:38:23.00,0:38:26.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您現在想去您的房間了嗎 好勒
Dialogue: 0,0:38:40.52,0:38:42.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 您需要我幫你找什麼嗎 - 噢 是的
Dialogue: 0,0:38:42.82,0:38:45.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想買一件新襯衫
Dialogue: 0,0:38:45.86,0:38:47.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們有很多短袖系扣襯衫
Dialogue: 0,0:38:48.03,0:38:48.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 是嗎 - 您要看看嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:38:49.41,0:38:50.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 勞駕 - 不客氣
Dialogue: 0,0:38:51.07,0:38:53.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,季末的時候最劃算了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:53.33,0:38:54.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:39:03.80,0:39:05.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 先生 您觸響了警報
Dialogue: 0,0:39:06.09,0:39:07.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得檢查一下您的包
Dialogue: 0,0:39:07.92,0:39:09.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 我看起來像個賊嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:39:10.34,0:39:12.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 跟這沒關係 先生 您觸響了警報
Dialogue: 0,0:39:12.72,0:39:14.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎樣我都得檢查一下您的包
Dialogue: 0,0:39:15.01,0:39:16.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是收據
Dialogue: 0,0:39:17.35,0:39:18.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 問題在這兒
Dialogue: 0,0:39:18.94,0:39:20.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們忘記把安全標籤取下了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:21.10,0:39:22.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還得檢查一下您另外一個包 先生
Dialogue: 0,0:39:34.95,0:39:35.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是一把格洛克嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:39:37.00,0:39:38.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:39:41.08,0:39:43.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我想起了我第一把槍
Dialogue: 0,0:39:44.79,0:39:46.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祝您今天過得愉快 先生
Dialogue: 0,0:39:46.55,0:39:50.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 給您 非常感謝 - 謝謝 謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:40:46.56,0:40:48.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您要續杯嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:40:48.44,0:40:50.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 好的 謝謝 - 不客氣
Dialogue: 0,0:40:51.69,0:40:54.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能告訴我從這兒到布魯諾有多遠嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:40:54.66,0:40:57.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我從沒去過布魯諾 不過那是在奧懷希郡
Dialogue: 0,0:40:57.70,0:41:00.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 我覺得大概是三四十分鐘的路程吧
Dialogue: 0,0:41:00.66,0:41:02.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 噢 - 我聽說那兒的鄉下很漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:41:02.91,0:41:04.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我從沒去過但是我朋友...
Dialogue: 0,0:41:04.58,0:41:05.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 噢 - 啊
Dialogue: 0,0:41:05.83,0:41:07.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 我很抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:41:07.13,0:41:08.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我把咖啡撒到你的信上了 - 噢 天啊
Dialogue: 0,0:41:09.05,0:41:10.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手 你把我的信毀了
Dialogue: 0,0:41:10.13,0:41:11.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 不要 不要 不要 - 我很抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:41:12.05,0:41:15.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這封信很重要 住手 住手 住手
Dialogue: 0,0:41:22.18,0:41:24.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了我
Dialogue: 0,0:41:25.10,0:41:29.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是唯一一個
Dialogue: 0,0:41:31.07,0:41:34.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仍然能認出
Dialogue: 0,0:41:37.95,0:41:41.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那人長相的人
Dialogue: 0,0:41:42.79,0:41:48.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他殺害了我們的家人
Dialogue: 0,0:42:37.63,0:42:39.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 沒人在家嗎 - 沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:42:39.76,0:42:41.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您想讓我把您送到其他地方嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:42:41.55,0:42:44.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 不不不 我再等等 - 給您
Dialogue: 0,0:42:46.31,0:42:49.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您什麼時候需要我回來接您就給我打個電話
Dialogue: 0,0:42:49.81,0:42:51.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我該付你多少錢
Dialogue: 0,0:42:51.98,0:42:54.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 您已經付過錢了 記得嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:42:56.32,0:42:58.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你需要乘車給我打個電話就行
Dialogue: 0,0:43:48.87,0:43:49.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早安
Dialogue: 0,0:43:53.25,0:43:55.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也早安 小可愛
Dialogue: 0,0:44:06.72,0:44:07.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯...
Dialogue: 0,0:44:11.39,0:44:12.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,該吃晚飯了 勞森鮑姆先生
Dialogue: 0,0:44:15.73,0:44:17.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我帶點吃的來 可以嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:44:18.73,0:44:20.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您確定嗎 您已經在房間裏待了一整天了
Dialogue: 0,0:44:21.07,0:44:23.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我確定 - 好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:44:54.90,0:44:56.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能幫您什麼嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:44:57.06,0:44:59.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我來找魯迪·庫蘭德
Dialogue: 0,0:45:03.95,0:45:06.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 您來對地方了 但是...
Dialogue: 0,0:45:09.16,0:45:11.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的爸爸3個月前去世了
Dialogue: 0,0:45:12.71,0:45:15.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 我不知道這個 我很遺憾
Dialogue: 0,0:45:23.47,0:45:24.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您在這兒等了多久了
Dialogue: 0,0:45:26.47,0:45:27.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一整天
Dialogue: 0,0:45:30.97,0:45:32.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您要喝點什麼嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:45:34.27,0:45:35.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那好極了
Dialogue: 0,0:45:36.81,0:45:37.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,進來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:45:37.90,0:45:40.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我自己也來點
Dialogue: 0,0:45:40.27,0:45:42.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 謝謝你 - 要啤酒還是水
Dialogue: 0,0:45:42.90,0:45:45.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水就可以了 謝謝你
Dialogue: 0,0:45:48.32,0:45:50.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 伊娃 乖 別叫了
Dialogue: 0,0:45:52.79,0:45:54.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽著 我有點怕狗
Dialogue: 0,0:45:54.91,0:45:56.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊娃不會咬人的 進來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:45:56.87,0:46:00.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我相信你 但我還是蠻害怕的
Dialogue: 0,0:46:00.46,0:46:02.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 我把它帶走 沒問題的
Dialogue: 0,0:46:02.84,0:46:04.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們走 好樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:46:04.76,0:46:06.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別叫了 伊娃
Dialogue: 0,0:46:06.13,0:46:07.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊娃 噓 安靜
Dialogue: 0,0:46:07.89,0:46:10.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安靜 別叫了 伊娃 噓
Dialogue: 0,0:46:11.51,0:46:13.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊娃 噓 噓
Dialogue: 0,0:46:13.47,0:46:15.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊娃 安靜下來 安靜
Dialogue: 0,0:46:21.40,0:46:22.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別叫了
Dialogue: 0,0:46:39.54,0:46:42.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我兒子的畢業照
Dialogue: 0,0:46:43.88,0:46:45.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我父親一直很喜歡那張照片
Dialogue: 0,0:46:46.05,0:46:48.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我去...拿水給你 - 好的
Dialogue: 0,0:46:48.55,0:46:50.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這張照片什麼時候拍的  你父親看起來很年輕
Dialogue: 0,0:46:51.05,0:46:53.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是 額 1997拍的
Dialogue: 0,0:46:54.52,0:46:57.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 哦 - 對啊 老當益壯 不是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:46:59.81,0:47:04.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他一直說他是庫蘭德家族基因最好的
Dialogue: 0,0:47:05.49,0:47:06.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給你
Dialogue: 0,0:47:13.99,0:47:16.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 你比伊娃還渴
Dialogue: 0,0:47:17.58,0:47:19.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 還要嗎 - 好的 謝謝你
Dialogue: 0,0:47:19.58,0:47:21.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後就不會再麻煩你了
Dialogue: 0,0:47:21.58,0:47:23.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不會的 完全不麻煩
Dialogue: 0,0:47:24.84,0:47:26.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要待多久都可以
Dialogue: 0,0:47:27.47,0:47:31.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自從...我父親去世了 一個人住在這裏很孤單
Dialogue: 0,0:47:33.43,0:47:35.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道嗎 我就一直在附近巡邏
Dialogue: 0,0:47:36.27,0:47:41.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了聽聽廣播 偶爾被調派 沒別的事了
Dialogue: 0,0:47:42.40,0:47:45.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回家時有人能跟我說說話真好
Dialogue: 0,0:47:45.94,0:47:48.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊娃很棒 但她畢竟不能跟我聊天
Dialogue: 0,0:47:48.57,0:47:50.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你要的水 - 你沒結婚?
Dialogue: 0,0:47:51.07,0:47:54.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不是的 請坐 我結過婚...兩次
Dialogue: 0,0:47:54.99,0:47:57.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一個老婆 帶走了我的房子
Dialogue: 0,0:47:58.29,0:48:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第二個老婆 在採石場收購
Dialogue: 0,0:48:00.12,0:48:01.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這套房子之前離開了
Dialogue: 0,0:48:03.17,0:48:06.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是...哇 七年前的事了
Dialogue: 0,0:48:07.17,0:48:08.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不介意再找一個
Dialogue: 0,0:48:09.30,0:48:12.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但布魯諾不是最適合單身的人的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:48:13.47,0:48:16.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我 也不是黃金單身漢
Dialogue: 0,0:48:18.89,0:48:23.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你爸爸跟你談起過德國嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:48:24.48,0:48:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在開玩笑嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:48:26.27,0:48:27.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他從來沒停止過討論德國
Dialogue: 0,0:48:29.40,0:48:31.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他有沒有跟你說過關於二戰的事?
Dialogue: 0,0:48:31.90,0:48:32.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當然
Dialogue: 0,0:48:33.57,0:48:35.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道他是個收集狂吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:48:35.66,0:48:36.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊
Dialogue: 0,0:48:38.54,0:48:41.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有一堆他的東西 你想看看嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:48:42.16,0:48:43.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:48:44.00,0:48:45.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心臺階 就在這裏
Dialogue: 0,0:48:54.34,0:48:56.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊娃 安靜 伊娃 噓
Dialogue: 0,0:48:56.64,0:49:00.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 聽著 額 這裏有點亂
Dialogue: 0,0:49:00.35,0:49:02.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得把箱子挪開 然後
Dialogue: 0,0:49:02.60,0:49:05.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我帶你去另一個房間
Dialogue: 0,0:49:10.19,0:49:11.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這邊
Dialogue: 0,0:49:12.32,0:49:14.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從這裏 好的 來吧 哦
Dialogue: 0,0:49:16.70,0:49:17.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,進來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:49:24.21,0:49:27.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是 額 那是我爸爸的驕傲和快樂
Dialogue: 0,0:49:29.30,0:49:36.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個賣給我們的人發誓1938年11月19日這面旗幟在柏林飛舞
Dialogue: 0,0:49:37.18,0:49:38.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水晶之夜
Dialogue: 0,0:49:39.56,0:49:41.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對啊 水晶之夜
Dialogue: 0,0:49:43.56,0:49:46.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父親曾經說 這面旗幟
Dialogue: 0,0:49:47.19,0:49:50.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,見證了歷史的開端
Dialogue: 0,0:49:52.23,0:49:53.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:49:59.08,0:50:01.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 箱子裏有什麼? - 額 就是
Dialogue: 0,0:50:02.58,0:50:05.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一些父親得到的其他獎賞 你知道
Dialogue: 0,0:50:05.75,0:50:08.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已經賣掉了大部分的收藏
Dialogue: 0,0:50:08.21,0:50:13.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 這些是跟他有感情的
Dialogue: 0,0:50:15.59,0:50:19.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,連我也還沒辦法賣了它們 你知道嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:50:23.64,0:50:25.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想到處看看嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:50:25.48,0:50:27.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 感謝 - 沒關係
Dialogue: 0,0:50:42.62,0:50:44.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對 這是初刊本
Dialogue: 0,0:50:45.12,0:50:48.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有個人想用6000美元跟我買 但我就是沒辦法...賣掉它
Dialogue: 0,0:50:51.13,0:50:53.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猜我跟我父親一樣感情用事 對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:50:56.76,0:51:00.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以隨便在周圍看看...任何東西都可以
Dialogue: 0,0:51:00.80,0:51:02.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去幫伊娃準備它的晚餐
Dialogue: 0,0:51:22.49,0:51:23.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安靜 噓
Dialogue: 0,0:51:39.51,0:51:40.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無價之寶 對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:51:43.26,0:51:44.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對啊
Dialogue: 0,0:51:45.43,0:51:48.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我不應該把它像那樣塞在箱子裏面
Dialogue: 0,0:52:04.20,0:52:05.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想要再喝點什麼嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:52:06.12,0:52:07.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 那會很好
Dialogue: 0,0:52:08.70,0:52:11.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再來一杯水 還是烈一點的東西
Dialogue: 0,0:52:12.50,0:52:14.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烈一點的好了
Dialogue: 0,0:52:15.38,0:52:16.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:52:17.38,0:52:19.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在你知道我在說什麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:52:19.72,0:52:20.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:52:25.81,0:52:27.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敬我父親
Dialogue: 0,0:52:33.44,0:52:34.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道嗎 我爸他...
Dialogue: 0,0:52:36.23,0:52:37.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爸那天晚上在那
Dialogue: 0,0:52:38.23,0:52:40.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 哪個晚上 - 額 水晶...
Dialogue: 0,0:52:40.90,0:52:42.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 水晶之夜 - 對 水晶之夜
Dialogue: 0,0:52:43.49,0:52:45.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對 他說他帶了一個鐵錘
Dialogue: 0,0:52:46.16,0:52:48.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他打碎了一些珠寶店的窗戶
Dialogue: 0,0:52:48.45,0:52:50.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 他跟你說過這件事嗎 - 沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:52:50.50,0:52:51.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有?
Dialogue: 0,0:52:52.37,0:52:54.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真希望你在他還活著的時候來這裏
Dialogue: 0,0:52:54.63,0:52:58.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道 每過一段時間 有一些他的朋友會過來
Dialogue: 0,0:52:58.17,0:53:01.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們就會坐在這裏 說一些故事 喝喝酒 你知道嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:53:02.59,0:53:05.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他很喜歡講一些以前的事
Dialogue: 0,0:53:07.22,0:53:08.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你還好嗎 你流了很多汗
Dialogue: 0,0:53:09.56,0:53:12.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 哦 我有點熱 - 把你的外套脫了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:53:12.48,0:53:13.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:53:14.40,0:53:17.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對 把你的外套脫了 然後 我只是想要告訴你
Dialogue: 0,0:53:17.77,0:53:19.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我求之不得你能... - 哦
Dialogue: 0,0:53:19.61,0:53:22.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,...在這裏住一晚 如果你不介意睡在我父親的舊床上
Dialogue: 0,0:53:22.82,0:53:24.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你人真好 不必了 謝謝你 - 不 不
Dialogue: 0,0:53:24.95,0:53:27.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 好吧 反正我的提議隨時有效 - 哦 謝謝你
Dialogue: 0,0:53:28.28,0:53:30.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父親的朋友就是我的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:53:31.62,0:53:35.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎麼認識他的 你曾經跟他一起服役?
Dialogue: 0,0:53:35.92,0:53:38.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 不是 - 好吧 那你怎麼認識他的
Dialogue: 0,0:53:40.84,0:53:43.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在奧斯維辛認識他的
Dialogue: 0,0:53:49.68,0:53:50.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奧斯維辛?
Dialogue: 0,0:53:51.77,0:53:53.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我父親很希望他能在奧斯維辛服役
Dialogue: 0,0:53:54.39,0:53:56.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是說你父親沒去過奧斯維辛?
Dialogue: 0,0:53:57.90,0:53:58.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在說什麼...
Dialogue: 0,0:53:58.98,0:54:01.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是認真的嗎 我父親是軍隊的廚師
Dialogue: 0,0:54:06.24,0:54:08.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不是集中營領袖? He was not a Blockfuhrer?
Dialogue: 0,0:54:08.82,0:54:13.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都不知道那是什麼 不是 我父親在戰爭開始的時候才10歲
Dialogue: 0,0:54:14.00,0:54:16.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德國人讓他做的最多的事就是 你知道
Dialogue: 0,0:54:16.50,0:54:19.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打破一些窗戶 煮一些維也納炸牛排 你知道嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:54:19.38,0:54:22.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很抱歉打擾你了
Dialogue: 0,0:54:22.71,0:54:27.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我找錯人了 - 不 沒事的 哇 哇塞
Dialogue: 0,0:54:27.51,0:54:30.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下 你以前在奧斯維辛?
Dialogue: 0,0:54:31.01,0:54:33.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 嗯 - 沒有一個我爸的朋友在那裏服役
Dialogue: 0,0:54:33.60,0:54:35.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我必須離開了 我已經打擾你很久了
Dialogue: 0,0:54:35.68,0:54:37.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打擾我? 不 沒有 請留下來
Dialogue: 0,0:54:37.69,0:54:40.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請留下來 分享一些故事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:54:40.73,0:54:42.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再去拿一瓶酒 我們就...
Dialogue: 0,0:54:50.03,0:54:51.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:54:57.00,0:54:58.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:54:59.54,0:55:00.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個他媽的是什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:55:01.71,0:55:04.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,額...對不起 我...
Dialogue: 0,0:55:05.51,0:55:06.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我 額...
Dialogue: 0,0:55:08.68,0:55:09.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個他媽的是什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:55:14.68,0:55:15.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是猶太人?
Dialogue: 0,0:55:18.64,0:55:19.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:55:21.40,0:55:22.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是一個猶太人?
Dialogue: 0,0:55:25.82,0:55:27.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在他媽是怎麼回事
Dialogue: 0,0:55:28.36,0:55:29.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起 我...
Dialogue: 0,0:55:30.41,0:55:32.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干你娘 給我坐下
Dialogue: 0,0:55:34.54,0:55:36.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜託你 讓我走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:55:39.58,0:55:41.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你他媽在我家幹嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:55:41.67,0:55:44.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我搞錯了 你父親不是我要找的人
Dialogue: 0,0:55:45.05,0:55:46.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我父親?
Dialogue: 0,0:55:49.59,0:55:51.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說你是我父親的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:55:53.43,0:55:54.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你騙我
Dialogue: 0,0:55:54.76,0:55:59.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我沒有說謊 我沒有說謊 - 干你娘雞掰
Dialogue: 0,0:56:02.44,0:56:05.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說你是我父親的朋友 你到我家裏
Dialogue: 0,0:56:06.53,0:56:08.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還他媽的喝我的威士忌
Dialogue: 0,0:56:08.74,0:56:11.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你他媽是一個骯髒的猶太人
Dialogue: 0,0:56:11.78,0:56:13.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊娃 閉上你的狗嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:56:14.03,0:56:16.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別吼了 求你了 別再吼了 我走
Dialogue: 0,0:56:16.58,0:56:17.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你給我坐下
Dialogue: 0,0:56:18.08,0:56:20.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你他媽現在立刻回答我的問題
Dialogue: 0,0:56:25.59,0:56:28.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,操你媽的 你剛剛是尿在了我的沙發上嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:56:29.01,0:56:32.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 對不起 我很抱歉 - 操你媽
Dialogue: 0,0:56:32.47,0:56:33.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別再叫了
Dialogue: 0,0:56:33.80,0:56:35.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊娃 你他媽閉嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:56:35.68,0:56:38.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是在命令我嗎 猶太人
Dialogue: 0,0:56:38.14,0:56:40.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊娃 我讓你閉嘴 你知道...
Dialogue: 0,0:56:41.56,0:56:46.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道如果我父親知道他媽有一個猶太人在他家他會說什麼嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:56:46.61,0:56:49.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他會說 "希特勒他媽的萬歲"
Dialogue: 0,0:56:49.69,0:56:50.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯 那就是他會說的
Dialogue: 0,0:56:50.74,0:56:54.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希特勒他媽的萬歲! 希特勒萬歲! 希特勒萬歲!
Dialogue: 0,0:56:54.82,0:56:56.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希特勒萬歲! 希特勒萬歲 你他媽的猶太人!
Dialogue: 0,0:56:57.08,0:56:58.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊娃 該死的 給我安靜
Dialogue: 0,0:56:59.04,0:57:00.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,閉嘴 你有什麼問題啊
Dialogue: 0,0:57:01.75,0:57:03.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈? 閉嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:57:04.42,0:57:06.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停下 伊娃 安靜
Dialogue: 0,0:57:06.67,0:57:07.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊娃
Dialogue: 0,0:57:07.88,0:57:10.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,該死 閉嘴 閉嘴 操你媽 安靜
Dialogue: 0,0:57:11.76,0:57:12.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊娃 冷靜下來
Dialogue: 0,0:57:17.18,0:57:19.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你他媽想要去見見活生生的猶太人嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:57:19.18,0:57:20.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈 是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:57:20.64,0:57:21.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈 去抓他吧
Dialogue: 0,0:57:23.89,0:57:24.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊!
Dialogue: 0,0:57:26.86,0:57:28.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我操你...
Dialogue: 0,0:57:32.78,0:57:34.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這該死的猶太人
Dialogue: 0,0:57:34.53,0:57:35.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我操...
Dialogue: 0,0:58:28.50,0:58:29.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦...
Dialogue: 0,0:59:05.66,0:59:07.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是約翰·庫蘭德
Dialogue: 0,0:59:07.29,0:59:10.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請留言吧 如果有急事 打我的手機
Dialogue: 0,0:59:10.67,0:59:11.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,露絲?
Dialogue: 0,0:59:11.75,0:59:14.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,約翰 你在哪 你已經晚了半個小時了
Dialogue: 0,0:59:14.13,0:59:15.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能整個早上都幫你掩護
Dialogue: 0,0:59:15.92,0:59:18.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我發誓 你最好是出車禍了... - 你在說什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:59:51.00,0:59:52.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的天啊
Dialogue: 0,1:00:05.72,1:00:07.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦...
Dialogue: 0,1:00:44.72,1:00:45.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好
Dialogue: 0,1:00:46.05,1:00:50.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 馬克思 我是澤夫 - 你去哪了
Dialogue: 0,1:00:51.89,1:00:54.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我殺了一個人
Dialogue: 0,1:00:56.23,1:00:57.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,額...
Dialogue: 0,1:00:58.69,1:01:04.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在是最難的部分了 你必須報警
Dialogue: 0,1:01:05.66,1:01:06.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你必須... - 不 不是的
Dialogue: 0,1:01:06.74,1:01:09.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不是我們要找的人
Dialogue: 0,1:01:13.29,1:01:16.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 那是誰 - 一個年輕很多的男人
Dialogue: 0,1:01:16.25,1:01:19.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我 額... 在一個箱子上看到了他的名字
Dialogue: 0,1:01:19.92,1:01:21.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他叫做約翰·庫蘭德
Dialogue: 0,1:01:23.05,1:01:24.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是一個納粹
Dialogue: 0,1:01:27.26,1:01:31.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你怎麼知道的 - 有很多納粹的東西
Dialogue: 0,1:01:31.14,1:01:33.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 在房間裏 有很多東西 - 哦
Dialogue: 0,1:01:35.35,1:01:38.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這不是我們的初衷
Dialogue: 0,1:01:40.28,1:01:41.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,澤夫
Dialogue: 0,1:01:42.36,1:01:44.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你還想繼續嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:01:45.32,1:01:48.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想 我必須完成
Dialogue: 0,1:01:49.12,1:01:50.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我必須
Dialogue: 0,1:01:51.33,1:01:54.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,畢竟 那是殺了我們全家的人
Dialogue: 0,1:03:15.08,1:03:16.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,露絲?
Dialogue: 0,1:03:19.04,1:03:20.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,露絲?
Dialogue: 0,1:03:21.38,1:03:24.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,露絲!
Dialogue: 0,1:03:43.02,1:03:44.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,1:03:45.48,1:03:46.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是
Dialogue: 0,1:03:50.95,1:03:53.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 我的天啊 謝謝你 太感謝你了
Dialogue: 0,1:03:57.58,1:03:58.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他還好嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:04:00.08,1:04:02.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 他有癡呆
Dialogue: 0,1:04:04.42,1:04:05.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 額
Dialogue: 0,1:04:06.09,1:04:08.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是從哪裏打來的? 我馬上過去
Dialogue: 0,1:04:11.30,1:04:12.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,裏諾紀念醫院?
Dialogue: 0,1:04:13.43,1:04:15.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 裏諾 內華達州? - 裏諾?
Dialogue: 0,1:04:16.43,1:04:18.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以跟我父親講話嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:04:22.60,1:04:24.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 謝謝 非常感謝你
Dialogue: 0,1:04:24.44,1:04:28.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夥計們 我要打噴嚏了
Dialogue: 0,1:04:41.04,1:04:42.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,1:04:43.33,1:04:44.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 你好啊 查爾斯
Dialogue: 0,1:04:45.92,1:04:49.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 哦 我很好 別擔心
Dialogue: 0,1:04:49.55,1:04:50.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你
Dialogue: 0,1:04:51.09,1:04:54.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫醫生別去打擾你
Dialogue: 0,1:04:54.34,1:04:55.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈
Dialogue: 0,1:04:56.10,1:04:58.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請你別擔心我了
Dialogue: 0,1:04:59.27,1:05:02.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 不 不用的 你別來醫院
Dialogue: 0,1:05:02.31,1:05:04.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你母親會來接我的
Dialogue: 0,1:05:06.06,1:05:08.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟她一起來?
Dialogue: 0,1:05:09.65,1:05:14.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對啊 我很好 沒事的 嗯 好的 再見
Dialogue: 0,1:05:23.96,1:05:25.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你喜歡卡通?
Dialogue: 0,1:05:25.50,1:05:27.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜歡迪士尼頻道的
Dialogue: 0,1:05:27.67,1:05:31.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 米老鼠嗎 - 不是 我喜歡飛哥與小佛
Dialogue: 0,1:05:31.26,1:05:32.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦
Dialogue: 0,1:05:32.67,1:05:34.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我沒聽說過他們
Dialogue: 0,1:05:35.01,1:05:36.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莫利 我馬上回來
Dialogue: 0,1:05:38.14,1:05:39.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你快做你的功課吧
Dialogue: 0,1:05:42.43,1:05:46.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你叫莫利? - 莫利·伊麗莎白
Dialogue: 0,1:05:46.52,1:05:50.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你喜歡糖果嗎 莫利·伊麗莎白
Dialogue: 0,1:05:51.36,1:05:52.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 額
Dialogue: 0,1:05:53.36,1:05:57.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我的大衣口袋裏有一些硬糖
Dialogue: 0,1:05:59.24,1:06:02.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直為我的孫子們準備一些在那裏
Dialogue: 0,1:06:03.04,1:06:04.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊
Dialogue: 0,1:06:05.54,1:06:07.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我找不到
Dialogue: 0,1:06:07.21,1:06:12.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 我妻子來的時候會帶一些的
Dialogue: 0,1:06:19.22,1:06:21.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你是澤夫嗎 - 是的
Dialogue: 0,1:06:22.39,1:06:24.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能看你的信嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:06:24.39,1:06:25.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以啊
Dialogue: 0,1:06:29.11,1:06:31.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 哇 你真有錢 - 什麼?
Dialogue: 0,1:06:42.58,1:06:44.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰是馬克思
Dialogue: 0,1:06:45.08,1:06:46.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,馬克思?
Dialogue: 0,1:06:47.33,1:06:48.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不清楚
Dialogue: 0,1:06:52.46,1:06:57.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 要不然你把信讀給我聽吧
Dialogue: 0,1:06:58.51,1:07:04.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"澤夫 有些事令人難以接受 可你得知道"
Dialogue: 0,1:07:05.31,1:07:10.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"首先 露絲已經過世了"
Dialogue: 0,1:07:10.65,1:07:12.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"她得了癌癥"
Dialogue: 0,1:07:13.36,1:07:18.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"她愛你 在她最後的時刻 你陪在她身邊 握著她的手"
Dialogue: 0,1:07:20.03,1:07:24.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"其次 你患有癡呆癥"
Dialogue: 0,1:07:25.29,1:07:28.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"最近你變得健忘了"
Dialogue: 0,1:07:30.04,1:07:33.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那很正常 老年人總是愛忘事
Dialogue: 0,1:07:33.46,1:07:34.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 是啊
Dialogue: 0,1:07:35.63,1:07:39.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"我們有著相似的經歷"
Dialogue: 0,1:07:39.68,1:07:43.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"我們都是奧斯維辛..."
Dialogue: 0,1:07:43.39,1:07:46.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 奧斯維辛 奧斯維辛 - "奧斯維辛的倖存者"
Dialogue: 0,1:07:47.39,1:07:53.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"看看你的左臂 你是98814號囚犯"
Dialogue: 0,1:08:00.53,1:08:03.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"戰爭結束時"
Dialogue: 0,1:08:03.32,1:08:06.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"我承諾自己"
Dialogue: 0,1:08:07.37,1:08:12.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"我要找到那些應為此負責的人"
Dialogue: 0,1:08:12.83,1:08:17.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"與西蒙·威森塔爾共事期間"
Dialogue: 0,1:08:17.42,1:08:22.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"我幫忙抓獲了大批前'納茲'分子"
Dialogue: 0,1:08:22.72,1:08:25.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"他們遍佈世界各地"
Dialogue: 0,1:08:25.22,1:08:28.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- '納茲'是什麼       - 是納粹 納粹
Dialogue: 0,1:08:31.10,1:08:32.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一種壞人
Dialogue: 0,1:08:36.44,1:08:39.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,六個月前 上帝賜我好運
Dialogue: 0,1:08:39.86,1:08:44.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當你搬到高級社區後
Dialogue: 0,1:08:44.87,1:08:48.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我立刻就認出了那個曾在奧斯維辛的你
Dialogue: 0,1:08:49.45,1:08:52.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,儘管你已經不記得我
Dialogue: 0,1:08:54.21,1:08:59.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們是那個獄區還健在的最後的倖存者
Dialogue: 0,1:08:59.55,1:09:03.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除我之外 你是唯一一個
Dialogue: 0,1:09:03.55,1:09:08.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還能認出殺害我們家人的兇手面孔的人
Dialogue: 0,1:09:10.52,1:09:13.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西蒙·威森塔爾堅持認為
Dialogue: 0,1:09:13.39,1:09:17.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有戰犯都應當受到公開審判
Dialogue: 0,1:09:18.78,1:09:23.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 我們不能給瓦利施這個機會
Dialogue: 0,1:09:24.74,1:09:27.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,儘管證據確鑿
Dialogue: 0,1:09:27.91,1:09:31.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他 跟我們一樣 很可能會
Dialogue: 0,1:09:31.54,1:09:34.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在被引渡德國之前已經去世
Dialogue: 0,1:09:36.17,1:09:41.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們都贊同 奧托·瓦利施必須死
Dialogue: 0,1:09:43.22,1:09:46.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你必須殺了他
Dialogue: 0,1:09:46.64,1:09:51.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"你答應等露絲去世你就去"
Dialogue: 0,1:09:51.77,1:09:55.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"你答應了我 你也答應了露絲"
Dialogue: 0,1:09:59.77,1:10:01.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你讀得很棒
Dialogue: 0,1:10:03.36,1:10:04.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝
Dialogue: 0,1:10:06.45,1:10:07.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,露絲是誰
Dialogue: 0,1:10:08.53,1:10:09.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的妻子
Dialogue: 0,1:10:10.33,1:10:12.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還以為她能帶點糖果給我
Dialogue: 0,1:10:13.66,1:10:15.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也希望來著
Dialogue: 0,1:10:22.26,1:10:25.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對 我要去假日旅館
Dialogue: 0,1:10:26.30,1:10:28.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔霍湖大道3961號
Dialogue: 0,1:10:29.80,1:10:30.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 在湖南岸 - 對
Dialogue: 0,1:10:30.93,1:10:32.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那得一個多小時
Dialogue: 0,1:10:32.93,1:10:37.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 哦 那... 我帶夠錢了 - 上車吧
Dialogue: 0,1:10:57.54,1:11:00.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你好 澤夫? - 是的
Dialogue: 0,1:11:01.59,1:11:03.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感謝上帝
Dialogue: 0,1:11:04.84,1:11:06.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在哪
Dialogue: 0,1:11:08.84,1:11:09.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,澤夫?
Dialogue: 0,1:11:10.85,1:11:11.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔霍
Dialogue: 0,1:11:12.85,1:11:16.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你明白你該怎麼做
Dialogue: 0,1:11:18.35,1:11:19.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只剩一個人了
Dialogue: 0,1:11:21.27,1:11:23.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 我明白
Dialogue: 0,1:11:26.36,1:11:27.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我該怎麼做
Dialogue: 0,1:11:36.00,1:11:36.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 早 - 早上好
Dialogue: 0,1:11:37.04,1:11:38.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想退房
Dialogue: 0,1:11:40.50,1:11:41.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你
Dialogue: 0,1:11:42.71,1:11:45.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你的手受傷了? - 哦 對 是的
Dialogue: 0,1:11:45.42,1:11:47.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 它...還好了 還能動 - 不錯
Dialogue: 0,1:11:48.76,1:11:51.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 總共106美元20美分
Dialogue: 0,1:11:52.89,1:11:56.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想搭出租的錢是夠了
Dialogue: 0,1:11:58.60,1:12:01.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 呃 我們也能用信用卡的
Dialogue: 0,1:12:02.02,1:12:03.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,1:12:04.57,1:12:05.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你
Dialogue: 0,1:12:07.07,1:12:10.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔霍? 他在塔霍搞什麼鬼
Dialogue: 0,1:12:11.45,1:12:13.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我正在租車
Dialogue: 0,1:12:13.72,1:12:15.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我會開車過去
Dialogue: 0,1:12:15.87,1:12:16.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,1:12:16.91,1:12:18.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 聽著 你能試著找到
Dialogue: 0,1:12:18.51,1:12:20.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他搭的那輛出租所屬公司的名字嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:12:22.00,1:12:23.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你
Dialogue: 0,1:13:14.84,1:13:16.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,需要幫忙嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:13:17.47,1:13:20.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魯迪·庫蘭德 他在這住嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:13:20.81,1:13:23.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 是的 - 我能跟他聊聊嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:13:24.15,1:13:26.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 他還在睡覺 - 哦
Dialogue: 0,1:13:26.69,1:13:30.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 我能在這等他...醒來嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:13:31.99,1:13:33.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是要緊事
Dialogue: 0,1:13:34.53,1:13:35.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼事啊
Dialogue: 0,1:13:35.78,1:13:37.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 是私事
Dialogue: 0,1:13:37.99,1:13:39.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且他認得我 他認得我
Dialogue: 0,1:13:39.49,1:13:41.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很久以前就認識他了
Dialogue: 0,1:13:43.75,1:13:46.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 進來吧 - 哦 謝謝你 謝謝你
Dialogue: 0,1:13:49.13,1:13:52.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 需要來杯咖啡嗎 您叫... - 古特曼
Dialogue: 0,1:13:53.47,1:13:55.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行 咖啡挺好 謝謝你
Dialogue: 0,1:13:55.64,1:13:59.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 呃 黑咖啡就好 - 在客廳坐會兒
Dialogue: 0,1:13:59.56,1:14:00.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去煮咖啡
Dialogue: 0,1:14:15.20,1:14:17.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我們家幾年前重聚的時候照的
Dialogue: 0,1:14:18.87,1:14:20.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢
Dialogue: 0,1:14:20.45,1:14:22.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是個大家庭
Dialogue: 0,1:14:22.91,1:14:25.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我父親總愛說他生了一支足球隊
Dialogue: 0,1:14:25.54,1:14:26.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是老小
Dialogue: 0,1:14:27.88,1:14:29.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你母親有多大
Dialogue: 0,1:14:29.71,1:14:31.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她年輕多了 父親是二婚
Dialogue: 0,1:14:33.80,1:14:36.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 謝謝你 - 古特曼先生 我能問您個問題麼
Dialogue: 0,1:14:38.05,1:14:40.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您的事跟奧斯維辛有關麼
Dialogue: 0,1:14:42.10,1:14:43.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,1:14:44.64,1:14:46.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我父親可不願談論那事
Dialogue: 0,1:14:46.94,1:14:48.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦
Dialogue: 0,1:14:49.56,1:14:51.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我理解
Dialogue: 0,1:14:53.48,1:14:55.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您願意跟我們共進早餐嗎 古特曼先生
Dialogue: 0,1:14:55.86,1:14:57.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做了些烤蘋果餅
Dialogue: 0,1:14:57.24,1:14:59.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不太餓 真是感謝你
Dialogue: 0,1:15:00.16,1:15:02.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不會打擾你太久的
Dialogue: 0,1:15:02.79,1:15:04.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你確定? 這可是家傳秘製
Dialogue: 0,1:15:04.95,1:15:08.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 是的 我確定 可還是謝謝你
Dialogue: 0,1:15:08.88,1:15:11.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您等我下 我去告訴父親您來了
Dialogue: 0,1:15:12.09,1:15:13.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 好的
Dialogue: 0,1:15:34.61,1:15:35.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 你是誰
Dialogue: 0,1:15:36.28,1:15:38.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 我是澤夫
Dialogue: 0,1:15:38.61,1:15:39.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 嗨 澤夫 - 英格
Dialogue: 0,1:15:45.29,1:15:46.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是誰
Dialogue: 0,1:15:47.29,1:15:51.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是你外公的老朋友
Dialogue: 0,1:16:46.72,1:16:47.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你喜歡瓦格納?
Dialogue: 0,1:16:50.85,1:16:54.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 我一直都喜愛瓦格納
Dialogue: 0,1:16:55.90,1:17:00.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我女兒說來了個我認識的奧斯維辛人
Dialogue: 0,1:17:02.07,1:17:04.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但作為一個倖存者不應該喜歡瓦格納的 不是嗎 (瓦格納 德國作曲家 種族主義者 反猶太主義者)
Dialogue: 0,1:17:04.82,1:17:07.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,音樂又不可恨
Dialogue: 0,1:17:10.71,1:17:14.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我 呃 沒能在那些照片中認出你
Dialogue: 0,1:17:15.71,1:17:16.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是...
Dialogue: 0,1:17:22.97,1:17:23.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的聲音...
Dialogue: 0,1:17:28.14,1:17:29.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒變
Dialogue: 0,1:17:34.40,1:17:37.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道有一天你會來找我
Dialogue: 0,1:17:39.11,1:17:40.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外公 澤夫是你朋友嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:17:41.03,1:17:43.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,英格 請你回廚房去
Dialogue: 0,1:17:44.24,1:17:47.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得跟我朋友探討些事
Dialogue: 0,1:17:50.12,1:17:52.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我沒忘記你
Dialogue: 0,1:17:53.41,1:17:56.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來吧...我們到外面去
Dialogue: 0,1:17:57.38,1:18:01.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想讓我的家人聽見...我們要說的事
Dialogue: 0,1:18:07.26,1:18:08.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經有很久...
Dialogue: 0,1:18:10.39,1:18:12.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒人認出從前的我了
Dialogue: 0,1:18:15.14,1:18:17.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我甚至記不清有多久
Dialogue: 0,1:18:20.44,1:18:24.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這些年來 人們盯著我看
Dialogue: 0,1:18:25.11,1:18:29.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就以為他們認出我了 其實他們從來沒有
Dialogue: 0,1:18:32.12,1:18:36.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或許他們只是太害怕 所以什麼都不敢說
Dialogue: 0,1:18:39.96,1:18:45.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有時候 我會到這來 說出自己的名字
Dialogue: 0,1:18:48.30,1:18:50.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我自言自語
Dialogue: 0,1:18:51.47,1:18:54.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重新回憶起以前的那個我
Dialogue: 0,1:18:57.35,1:19:01.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是唯一一種讓我知道自己存在過的方式
Dialogue: 0,1:19:03.03,1:19:05.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我變成現在這個人之前的那個自我
Dialogue: 0,1:19:07.28,1:19:13.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 靠謊言過活算什麼人生
Dialogue: 0,1:19:16.00,1:19:18.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直都知道你會找到我
Dialogue: 0,1:19:24.84,1:19:26.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經過了太久
Dialogue: 0,1:19:27.26,1:19:28.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在我們都是老人了
Dialogue: 0,1:19:30.34,1:19:35.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把你的手拿開 奧托
Dialogue: 0,1:19:37.85,1:19:38.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼
Dialogue: 0,1:19:38.94,1:19:42.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說 "把你的手拿開"
Dialogue: 0,1:19:43.94,1:19:47.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你叫我奧托?
Dialogue: 0,1:19:48.03,1:19:49.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想你弄糊塗了
Dialogue: 0,1:19:49.24,1:19:53.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有 你的名字叫奧托·瓦利施
Dialogue: 0,1:19:53.37,1:19:57.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是奧斯維辛的一個獄長 You were a Blockfuhrer at Auschwitz.
Dialogue: 0,1:19:57.50,1:20:01.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你殺了我的家人
Dialogue: 0,1:20:03.17,1:20:04.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你瘋了嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:20:07.01,1:20:08.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你自欺欺人這麼久
Dialogue: 0,1:20:08.94,1:20:12.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你自己都信以為真了
Dialogue: 0,1:20:13.97,1:20:14.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...
Dialogue: 0,1:20:17.56,1:20:19.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不明白
Dialogue: 0,1:20:19.23,1:20:20.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我來幫你
Dialogue: 0,1:20:22.40,1:20:24.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弄明白
Dialogue: 0,1:20:34.28,1:20:36.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺像我們開了家旅館
Dialogue: 0,1:20:37.95,1:20:40.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去告訴外公早飯好了
Dialogue: 0,1:20:43.88,1:20:45.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 是誰啊 - 我叫查爾斯·古特曼
Dialogue: 0,1:20:45.84,1:20:47.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我父親在這
Dialogue: 0,1:20:48.09,1:20:50.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨 真抱歉打擾您
Dialogue: 0,1:20:50.59,1:20:54.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是我聽說不久前有輛出租車載我爸爸到這
Dialogue: 0,1:20:54.93,1:20:56.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 他跟我父親在外面
Dialogue: 0,1:20:58.43,1:20:59.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感謝上帝
Dialogue: 0,1:21:00.56,1:21:03.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他已經失蹤一周了
Dialogue: 0,1:21:03.94,1:21:05.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失蹤?
Dialogue: 0,1:21:06.32,1:21:09.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 難以置信 跟我來 - 謝謝
Dialogue: 0,1:21:22.25,1:21:24.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 爸? - 哦 上帝啊
Dialogue: 0,1:21:24.29,1:21:27.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 媽媽 - 請別緊張
Dialogue: 0,1:21:27.21,1:21:28.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別害怕
Dialogue: 0,1:21:28.55,1:21:32.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸 你為什麼不 呃 把槍放低些
Dialogue: 0,1:21:33.63,1:21:35.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 查爾斯? - 啊
Dialogue: 0,1:21:36.14,1:21:38.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你在這幹嘛 - 呃...
Dialogue: 0,1:21:39.14,1:21:40.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸 把槍放下
Dialogue: 0,1:21:41.31,1:21:44.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 把槍放下 爸 - 不 不
Dialogue: 0,1:21:45.15,1:21:47.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除非他說出真相
Dialogue: 0,1:21:50.28,1:21:51.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼你要這樣做
Dialogue: 0,1:21:52.36,1:21:54.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告訴她們你是誰
Dialogue: 0,1:21:54.36,1:21:57.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請你別發瘋了
Dialogue: 0,1:21:57.16,1:21:59.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告訴她們你做了什麼
Dialogue: 0,1:21:59.91,1:22:02.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 放過她們 拜託了 - 說英語
Dialogue: 0,1:22:02.50,1:22:03.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我求你了
Dialogue: 0,1:22:04.04,1:22:06.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要讓她們聽懂你說的
Dialogue: 0,1:22:06.67,1:22:08.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸 他在說什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,1:22:08.92,1:22:11.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別聽他的 他瘋了
Dialogue: 0,1:22:12.67,1:22:13.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:22:16.64,1:22:18.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的選擇很簡單
Dialogue: 0,1:22:19.10,1:22:21.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以說出真相讓她活下來
Dialogue: 0,1:22:21.39,1:22:24.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也可以撒謊 然後看著她倒下
Dialogue: 0,1:22:24.18,1:22:25.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給你三秒鐘
Dialogue: 0,1:22:25.27,1:22:26.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 一 - 拜託 別這樣
Dialogue: 0,1:22:26.35,1:22:28.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 二 - 求你了 朝我開槍吧
Dialogue: 0,1:22:28.27,1:22:29.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 爸 停下 - 三
Dialogue: 0,1:22:29.36,1:22:30.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 好吧
Dialogue: 0,1:22:31.69,1:22:33.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧
Dialogue: 0,1:22:42.37,1:22:44.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在戰爭期間
Dialogue: 0,1:22:46.42,1:22:48.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是囚犯
Dialogue: 0,1:22:48.71,1:22:49.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大點聲
Dialogue: 0,1:22:52.38,1:22:54.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 在戰爭期間我不是囚犯 - 再大點!
Dialogue: 0,1:22:56.05,1:22:58.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在戰爭期間我不是囚犯!
Dialogue: 0,1:23:09.06,1:23:10.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是個納粹
Dialogue: 0,1:23:14.11,1:23:15.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是個黨衛軍
Dialogue: 0,1:23:16.99,1:23:19.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是奧斯維辛集中營的一個獄長 I was a Blockfuhrer at Auschwitz.
Dialogue: 0,1:23:20.74,1:23:22.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你殺過人嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:23:23.58,1:23:24.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,1:23:25.45,1:23:30.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 爺爺 你殺過人? - 你殺了多少人
Dialogue: 0,1:23:31.29,1:23:32.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不清楚
Dialogue: 0,1:23:33.46,1:23:34.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很多人
Dialogue: 0,1:23:37.34,1:23:40.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在告訴她們你的真名
Dialogue: 0,1:23:47.64,1:23:49.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的名字叫...
Dialogue: 0,1:23:52.31,1:23:53.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,庫尼伯特·斯德姆
Dialogue: 0,1:23:54.73,1:23:55.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不對
Dialogue: 0,1:23:56.61,1:23:58.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的名字叫瓦利施!
Dialogue: 0,1:23:59.03,1:24:01.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 就是庫尼伯特·斯德姆
Dialogue: 0,1:24:01.49,1:24:03.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你叫奧托·瓦利施!
Dialogue: 0,1:24:04.12,1:24:05.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,1:24:06.62,1:24:10.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你 你叫奧托·瓦利施
Dialogue: 0,1:24:14.13,1:24:16.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在撒謊
Dialogue: 0,1:24:17.26,1:24:18.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有
Dialogue: 0,1:24:21.09,1:24:24.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是70年來我第一次說真話
Dialogue: 0,1:24:26.18,1:24:28.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你才是奧托·瓦利施
Dialogue: 0,1:24:30.23,1:24:34.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是庫尼伯特·斯德姆 我們都是奧斯維辛的獄長
Dialogue: 0,1:24:35.52,1:24:38.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不...
Dialogue: 0,1:24:38.15,1:24:39.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是個囚犯
Dialogue: 0,1:24:40.15,1:24:41.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看你的胳膊
Dialogue: 0,1:24:42.45,1:24:47.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是98814號 我是98813號
Dialogue: 0,1:24:49.12,1:24:54.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我們互相紋的 這是我們唯一的逃生辦法
Dialogue: 0,1:25:10.73,1:25:11.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸?
Dialogue: 0,1:25:13.69,1:25:14.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是真的嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:25:15.56,1:25:19.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 都是謊言 都是謊言
Dialogue: 0,1:25:19.74,1:25:21.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這不是真的
Dialogue: 0,1:25:21.78,1:25:23.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謊言?
Dialogue: 0,1:25:26.53,1:25:28.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎麼能忘記呢
Dialogue: 0,1:25:29.33,1:25:32.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你給自己取名叫澤夫 因為它是狼的意思
Dialogue: 0,1:25:34.17,1:25:36.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說我倆都是狼
Dialogue: 0,1:25:47.55,1:25:49.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 我的上帝
Dialogue: 0,1:26:03.15,1:26:04.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我記得
Dialogue: 0,1:26:08.37,1:26:09.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸?
Dialogue: 0,1:26:12.33,1:26:13.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸
Dialogue: 0,1:26:17.17,1:26:18.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在 我們還在等待
Dialogue: 0,1:26:18.50,1:26:20.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來自塔霍湖警察局的消息
Dialogue: 0,1:26:20.38,1:26:23.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們仍未向記者透露或發佈官方聲明
Dialogue: 0,1:26:23.67,1:26:24.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他們向我們保證
Dialogue: 0,1:26:24.74,1:26:27.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不出一小時我們將悉數獲知
Dialogue: 0,1:26:27.93,1:26:31.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居民們 如你所想的那樣 十分震驚
Dialogue: 0,1:26:31.64,1:26:35.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我同一些不願在攝像機前發表言論的人談了談
Dialogue: 0,1:26:35.35,1:26:38.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其中一位告訴我...
Dialogue: 0,1:26:38.27,1:26:42.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 可憐的澤夫 - 悲劇 真正的悲劇
Dialogue: 0,1:26:42.73,1:26:45.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他一定不知道他在做什麼
Dialogue: 0,1:26:49.49,1:26:52.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他很清楚他在做什麼
Dialogue: 0,1:26:54.37,1:26:56.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼 你是什麼意思 馬克斯
Dialogue: 0,1:27:00.88,1:27:03.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他殺掉的那個人
Dialogue: 0,1:27:04.42,1:27:08.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫做庫尼伯特·斯德姆
Dialogue: 0,1:27:11.81,1:27:13.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而澤夫的真名
Dialogue: 0,1:27:16.31,1:27:19.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫做奧托·瓦利施
Dialogue: 0,1:27:23.32,1:27:25.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是他們兩個...
Dialogue: 0,1:27:27.24,1:27:30.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,殺害了我的家人
