[Script Info]
由101eagle合成

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,华文楷体,19,&H00E0E0E0,&HF0000000,&H000D0500,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,0,0,3,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.06,0:00:09.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,字幕来源：奇遇电影字幕组
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.39,0:00:20.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,字幕特效：101eagle
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.68,0:00:31.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,压制：101eagle
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.72,0:00:43.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上传UP：101eagle
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.06,0:01:05.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,露丝?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.40,0:01:16.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,露丝?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.69,0:01:48.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我妻子在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.31,0:01:51.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,古特曼先生 你可不能这样偷偷在背后吓我一跳
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.48,0:01:54.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我太太呢 露丝在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.15,0:01:57.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很抱歉 古特曼先生
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.16,0:02:01.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你太太大约一周前过世了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.54,0:02:05.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.72,0:02:19.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 请问你是?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.59,0:02:21.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫保拉
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.55,0:02:23.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾是古特曼太太的护理
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.56,0:02:27.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们家请我再多待一两周
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.23,0:02:30.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去吃点早餐吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.23,0:02:33.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃完早餐你会感觉好些的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.65,0:02:34.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的鞋在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.53,0:02:37.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 我去给你拿拖鞋
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.82,0:02:39.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用你的帽子去换双拖鞋 可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.66,0:02:41.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 进来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.79,0:02:46.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 早安 泽夫 - 早安
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.54,0:02:49.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但愿你没有很饿 早餐和往常一样少得可怜
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.50,0:02:51.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系 我不是很饿
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.42,0:02:54.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是塞莱 你太太以前的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.88,0:02:57.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道她是谁 我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.39,0:03:08.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能给我们私聊的时间吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.60,0:03:10.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.52,0:03:12.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是马克斯
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.60,0:03:14.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没必要告诉我所有人的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.28,0:03:25.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚是为露丝服丧的最后一晚对吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.62,0:03:30.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还记不记得你说过露丝死后
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.91,0:03:32.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.30,0:03:37.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不记得了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.80,0:03:40.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事 没事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.72,0:03:42.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.55,0:03:44.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记下了所有事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.64,0:03:46.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.97,0:03:48.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会记起来的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.81,0:03:57.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我来 劳森鲍姆先生
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.38,0:04:16.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.34,0:04:19.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道这张照片什么时候照的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.84,0:04:24.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们结婚的时候照的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.43,0:04:26.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,1946年
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.01,0:04:29.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是在德国遇见奶奶的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.35,0:04:31.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 不 不是
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.60,0:04:36.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在美国遇见她的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.90,0:04:38.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在康尼
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.61,0:04:41.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 在康尼岛 - 对
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.44,0:04:44.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 为什么不拿给你哥哥看看呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.03,0:04:48.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚当 快看这个
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.58,0:04:54.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给 把这个放口袋里
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.42,0:04:57.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.04,0:04:59.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站起来
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.50,0:05:01.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉所有人你累了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.55,0:05:06.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后独自一人看完
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.34,0:05:08.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,独自一人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.97,0:05:10.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你累了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.76,0:05:11.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 对
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.06,0:05:13.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样 好的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.82,0:05:22.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原谅我 我
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.53,0:05:25.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有点累 我想我该去睡觉了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.03,0:05:28.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.70,0:05:30.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是漫长的一周
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.33,0:05:33.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.47,0:06:34.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 佩恩车站 对吗 - 是的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.03,0:06:55.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后通知
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.54,0:06:57.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,49号湖滨列车要发车了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.75,0:06:59.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后通知
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.08,0:07:03.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后通知 要开车了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.01,0:07:09.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是你妈妈吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.55,0:07:11.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.10,0:07:14.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不和你一起吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.85,0:07:17.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我去找我爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.98,0:07:20.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.52,0:07:23.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你是一个人咯
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.11,0:07:26.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是一个人 我的兄弟们在那呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.53,0:07:29.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.03,0:07:31.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 我看见了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.78,0:07:36.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也是去克利夫兰吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.62,0:07:37.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.74,0:07:39.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不坐飞机呢 那样更快
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.12,0:07:43.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.50,0:07:45.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可不是个好理由
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.21,0:07:49.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个不知天高地厚的小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.71,0:07:51.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你为什么不坐飞机去克利夫兰呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.80,0:07:53.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三张飞机票太贵了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.09,0:07:55.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我爸妈说的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.22,0:07:57.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 这是个好理由
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.89,0:08:03.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不坐飞机是因为我朋友在他写给我的信里
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.15,0:08:06.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我要坐火车
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.11,0:08:11.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想这也是个好理由
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.95,0:08:13.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫泰勒
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.91,0:08:16.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很高兴认识你 泰勒
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.08,0:08:18.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫泽夫
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.54,0:08:20.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个奇怪的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.95,0:08:23.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在希伯来语里 它的意思是"狼"
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.87,0:08:26.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真酷
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.97,0:08:36.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我为你计划了所有事项
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.51,0:08:40.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你必须精准地执行这些步骤
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.18,0:08:44.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每做完一项就划掉一项
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.86,0:08:49.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们已经通知过警方 他们向社区发出了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.90,0:08:52.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,银色警报并启动反911系统
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.82,0:08:55.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们...我们这边会竭尽全力
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.57,0:08:57.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 确实难以接受... - 我只是不敢相信
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.91,0:09:00.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生的这一切
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.20,0:09:02.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们感到万分的抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.79,0:09:05.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会密切留意每个人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.92,0:09:07.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但...我相信你能理解的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.88,0:09:09.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们能帮到什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.59,0:09:12.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了付钱让你们看丢人还有别的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.30,0:09:14.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你父亲有信用卡吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.09,0:09:17.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他一旦使用你可以让银行联系你
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.64,0:09:22.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.81,0:09:25.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你母亲的护工告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.73,0:09:28.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你父亲最近特别糊涂
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.31,0:09:30.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 他患有痴呆
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.82,0:09:33.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而这也是起初我母亲把父亲一起带到这来的原因
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.74,0:09:34.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白 但是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.65,0:09:37.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通常在配偶死亡后
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.66,0:09:40.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会出现更多认知障碍
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.99,0:09:44.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有没有注意到你父亲的情绪波动
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.33,0:09:47.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且他几乎不再弹钢琴了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.92,0:09:52.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我察觉到了一些 查尔斯
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.30,0:09:56.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想那时我们
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.84,0:10:00.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在你母亲的事情上太操劳了以至于我没有理会这些
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.93,0:10:05.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安心吧 我们会让他在你知晓前平安回来的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.81,0:10:07.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这些情况下
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.35,0:10:09.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人不会走太远
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.11,0:10:16.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,露丝?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.20,0:10:20.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,露丝?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.04,0:10:25.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚当?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.37,0:10:27.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你奶奶在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.37,0:10:30.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚当?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.92,0:10:32.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你奶奶呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.21,0:10:34.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在跟我说话吗 泽夫
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.13,0:10:36.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我问你奶奶在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.38,0:10:41.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个在纽约州 一个在俄亥俄州
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.76,0:10:45.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你妹妹呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.18,0:10:47.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.02,0:10:50.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别玩那玩意儿了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.23,0:10:52.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回答我
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.27,0:10:56.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你...还好吗 泽夫
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.28,0:10:59.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.82,0:11:01.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在火车上
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.87,0:11:03.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去哪
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.28,0:11:04.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克利夫兰
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.91,0:11:06.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克利夫兰?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.16,0:11:09.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要去见一个朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.00,0:11:11.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.38,0:11:14.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你写了你口袋里那封信的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.17,0:11:21.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能把我的游戏机还给我了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.15,0:11:41.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,露丝死了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.45,0:11:49.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泽夫
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.79,0:11:52.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要去和我兄弟们坐一会
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.50,0:12:33.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你好 - 嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.29,0:12:35.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨 我... 我儿子在火车上时你和他挨着
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.08,0:12:38.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你看起来有些糊涂了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.84,0:12:40.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 是的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.80,0:12:42.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我对此感到很抱歉 - 噢 不会不会
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.84,0:12:44.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不需要道歉 我们...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.88,0:12:47.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 只是想确认你没事 - 噢我没事的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.76,0:12:49.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 我很好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.06,0:12:51.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,额...你要去哪需要帮忙吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.02,0:12:54.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用 会有人来接我的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.81,0:12:57.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我朋友说他会举一个
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.02,0:12:59.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,写有我姓名的牌子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.98,0:13:02.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 我们会帮你找
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.86,0:13:05.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些车刚到
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.78,0:13:11.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是姓古特曼吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.49,0:13:12.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.33,0:13:14.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你坐的车看起来很时髦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.42,0:13:18.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见 泽夫
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.29,0:13:20.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见 再见
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.21,0:13:22.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧 孩子们
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.46,0:13:24.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 古特曼先生? - 是的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.92,0:13:26.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.19,0:13:40.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 下午好 - 下午好
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.36,0:13:42.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎样帮到你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.86,0:13:46.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我朋友向我推荐了你的店
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.40,0:13:48.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 请转告你的朋友我们很感谢他的推荐
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.03,0:13:51.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你想要拿哪种呢 - 噢...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.91,0:13:53.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小一点的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.91,0:13:55.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然有
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.91,0:13:57.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 能给我看看你的驾驶证吗 - 好的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.05,0:14:07.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这儿...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.18,0:14:09.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.97,0:14:12.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比奇伍德 很棒的小镇
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.26,0:14:13.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 但...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.18,0:14:15.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们搬走了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.39,0:14:18.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们搬去离我儿子更近的住处了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.36,0:14:21.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你拿我的驾驶证干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.98,0:14:25.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在把你的信息输入FBI的背景调查数据库
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.07,0:14:27.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.36,0:14:29.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们在调查什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.57,0:14:31.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一大堆资料 看你是否为已被定罪的重刑犯
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.91,0:14:33.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,涉嫌暴力犯罪
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.62,0:14:35.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被军队惩戒免职
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.33,0:14:38.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是否智力健全 或者是否过去五年内
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.41,0:14:40.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不止一次酒驾 是否是个逃犯
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.46,0:14:42.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 或者最近被指控重罪 - 逃犯?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.21,0:14:44.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 比如你在逃脱法律的制裁
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.96,0:14:47.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得我看起来逃得动吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.34,0:14:54.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 给你看些小一点的手枪
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.26,0:14:57.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们应有尽有 西格绍尔 M1911 格洛克（均为手枪型号）
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.39,0:14:58.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,单动枪 双动枪
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.06,0:15:01.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 先生 你懂枪吗 - 额...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.36,0:15:04.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 不懂 怎么了 - 那没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.65,0:15:06.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们这什么类型的都有
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.65,0:15:08.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 新手的话...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.99,0:15:10.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通常是用点22口径的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.49,0:15:12.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它很轻 易上手 后坐力很小
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.29,0:15:17.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得这就是我朋友建议的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.66,0:15:19.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 依我来看
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.50,0:15:22.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你买点22就相当于拥有了一把气枪
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.13,0:15:27.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 我不是在强行推销 但多花500块
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.21,0:15:30.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能拥有一把真正有制动能力的枪
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.38,0:15:34.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是格洛克17 9mm手枪
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.68,0:15:36.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,格洛克? 这是德国枪 对吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.06,0:15:39.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接近正确答案了 它产自奥地利
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.31,0:15:43.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是世界上最流行的执法手枪 不错吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.40,0:15:45.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它的后坐力非常小 所以应该不会伤到手
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.98,0:15:47.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但它肯定会伤到入侵者
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.94,0:15:50.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个好用吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.61,0:15:52.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但愿
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.49,0:15:53.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 它很简易
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.37,0:15:55.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 但是...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.03,0:15:58.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知你介不介意 可不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.29,0:16:00.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮我写个使用说明书
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.37,0:16:04.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然可以 我的意思是 我可以示范给你看怎么使用
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.04,0:16:08.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不了 那是很好 但拜托了 帮我写下来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.71,0:16:11.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有时候会健忘
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.39,0:16:21.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顾客至上 这没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.68,0:16:23.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 一切都妥当了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.56,0:16:25.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去拿支笔 然后
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.52,0:16:27.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮你写下使用说明
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.99,0:16:38.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 古特曼先生吗 - 对 古特曼
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.41,0:16:39.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么知道
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.62,0:16:42.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你朋友早些时候打过电话说你快到了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.41,0:16:44.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,房间已经为你准备好了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.25,0:16:46.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,房间号是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.17,0:16:49.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,125 就顺着走廊走
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.51,0:16:53.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我该付多少钱 - 已经付过了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.63,0:16:55.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,包括附加费
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.09,0:16:58.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 应你朋友的要求 我们为你订了明天早上的出租车
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.06,0:17:00.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.57,0:17:18.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 喂? - 喂
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.33,0:17:20.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 泽夫吗 - 是我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.79,0:17:22.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是马克斯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.29,0:17:25.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我指示了酒店一些事项
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.08,0:17:29.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你还好吗 - 是的我还好 马克斯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.30,0:17:33.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你拿到枪了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.30,0:17:35.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 拿到了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.38,0:17:37.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好 很好
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.14,0:17:40.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道该做什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.81,0:17:44.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照顾好自己 知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.64,0:17:48.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安好梦 马克斯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.35,0:17:49.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安 泽夫
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.19,0:18:30.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,露丝?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.15,0:18:33.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,露丝?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.20,0:18:39.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,露丝?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.57,0:18:42.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把灯打开好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.24,0:18:45.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太黑了 我看不...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.58,0:18:47.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看不清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.79,0:20:11.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你好 - 嗨
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.62,0:20:14.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请问鲁迪·库兰德在家吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.63,0:20:16.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在家 他在楼下
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.58,0:20:54.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.33,0:20:55.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鲁迪·库兰德?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.50,0:20:57.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.67,0:20:59.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是鲁迪·库兰德
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.84,0:21:01.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.26,0:21:02.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以...呃...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.84,0:21:03.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把电视关掉吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.51,0:21:11.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认识你吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.02,0:21:20.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在 请你...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.61,0:21:24.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站到窗户旁边
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.70,0:21:27.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.70,0:21:31.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站到窗户旁边
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.33,0:21:34.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你不告诉我你是谁还有你来这儿的原因
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.54,0:21:36.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我什么都不会做
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.29,0:21:38.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咱们还是别争了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.29,0:21:41.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站到窗边去
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.33,0:22:14.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在又要做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.54,0:22:22.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得亮堂些我才能看清你的脸
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.96,0:22:25.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 把头转过去 - 你是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.92,0:22:27.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别吼
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.55,0:22:28.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托 不要吼
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.34,0:22:31.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,按我说的做 抬起头来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.10,0:22:37.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是德国人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.10,0:22:39.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.40,0:22:42.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你也是德国人? (德语) - 是
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.57,0:22:45.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你多少岁了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.11,0:22:51.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你曾在德军服役吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.58,0:22:53.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在军队里做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.70,0:22:57.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 那都过去了 - 英语 请说英语
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.87,0:23:01.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我不喜欢说德语 - 那都是70年前了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.67,0:23:03.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我那时太年轻
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.13,0:23:04.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回答我的问题
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.09,0:23:08.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是犹太人?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.97,0:23:11.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.97,0:23:14.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你当时在奥斯维辛集中营吗 - 我不在
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.14,0:23:16.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都这个岁数了 还有必要撒谎吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.44,0:23:21.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在战争结束前
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.48,0:23:24.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都不知道奥斯维辛集中营的事
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.48,0:23:26.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当时在北非
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.48,0:23:29.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和隆美尔元帅一起
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.99,0:23:33.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你有证据吗 - 有
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.53,0:23:36.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在那边
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.00,0:23:50.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当我成为美国公民的时候 移民局的官员问我
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.09,0:23:53.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是否曾和纳粹政府
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.59,0:23:55.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有关联
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.93,0:23:58.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者是否曾在集中营工作
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.02,0:24:03.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的回答说
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.94,0:24:07.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 我效忠于我的国家 我是一名军人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.78,0:24:11.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我为自己身为德国人而自豪 所有人都为自己的国家而自豪
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.53,0:24:15.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我仍然为我为国家作出的贡献感到自豪
Dialogue: 0,0:24:22.79,0:24:24.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是隆美尔元帅
Dialogue: 0,0:24:26.75,0:24:28.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至于犹太人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:32.59,0:24:36.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我并不关心犹太人 我认为希特勒是对的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:37.76,0:24:40.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,犹太人给我们国家带来了太多麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:24:41.48,0:24:46.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认为我们是在驱逐他们 或是把他们安置在劳动营里...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:47.15,0:24:48.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而不是像他们所做的那样
Dialogue: 0,0:24:52.11,0:24:53.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那太可耻了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:54.53,0:24:55.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我没有做那些事
Dialogue: 0,0:25:08.92,0:25:12.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 喂? - 是马克斯吗
Dialogue: 0,0:25:12.92,0:25:13.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.63,0:25:15.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是泽夫
Dialogue: 0,0:25:16.01,0:25:17.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃... 不是...
Dialogue: 0,0:25:18.22,0:25:19.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是他
Dialogue: 0,0:25:20.85,0:25:23.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你确定吗 - 我确定
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.52,0:25:26.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你必须要继续
Dialogue: 0,0:25:27.73,0:25:29.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须履行
Dialogue: 0,0:25:30.19,0:25:31.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你曾经承诺过的
Dialogue: 0,0:25:47.00,0:25:49.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近些年来一直有传闻
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.13,0:25:53.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一些奥斯维辛集中营里的党卫队军官
Dialogue: 0,0:25:53.13,0:25:56.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在战争接近尾声的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:25:57.09,0:25:58.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冒名顶替了被处死的犹太人的身份
Dialogue: 0,0:25:59.76,0:26:02.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我中风后不久
Dialogue: 0,0:26:02.64,0:26:06.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有证据表明 一名奥斯维辛集中营军官
Dialogue: 0,0:26:06.77,0:26:10.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于19世纪40年代从德国移民
Dialogue: 0,0:26:10.31,0:26:14.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且最可能用假名鲁迪·库兰德
Dialogue: 0,0:26:14.28,0:26:16.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,继续生活
Dialogue: 0,0:26:17.20,0:26:19.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西蒙·维森塔尔中心(西蒙·维森塔尔中心是一个国际犹太人权组织 这组织是为了纪念纳粹在二次世界大战中被杀的犹太人而成立的)
Dialogue: 0,0:26:19.62,0:26:22.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到了四名在那个时期移民至此的
Dialogue: 0,0:26:22.95,0:26:25.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鲁迪·库兰德
Dialogue: 0,0:26:26.04,0:26:28.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然而 没有足够的证据
Dialogue: 0,0:26:28.67,0:26:30.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逮捕他们其中任何一人
Dialogue: 0,0:26:34.00,0:26:38.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的真名是奥托·瓦利施
Dialogue: 0,0:26:40.72,0:26:43.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你必须要找到他
Dialogue: 0,0:26:48.73,0:26:52.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我正在寻找我父亲 他已经将近90岁了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:53.86,0:26:56.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的名字叫泽夫
Dialogue: 0,0:26:56.19,0:26:57.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在寻找我的父亲
Dialogue: 0,0:26:58.36,0:26:59.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他90岁了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:00.03,0:27:02.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他几天前外出闲逛
Dialogue: 0,0:27:03.08,0:27:05.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的名字是泽夫·古特曼
Dialogue: 0,0:27:05.66,0:27:08.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道他是否随身携带了可以证明身份的证件
Dialogue: 0,0:27:09.00,0:27:11.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我甚至不确定他是否还记得自己的姓名
Dialogue: 0,0:27:11.96,0:27:15.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想知道有没有人被送进医院
Dialogue: 0,0:27:17.88,0:27:21.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得我还没报警吗
Dialogue: 0,0:27:28.14,0:27:29.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女士们先生们
Dialogue: 0,0:27:29.94,0:27:31.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们快到加拿大边境了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:31.40,0:27:34.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到时候大家都需要下车接受检查
Dialogue: 0,0:27:34.65,0:27:36.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果您能提前准备好您的护照或其他旅行证件
Dialogue: 0,0:27:37.07,0:27:39.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将节省不少时间 谢谢合作
Dialogue: 0,0:28:03.76,0:28:04.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请出示申报单
Dialogue: 0,0:28:07.26,0:28:08.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您此行的目的是?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:08.93,0:28:11.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜访一位朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:28:11.77,0:28:12.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您朋友的姓名是?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:12.85,0:28:14.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 鲁迪·库兰德 - 他住哪
Dialogue: 0,0:28:15.06,0:28:18.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,福伊尔·德斯...福伊尔...
Dialogue: 0,0:28:25.12,0:28:27.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我能看看吗 - 当然可以
Dialogue: 0,0:28:29.45,0:28:32.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 福伊尔·德斯先驱者养老院? - 是的
Dialogue: 0,0:28:32.37,0:28:34.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您将入住安大略省赫斯特的皇后汽车旅馆?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:34.79,0:28:35.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:28:36.17,0:28:37.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您将在加拿大停留多久
Dialogue: 0,0:28:38.13,0:28:40.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概两晚吧
Dialogue: 0,0:28:41.97,0:28:43.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,护照
Dialogue: 0,0:29:02.32,0:29:03.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生 您的护照过期了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:05.36,0:29:07.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 过期了? - 对
Dialogue: 0,0:29:10.33,0:29:12.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您有驾照吗
Dialogue: 0,0:29:12.16,0:29:13.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 当然有
Dialogue: 0,0:29:18.92,0:29:20.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍等
Dialogue: 0,0:29:37.90,0:29:39.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 您可以走了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:40.02,0:29:41.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过请您将护照延期
Dialogue: 0,0:29:43.24,0:29:46.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都这个岁数了 用不着了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:47.91,0:29:49.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祝您与朋友相聚愉快
Dialogue: 0,0:29:49.16,0:29:50.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:30:24.40,0:30:25.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打扰一下
Dialogue: 0,0:30:25.82,0:30:26.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,需要什么帮助吗 先生
Dialogue: 0,0:30:27.03,0:30:30.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鲁迪·库兰德在哪个房间
Dialogue: 0,0:30:30.91,0:30:32.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,库兰德?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:32.53,0:30:34.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 库兰德 他在238房
Dialogue: 0,0:30:35.04,0:30:38.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沿着这条走廊走 坐电梯
Dialogue: 0,0:30:38.29,0:30:41.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出电梯后 左转 再右转
Dialogue: 0,0:30:42.04,0:30:43.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,238号房就在你的左手边
Dialogue: 0,0:30:45.26,0:30:46.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:30:47.84,0:30:49.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我直接带您去您朋友的房间吧
Dialogue: 0,0:30:50.09,0:30:51.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:31:20.42,0:31:22.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是鲁迪·库兰德吗
Dialogue: 0,0:31:25.00,0:31:26.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鲁迪·库兰德?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:26.88,0:31:28.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是
Dialogue: 0,0:31:54.37,0:31:58.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你是鲁迪·库兰德? - 是的
Dialogue: 0,0:32:01.04,0:32:02.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是德国人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:32:03.00,0:32:04.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:32:07.50,0:32:10.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以前在奥斯维辛集中营吗
Dialogue: 0,0:32:14.14,0:32:15.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:32:19.22,0:32:22.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去过奥斯维辛集中营
Dialogue: 0,0:32:24.15,0:32:27.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我全家人都在
Dialogue: 0,0:32:28.69,0:32:30.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奥斯维辛集中营
Dialogue: 0,0:32:30.94,0:32:32.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被杀了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:35.03,0:32:36.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我感到很抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:32:38.45,0:32:40.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很...很抱歉?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:41.96,0:32:43.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:32:46.29,0:32:51.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的所作所为不是道个歉就足够的
Dialogue: 0,0:32:56.22,0:32:59.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发过誓我会杀死
Dialogue: 0,0:32:59.18,0:33:01.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀害我全家性命的那个人
Dialogue: 0,0:33:11.57,0:33:13.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是犹太人?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:14.11,0:33:15.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是同性恋
Dialogue: 0,0:33:21.16,0:33:23.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该是我道歉才对
Dialogue: 0,0:33:28.21,0:33:32.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 真的很抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:34:51.54,0:34:53.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莫什科夫斯基
Dialogue: 0,0:34:54.17,0:34:55.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道莫什科夫斯基?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:56.17,0:34:59.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以前的钢琴老师曾说
Dialogue: 0,0:34:59.13,0:35:01.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三位最伟大的作曲家分别是
Dialogue: 0,0:35:02.51,0:35:04.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,门德尔松 梅耶贝尔
Dialogue: 0,0:35:05.35,0:35:06.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及莫什科夫斯基
Dialogue: 0,0:35:07.18,0:35:09.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你现在还弹吗 - 噢...
Dialogue: 0,0:35:10.52,0:35:12.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:35:12.36,0:35:14.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我不知道 我不确定
Dialogue: 0,0:35:14.57,0:35:15.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么...
Dialogue: 0,0:35:16.69,0:35:19.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不试试呢
Dialogue: 0,0:35:20.45,0:35:22.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢... 好吧...
Dialogue: 0,0:35:25.87,0:35:27.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,门德尔松
Dialogue: 0,0:35:27.54,0:35:28.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概吧
Dialogue: 0,0:37:16.98,0:37:19.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好 先生 欢迎来到博伊西
Dialogue: 0,0:37:20.61,0:37:21.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您预定过了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:37:22.40,0:37:25.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这边有记录您早上8点需要出租车服务
Dialogue: 0,0:37:25.49,0:37:30.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们将于6点起供应免费早餐
Dialogue: 0,0:37:32.62,0:37:35.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果您径直穿过左手边的大厅...
Dialogue: 0,0:37:43.01,0:37:44.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我来帮助您 好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:37:51.89,0:37:55.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有件事 我忘了带衣服了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:55.52,0:37:56.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 换洗的衣服 - 噢
Dialogue: 0,0:37:57.02,0:37:59.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个完全不是问题
Dialogue: 0,0:37:59.65,0:38:02.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每整点都有一趟公共汽车从我们这里发往市中心
Dialogue: 0,0:38:02.53,0:38:06.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这趟车会将您送到北密尔沃基路的商场
Dialogue: 0,0:38:07.49,0:38:09.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您可以在那买到您需要的所有东西
Dialogue: 0,0:38:15.58,0:38:18.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生 你需要我帮您预订吗
Dialogue: 0,0:38:19.50,0:38:20.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生 您还好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:38:23.00,0:38:26.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您现在想去您的房间了吗 好勒
Dialogue: 0,0:38:40.52,0:38:42.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 您需要我帮你找什么吗 - 噢 是的
Dialogue: 0,0:38:42.82,0:38:45.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想买一件新衬衫
Dialogue: 0,0:38:45.86,0:38:47.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们有很多短袖系扣衬衫
Dialogue: 0,0:38:48.03,0:38:48.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 是吗 - 您要看看吗
Dialogue: 0,0:38:49.41,0:38:50.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 劳驾 - 不客气
Dialogue: 0,0:38:51.07,0:38:53.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,季末的时候最划算了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:53.33,0:38:54.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:39:03.80,0:39:05.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 先生 您触响了警报
Dialogue: 0,0:39:06.09,0:39:07.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得检查一下您的包
Dialogue: 0,0:39:07.92,0:39:09.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 我看起来像个贼吗
Dialogue: 0,0:39:10.34,0:39:12.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 跟这没关系 先生 您触响了警报
Dialogue: 0,0:39:12.72,0:39:14.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎样我都得检查一下您的包
Dialogue: 0,0:39:15.01,0:39:16.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是收据
Dialogue: 0,0:39:17.35,0:39:18.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 问题在这儿
Dialogue: 0,0:39:18.94,0:39:20.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们忘记把安全标签取下了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:21.10,0:39:22.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还得检查一下您另外一个包 先生
Dialogue: 0,0:39:34.95,0:39:35.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是一把格洛克吗
Dialogue: 0,0:39:37.00,0:39:38.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:39:41.08,0:39:43.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我想起了我第一把枪
Dialogue: 0,0:39:44.79,0:39:46.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祝您今天过得愉快 先生
Dialogue: 0,0:39:46.55,0:39:50.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 给您 非常感谢 - 谢谢 谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:40:46.56,0:40:48.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您要续杯吗
Dialogue: 0,0:40:48.44,0:40:50.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 好的 谢谢 - 不客气
Dialogue: 0,0:40:51.69,0:40:54.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能告诉我从这儿到布鲁诺有多远吗
Dialogue: 0,0:40:54.66,0:40:57.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从没去过布鲁诺 不过那是在奥怀希郡
Dialogue: 0,0:40:57.70,0:41:00.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 我觉得大概是三四十分钟的路程吧
Dialogue: 0,0:41:00.66,0:41:02.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 噢 - 我听说那儿的乡下很漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:41:02.91,0:41:04.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从没去过但是我朋友...
Dialogue: 0,0:41:04.58,0:41:05.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 噢 - 啊
Dialogue: 0,0:41:05.83,0:41:07.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 我很抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:41:07.13,0:41:08.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我把咖啡撒到你的信上了 - 噢 天啊
Dialogue: 0,0:41:09.05,0:41:10.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手 你把我的信毁了
Dialogue: 0,0:41:10.13,0:41:11.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 不要 不要 不要 - 我很抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:41:12.05,0:41:15.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这封信很重要 住手 住手 住手
Dialogue: 0,0:41:22.18,0:41:24.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了我
Dialogue: 0,0:41:25.10,0:41:29.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是唯一一个
Dialogue: 0,0:41:31.07,0:41:34.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仍然能认出
Dialogue: 0,0:41:37.95,0:41:41.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那人长相的人
Dialogue: 0,0:41:42.79,0:41:48.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他杀害了我们的家人
Dialogue: 0,0:42:37.63,0:42:39.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 没人在家吗 - 没有
Dialogue: 0,0:42:39.76,0:42:41.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您想让我把您送到其他地方吗
Dialogue: 0,0:42:41.55,0:42:44.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 不不不 我再等等 - 给您
Dialogue: 0,0:42:46.31,0:42:49.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您什么时候需要我回来接您就给我打个电话
Dialogue: 0,0:42:49.81,0:42:51.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我该付你多少钱
Dialogue: 0,0:42:51.98,0:42:54.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 您已经付过钱了 记得吗
Dialogue: 0,0:42:56.32,0:42:58.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你需要乘车给我打个电话就行
Dialogue: 0,0:43:48.87,0:43:49.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早安
Dialogue: 0,0:43:53.25,0:43:55.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也早安 小可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:44:06.72,0:44:07.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错...
Dialogue: 0,0:44:11.39,0:44:12.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该吃晚饭了 劳森鲍姆先生
Dialogue: 0,0:44:15.73,0:44:17.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我带点吃的来 可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:44:18.73,0:44:20.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您确定吗 您已经在房间里待了一整天了
Dialogue: 0,0:44:21.07,0:44:23.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我确定 - 好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:44:54.90,0:44:56.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能帮您什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:44:57.06,0:44:59.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来找鲁迪·库兰德
Dialogue: 0,0:45:03.95,0:45:06.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 您来对地方了 但是...
Dialogue: 0,0:45:09.16,0:45:11.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的爸爸3个月前去世了
Dialogue: 0,0:45:12.71,0:45:15.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 我不知道这个 我很遗憾
Dialogue: 0,0:45:23.47,0:45:24.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您在这儿等了多久了
Dialogue: 0,0:45:26.47,0:45:27.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一整天
Dialogue: 0,0:45:30.97,0:45:32.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您要喝点什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:45:34.27,0:45:35.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那好极了
Dialogue: 0,0:45:36.81,0:45:37.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:45:37.90,0:45:40.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我自己也来点
Dialogue: 0,0:45:40.27,0:45:42.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 谢谢你 - 要啤酒还是水
Dialogue: 0,0:45:42.90,0:45:45.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水就可以了 谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:45:48.32,0:45:50.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 伊娃 乖 别叫了
Dialogue: 0,0:45:52.79,0:45:54.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着 我有点怕狗
Dialogue: 0,0:45:54.91,0:45:56.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊娃不会咬人的 进来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:45:56.87,0:46:00.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我相信你 但我还是蛮害怕的
Dialogue: 0,0:46:00.46,0:46:02.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 我把它带走 没问题的
Dialogue: 0,0:46:02.84,0:46:04.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们走 好样的
Dialogue: 0,0:46:04.76,0:46:06.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别叫了 伊娃
Dialogue: 0,0:46:06.13,0:46:07.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊娃 嘘 安静
Dialogue: 0,0:46:07.89,0:46:10.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安静 别叫了 伊娃 嘘
Dialogue: 0,0:46:11.51,0:46:13.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊娃 嘘 嘘
Dialogue: 0,0:46:13.47,0:46:15.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊娃 安静下来 安静
Dialogue: 0,0:46:21.40,0:46:22.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别叫了
Dialogue: 0,0:46:39.54,0:46:42.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我儿子的毕业照
Dialogue: 0,0:46:43.88,0:46:45.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我父亲一直很喜欢那张照片
Dialogue: 0,0:46:46.05,0:46:48.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我去...拿水给你 - 好的
Dialogue: 0,0:46:48.55,0:46:50.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这张照片什么时候拍的  你父亲看起来很年轻
Dialogue: 0,0:46:51.05,0:46:53.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是 额 1997拍的
Dialogue: 0,0:46:54.52,0:46:57.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 哦 - 对啊 老当益壮 不是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:46:59.81,0:47:04.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他一直说他是库兰德家族基因最好的
Dialogue: 0,0:47:05.49,0:47:06.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你
Dialogue: 0,0:47:13.99,0:47:16.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 你比伊娃还渴
Dialogue: 0,0:47:17.58,0:47:19.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 还要吗 - 好的 谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:47:19.58,0:47:21.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后就不会再麻烦你了
Dialogue: 0,0:47:21.58,0:47:23.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不会的 完全不麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:47:24.84,0:47:26.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要待多久都可以
Dialogue: 0,0:47:27.47,0:47:31.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自从...我父亲去世了 一个人住在这里很孤单
Dialogue: 0,0:47:33.43,0:47:35.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗 我就一直在附近巡逻
Dialogue: 0,0:47:36.27,0:47:41.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了听听广播 偶尔被调派 没别的事了
Dialogue: 0,0:47:42.40,0:47:45.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回家时有人能跟我说说话真好
Dialogue: 0,0:47:45.94,0:47:48.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊娃很棒 但她毕竟不能跟我聊天
Dialogue: 0,0:47:48.57,0:47:50.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你要的水 - 你没结婚?
Dialogue: 0,0:47:51.07,0:47:54.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不是的 请坐 我结过婚...两次
Dialogue: 0,0:47:54.99,0:47:57.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一个老婆 带走了我的房子
Dialogue: 0,0:47:58.29,0:48:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第二个老婆 在采石场收购
Dialogue: 0,0:48:00.12,0:48:01.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这套房子之前离开了
Dialogue: 0,0:48:03.17,0:48:06.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是...哇 七年前的事了
Dialogue: 0,0:48:07.17,0:48:08.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不介意再找一个
Dialogue: 0,0:48:09.30,0:48:12.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但布鲁诺不是最适合单身的人的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:48:13.47,0:48:16.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我 也不是黄金单身汉
Dialogue: 0,0:48:18.89,0:48:23.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你爸爸跟你谈起过德国吗
Dialogue: 0,0:48:24.48,0:48:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在开玩笑吗
Dialogue: 0,0:48:26.27,0:48:27.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他从来没停止过讨论德国
Dialogue: 0,0:48:29.40,0:48:31.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他有没有跟你说过关于二战的事?
Dialogue: 0,0:48:31.90,0:48:32.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然
Dialogue: 0,0:48:33.57,0:48:35.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道他是个收集狂吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:48:35.66,0:48:36.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊
Dialogue: 0,0:48:38.54,0:48:41.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有一堆他的东西 你想看看吗
Dialogue: 0,0:48:42.16,0:48:43.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:48:44.00,0:48:45.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心台阶 就在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:48:54.34,0:48:56.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊娃 安静 伊娃 嘘
Dialogue: 0,0:48:56.64,0:49:00.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 听着 额 这里有点乱
Dialogue: 0,0:49:00.35,0:49:02.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得把箱子挪开 然后
Dialogue: 0,0:49:02.60,0:49:05.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我带你去另一个房间
Dialogue: 0,0:49:10.19,0:49:11.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边
Dialogue: 0,0:49:12.32,0:49:14.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从这里 好的 来吧 哦
Dialogue: 0,0:49:16.70,0:49:17.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:49:24.21,0:49:27.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是 额 那是我爸爸的骄傲和快乐
Dialogue: 0,0:49:29.30,0:49:36.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个卖给我们的人发誓1938年11月19日这面旗帜在柏林飞舞
Dialogue: 0,0:49:37.18,0:49:38.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水晶之夜
Dialogue: 0,0:49:39.56,0:49:41.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊 水晶之夜
Dialogue: 0,0:49:43.56,0:49:46.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父亲曾经说 这面旗帜
Dialogue: 0,0:49:47.19,0:49:50.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见证了历史的开端
Dialogue: 0,0:49:52.23,0:49:53.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:49:59.08,0:50:01.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 箱子里有什么? - 额 就是
Dialogue: 0,0:50:02.58,0:50:05.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一些父亲得到的其他奖赏 你知道
Dialogue: 0,0:50:05.75,0:50:08.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经卖掉了大部分的收藏
Dialogue: 0,0:50:08.21,0:50:13.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 这些是跟他有感情的
Dialogue: 0,0:50:15.59,0:50:19.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连我也还没办法卖了它们 你知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:50:23.64,0:50:25.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想到处看看吗
Dialogue: 0,0:50:25.48,0:50:27.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 感谢 - 没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:50:42.62,0:50:44.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 这是初刊本
Dialogue: 0,0:50:45.12,0:50:48.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有个人想用6000美元跟我买 但我就是没办法...卖掉它
Dialogue: 0,0:50:51.13,0:50:53.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猜我跟我父亲一样感情用事 对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:50:56.76,0:51:00.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以随便在周围看看...任何东西都可以
Dialogue: 0,0:51:00.80,0:51:02.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去帮伊娃准备它的晚餐
Dialogue: 0,0:51:22.49,0:51:23.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安静 嘘
Dialogue: 0,0:51:39.51,0:51:40.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无价之宝 对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:51:43.26,0:51:44.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊
Dialogue: 0,0:51:45.43,0:51:48.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我不应该把它像那样塞在箱子里面
Dialogue: 0,0:52:04.20,0:52:05.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想要再喝点什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:52:06.12,0:52:07.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 那会很好
Dialogue: 0,0:52:08.70,0:52:11.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再来一杯水 还是烈一点的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:52:12.50,0:52:14.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烈一点的好了
Dialogue: 0,0:52:15.38,0:52:16.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:52:17.38,0:52:19.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在你知道我在说什么了
Dialogue: 0,0:52:19.72,0:52:20.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:52:25.81,0:52:27.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敬我父亲
Dialogue: 0,0:52:33.44,0:52:34.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗 我爸他...
Dialogue: 0,0:52:36.23,0:52:37.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爸那天晚上在那
Dialogue: 0,0:52:38.23,0:52:40.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 哪个晚上 - 额 水晶...
Dialogue: 0,0:52:40.90,0:52:42.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 水晶之夜 - 对 水晶之夜
Dialogue: 0,0:52:43.49,0:52:45.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 他说他带了一个铁锤
Dialogue: 0,0:52:46.16,0:52:48.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他打碎了一些珠宝店的窗户
Dialogue: 0,0:52:48.45,0:52:50.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 他跟你说过这件事吗 - 没有
Dialogue: 0,0:52:50.50,0:52:51.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有?
Dialogue: 0,0:52:52.37,0:52:54.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真希望你在他还活着的时候来这里
Dialogue: 0,0:52:54.63,0:52:58.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道 每过一段时间 有一些他的朋友会过来
Dialogue: 0,0:52:58.17,0:53:01.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们就会坐在这里 说一些故事 喝喝酒 你知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:53:02.59,0:53:05.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他很喜欢讲一些以前的事
Dialogue: 0,0:53:07.22,0:53:08.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还好吗 你流了很多汗
Dialogue: 0,0:53:09.56,0:53:12.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 哦 我有点热 - 把你的外套脱了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:53:12.48,0:53:13.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:53:14.40,0:53:17.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 把你的外套脱了 然后 我只是想要告诉你
Dialogue: 0,0:53:17.77,0:53:19.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我求之不得你能... - 哦
Dialogue: 0,0:53:19.61,0:53:22.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,...在这里住一晚 如果你不介意睡在我父亲的旧床上
Dialogue: 0,0:53:22.82,0:53:24.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你人真好 不必了 谢谢你 - 不 不
Dialogue: 0,0:53:24.95,0:53:27.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 好吧 反正我的提议随时有效 - 哦 谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:53:28.28,0:53:30.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父亲的朋友就是我的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:53:31.62,0:53:35.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么认识他的 你曾经跟他一起服役?
Dialogue: 0,0:53:35.92,0:53:38.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 不是 - 好吧 那你怎么认识他的
Dialogue: 0,0:53:40.84,0:53:43.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在奥斯维辛认识他的
Dialogue: 0,0:53:49.68,0:53:50.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奥斯维辛?
Dialogue: 0,0:53:51.77,0:53:53.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我父亲很希望他能在奥斯维辛服役
Dialogue: 0,0:53:54.39,0:53:56.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是说你父亲没去过奥斯维辛?
Dialogue: 0,0:53:57.90,0:53:58.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么...
Dialogue: 0,0:53:58.98,0:54:01.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是认真的吗 我父亲是军队的厨师
Dialogue: 0,0:54:06.24,0:54:08.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不是集中营领袖? He was not a Blockfuhrer?
Dialogue: 0,0:54:08.82,0:54:13.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都不知道那是什么 不是 我父亲在战争开始的时候才10岁
Dialogue: 0,0:54:14.00,0:54:16.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德国人让他做的最多的事就是 你知道
Dialogue: 0,0:54:16.50,0:54:19.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打破一些窗户 煮一些维也纳炸牛排 你知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:54:19.38,0:54:22.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很抱歉打扰你了
Dialogue: 0,0:54:22.71,0:54:27.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我找错人了 - 不 没事的 哇 哇塞
Dialogue: 0,0:54:27.51,0:54:30.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下 你以前在奥斯维辛?
Dialogue: 0,0:54:31.01,0:54:33.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 嗯 - 没有一个我爸的朋友在那里服役
Dialogue: 0,0:54:33.60,0:54:35.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我必须离开了 我已经打扰你很久了
Dialogue: 0,0:54:35.68,0:54:37.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打扰我? 不 没有 请留下来
Dialogue: 0,0:54:37.69,0:54:40.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请留下来 分享一些故事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:54:40.73,0:54:42.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再去拿一瓶酒 我们就...
Dialogue: 0,0:54:50.03,0:54:51.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:54:57.00,0:54:58.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:54:59.54,0:55:00.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个他妈的是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:55:01.71,0:55:04.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,额...对不起 我...
Dialogue: 0,0:55:05.51,0:55:06.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我 额...
Dialogue: 0,0:55:08.68,0:55:09.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个他妈的是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:55:14.68,0:55:15.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是犹太人?
Dialogue: 0,0:55:18.64,0:55:19.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:55:21.40,0:55:22.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是一个犹太人?
Dialogue: 0,0:55:25.82,0:55:27.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在他妈是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:55:28.36,0:55:29.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 我...
Dialogue: 0,0:55:30.41,0:55:32.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干你娘 给我坐下
Dialogue: 0,0:55:34.54,0:55:36.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你 让我走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:55:39.58,0:55:41.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你他妈在我家干吗
Dialogue: 0,0:55:41.67,0:55:44.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我搞错了 你父亲不是我要找的人
Dialogue: 0,0:55:45.05,0:55:46.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我父亲?
Dialogue: 0,0:55:49.59,0:55:51.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说你是我父亲的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:55:53.43,0:55:54.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你骗我
Dialogue: 0,0:55:54.76,0:55:59.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我没有说谎 我没有说谎 - 干你娘鸡掰
Dialogue: 0,0:56:02.44,0:56:05.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说你是我父亲的朋友 你到我家里
Dialogue: 0,0:56:06.53,0:56:08.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还他妈的喝我的威士忌
Dialogue: 0,0:56:08.74,0:56:11.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你他妈是一个肮脏的犹太人
Dialogue: 0,0:56:11.78,0:56:13.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊娃 闭上你的狗嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:56:14.03,0:56:16.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别吼了 求你了 别再吼了 我走
Dialogue: 0,0:56:16.58,0:56:17.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你给我坐下
Dialogue: 0,0:56:18.08,0:56:20.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你他妈现在立刻回答我的问题
Dialogue: 0,0:56:25.59,0:56:28.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,操你妈的 你刚刚是尿在了我的沙发上吗
Dialogue: 0,0:56:29.01,0:56:32.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 对不起 我很抱歉 - 操你妈
Dialogue: 0,0:56:32.47,0:56:33.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别再叫了
Dialogue: 0,0:56:33.80,0:56:35.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊娃 你他妈闭嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:56:35.68,0:56:38.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是在命令我吗 犹太人
Dialogue: 0,0:56:38.14,0:56:40.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊娃 我让你闭嘴 你知道...
Dialogue: 0,0:56:41.56,0:56:46.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道如果我父亲知道他妈有一个犹太人在他家他会说什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:56:46.61,0:56:49.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他会说 "希特勒他妈的万岁"
Dialogue: 0,0:56:49.69,0:56:50.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 那就是他会说的
Dialogue: 0,0:56:50.74,0:56:54.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希特勒他妈的万岁! 希特勒万岁! 希特勒万岁!
Dialogue: 0,0:56:54.82,0:56:56.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希特勒万岁! 希特勒万岁 你他妈的犹太人!
Dialogue: 0,0:56:57.08,0:56:58.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊娃 该死的 给我安静
Dialogue: 0,0:56:59.04,0:57:00.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴 你有什么问题啊
Dialogue: 0,0:57:01.75,0:57:03.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈? 闭嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:57:04.42,0:57:06.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停下 伊娃 安静
Dialogue: 0,0:57:06.67,0:57:07.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊娃
Dialogue: 0,0:57:07.88,0:57:10.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死 闭嘴 闭嘴 操你妈 安静
Dialogue: 0,0:57:11.76,0:57:12.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊娃 冷静下来
Dialogue: 0,0:57:17.18,0:57:19.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你他妈想要去见见活生生的犹太人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:57:19.18,0:57:20.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈 是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:57:20.64,0:57:21.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈 去抓他吧
Dialogue: 0,0:57:23.89,0:57:24.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊!
Dialogue: 0,0:57:26.86,0:57:28.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我操你...
Dialogue: 0,0:57:32.78,0:57:34.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这该死的犹太人
Dialogue: 0,0:57:34.53,0:57:35.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我操...
Dialogue: 0,0:58:28.50,0:58:29.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦...
Dialogue: 0,0:59:05.66,0:59:07.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是约翰·库兰德
Dialogue: 0,0:59:07.29,0:59:10.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请留言吧 如果有急事 打我的手机
Dialogue: 0,0:59:10.67,0:59:11.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,露丝?
Dialogue: 0,0:59:11.75,0:59:14.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约翰 你在哪 你已经晚了半个小时了
Dialogue: 0,0:59:14.13,0:59:15.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能整个早上都帮你掩护
Dialogue: 0,0:59:15.92,0:59:18.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我发誓 你最好是出车祸了... - 你在说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:59:51.00,0:59:52.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的天啊
Dialogue: 0,1:00:05.72,1:00:07.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦...
Dialogue: 0,1:00:44.72,1:00:45.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好
Dialogue: 0,1:00:46.05,1:00:50.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 马克思 我是泽夫 - 你去哪了
Dialogue: 0,1:00:51.89,1:00:54.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我杀了一个人
Dialogue: 0,1:00:56.23,1:00:57.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,额...
Dialogue: 0,1:00:58.69,1:01:04.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在是最难的部分了 你必须报警
Dialogue: 0,1:01:05.66,1:01:06.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你必须... - 不 不是的
Dialogue: 0,1:01:06.74,1:01:09.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不是我们要找的人
Dialogue: 0,1:01:13.29,1:01:16.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 那是谁 - 一个年轻很多的男人
Dialogue: 0,1:01:16.25,1:01:19.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我 额... 在一个箱子上看到了他的名字
Dialogue: 0,1:01:19.92,1:01:21.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他叫做约翰·库兰德
Dialogue: 0,1:01:23.05,1:01:24.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是一个纳粹
Dialogue: 0,1:01:27.26,1:01:31.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你怎么知道的 - 有很多纳粹的东西
Dialogue: 0,1:01:31.14,1:01:33.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 在房间里 有很多东西 - 哦
Dialogue: 0,1:01:35.35,1:01:38.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是我们的初衷
Dialogue: 0,1:01:40.28,1:01:41.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泽夫
Dialogue: 0,1:01:42.36,1:01:44.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还想继续吗
Dialogue: 0,1:01:45.32,1:01:48.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想 我必须完成
Dialogue: 0,1:01:49.12,1:01:50.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我必须
Dialogue: 0,1:01:51.33,1:01:54.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟 那是杀了我们全家的人
Dialogue: 0,1:03:15.08,1:03:16.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,露丝?
Dialogue: 0,1:03:19.04,1:03:20.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,露丝?
Dialogue: 0,1:03:21.38,1:03:24.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,露丝!
Dialogue: 0,1:03:43.02,1:03:44.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,1:03:45.48,1:03:46.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是
Dialogue: 0,1:03:50.95,1:03:53.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 我的天啊 谢谢你 太感谢你了
Dialogue: 0,1:03:57.58,1:03:58.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他还好吗
Dialogue: 0,1:04:00.08,1:04:02.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 他有痴呆
Dialogue: 0,1:04:04.42,1:04:05.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 额
Dialogue: 0,1:04:06.09,1:04:08.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是从哪里打来的? 我马上过去
Dialogue: 0,1:04:11.30,1:04:12.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里诺纪念医院?
Dialogue: 0,1:04:13.43,1:04:15.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 里诺 内华达州? - 里诺?
Dialogue: 0,1:04:16.43,1:04:18.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以跟我父亲讲话吗
Dialogue: 0,1:04:22.60,1:04:24.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 谢谢 非常感谢你
Dialogue: 0,1:04:24.44,1:04:28.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伙计们 我要打喷嚏了
Dialogue: 0,1:04:41.04,1:04:42.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,1:04:43.33,1:04:44.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 你好啊 查尔斯
Dialogue: 0,1:04:45.92,1:04:49.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 哦 我很好 别担心
Dialogue: 0,1:04:49.55,1:04:50.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,1:04:51.09,1:04:54.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫医生别去打扰你
Dialogue: 0,1:04:54.34,1:04:55.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈
Dialogue: 0,1:04:56.10,1:04:58.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请你别担心我了
Dialogue: 0,1:04:59.27,1:05:02.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 不 不用的 你别来医院
Dialogue: 0,1:05:02.31,1:05:04.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你母亲会来接我的
Dialogue: 0,1:05:06.06,1:05:08.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟她一起来?
Dialogue: 0,1:05:09.65,1:05:14.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊 我很好 没事的 嗯 好的 再见
Dialogue: 0,1:05:23.96,1:05:25.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你喜欢卡通?
Dialogue: 0,1:05:25.50,1:05:27.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢迪士尼频道的
Dialogue: 0,1:05:27.67,1:05:31.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 米老鼠吗 - 不是 我喜欢飞哥与小佛
Dialogue: 0,1:05:31.26,1:05:32.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦
Dialogue: 0,1:05:32.67,1:05:34.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没听说过他们
Dialogue: 0,1:05:35.01,1:05:36.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莫利 我马上回来
Dialogue: 0,1:05:38.14,1:05:39.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你快做你的功课吧
Dialogue: 0,1:05:42.43,1:05:46.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你叫莫利? - 莫利·伊丽莎白
Dialogue: 0,1:05:46.52,1:05:50.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你喜欢糖果吗 莫利·伊丽莎白
Dialogue: 0,1:05:51.36,1:05:52.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 额
Dialogue: 0,1:05:53.36,1:05:57.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我的大衣口袋里有一些硬糖
Dialogue: 0,1:05:59.24,1:06:02.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直为我的孙子们准备一些在那里
Dialogue: 0,1:06:03.04,1:06:04.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊
Dialogue: 0,1:06:05.54,1:06:07.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我找不到
Dialogue: 0,1:06:07.21,1:06:12.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 我妻子来的时候会带一些的
Dialogue: 0,1:06:19.22,1:06:21.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你是泽夫吗 - 是的
Dialogue: 0,1:06:22.39,1:06:24.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能看你的信吗
Dialogue: 0,1:06:24.39,1:06:25.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以啊
Dialogue: 0,1:06:29.11,1:06:31.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 哇 你真有钱 - 什么?
Dialogue: 0,1:06:42.58,1:06:44.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁是马克思
Dialogue: 0,1:06:45.08,1:06:46.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马克思?
Dialogue: 0,1:06:47.33,1:06:48.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不清楚
Dialogue: 0,1:06:52.46,1:06:57.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 要不然你把信读给我听吧
Dialogue: 0,1:06:58.51,1:07:04.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"泽夫 有些事令人难以接受 可你得知道"
Dialogue: 0,1:07:05.31,1:07:10.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"首先 露丝已经过世了"
Dialogue: 0,1:07:10.65,1:07:12.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"她得了癌症"
Dialogue: 0,1:07:13.36,1:07:18.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"她爱你 在她最后的时刻 你陪在她身边 握着她的手"
Dialogue: 0,1:07:20.03,1:07:24.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"其次 你患有痴呆症"
Dialogue: 0,1:07:25.29,1:07:28.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"最近你变得健忘了"
Dialogue: 0,1:07:30.04,1:07:33.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那很正常 老年人总是爱忘事
Dialogue: 0,1:07:33.46,1:07:34.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 是啊
Dialogue: 0,1:07:35.63,1:07:39.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"我们有着相似的经历"
Dialogue: 0,1:07:39.68,1:07:43.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"我们都是奥斯维辛..."
Dialogue: 0,1:07:43.39,1:07:46.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 奥斯维辛 奥斯维辛 - "奥斯维辛的幸存者"
Dialogue: 0,1:07:47.39,1:07:53.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"看看你的左臂 你是98814号囚犯"
Dialogue: 0,1:08:00.53,1:08:03.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"战争结束时"
Dialogue: 0,1:08:03.32,1:08:06.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"我承诺自己"
Dialogue: 0,1:08:07.37,1:08:12.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"我要找到那些应为此负责的人"
Dialogue: 0,1:08:12.83,1:08:17.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"与西蒙·威森塔尔共事期间"
Dialogue: 0,1:08:17.42,1:08:22.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"我帮忙抓获了大批前'纳兹'分子"
Dialogue: 0,1:08:22.72,1:08:25.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"他们遍布世界各地"
Dialogue: 0,1:08:25.22,1:08:28.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- '纳兹'是什么       - 是纳粹 纳粹
Dialogue: 0,1:08:31.10,1:08:32.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一种坏人
Dialogue: 0,1:08:36.44,1:08:39.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,六个月前 上帝赐我好运
Dialogue: 0,1:08:39.86,1:08:44.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当你搬到高级社区后
Dialogue: 0,1:08:44.87,1:08:48.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我立刻就认出了那个曾在奥斯维辛的你
Dialogue: 0,1:08:49.45,1:08:52.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽管你已经不记得我
Dialogue: 0,1:08:54.21,1:08:59.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是那个狱区还健在的最后的幸存者
Dialogue: 0,1:08:59.55,1:09:03.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除我之外 你是唯一一个
Dialogue: 0,1:09:03.55,1:09:08.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还能认出杀害我们家人的凶手面孔的人
Dialogue: 0,1:09:10.52,1:09:13.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西蒙·威森塔尔坚持认为
Dialogue: 0,1:09:13.39,1:09:17.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有战犯都应当受到公开审判
Dialogue: 0,1:09:18.78,1:09:23.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 我们不能给瓦利施这个机会
Dialogue: 0,1:09:24.74,1:09:27.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽管证据确凿
Dialogue: 0,1:09:27.91,1:09:31.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他 跟我们一样 很可能会
Dialogue: 0,1:09:31.54,1:09:34.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在被引渡德国之前已经去世
Dialogue: 0,1:09:36.17,1:09:41.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都赞同 奥托·瓦利施必须死
Dialogue: 0,1:09:43.22,1:09:46.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你必须杀了他
Dialogue: 0,1:09:46.64,1:09:51.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"你答应等露丝去世你就去"
Dialogue: 0,1:09:51.77,1:09:55.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"你答应了我 你也答应了露丝"
Dialogue: 0,1:09:59.77,1:10:01.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你读得很棒
Dialogue: 0,1:10:03.36,1:10:04.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,1:10:06.45,1:10:07.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,露丝是谁
Dialogue: 0,1:10:08.53,1:10:09.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的妻子
Dialogue: 0,1:10:10.33,1:10:12.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为她能带点糖果给我
Dialogue: 0,1:10:13.66,1:10:15.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也希望来着
Dialogue: 0,1:10:22.26,1:10:25.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 我要去假日旅馆
Dialogue: 0,1:10:26.30,1:10:28.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔霍湖大道3961号
Dialogue: 0,1:10:29.80,1:10:30.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 在湖南岸 - 对
Dialogue: 0,1:10:30.93,1:10:32.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那得一个多小时
Dialogue: 0,1:10:32.93,1:10:37.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 哦 那... 我带够钱了 - 上车吧
Dialogue: 0,1:10:57.54,1:11:00.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你好 泽夫? - 是的
Dialogue: 0,1:11:01.59,1:11:03.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感谢上帝
Dialogue: 0,1:11:04.84,1:11:06.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在哪
Dialogue: 0,1:11:08.84,1:11:09.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泽夫?
Dialogue: 0,1:11:10.85,1:11:11.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔霍
Dialogue: 0,1:11:12.85,1:11:16.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你明白你该怎么做
Dialogue: 0,1:11:18.35,1:11:19.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只剩一个人了
Dialogue: 0,1:11:21.27,1:11:23.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 我明白
Dialogue: 0,1:11:26.36,1:11:27.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我该怎么做
Dialogue: 0,1:11:36.00,1:11:36.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 早 - 早上好
Dialogue: 0,1:11:37.04,1:11:38.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想退房
Dialogue: 0,1:11:40.50,1:11:41.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,1:11:42.71,1:11:45.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你的手受伤了? - 哦 对 是的
Dialogue: 0,1:11:45.42,1:11:47.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 它...还好了 还能动 - 不错
Dialogue: 0,1:11:48.76,1:11:51.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 总共106美元20美分
Dialogue: 0,1:11:52.89,1:11:56.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想搭出租的钱是够了
Dialogue: 0,1:11:58.60,1:12:01.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 呃 我们也能用信用卡的
Dialogue: 0,1:12:02.02,1:12:03.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,1:12:04.57,1:12:05.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,1:12:07.07,1:12:10.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔霍? 他在塔霍搞什么鬼
Dialogue: 0,1:12:11.45,1:12:13.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我正在租车
Dialogue: 0,1:12:13.72,1:12:15.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我会开车过去
Dialogue: 0,1:12:15.87,1:12:16.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,1:12:16.91,1:12:18.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 听着 你能试着找到
Dialogue: 0,1:12:18.51,1:12:20.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他搭的那辆出租所属公司的名字吗
Dialogue: 0,1:12:22.00,1:12:23.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,1:13:14.84,1:13:16.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,需要帮忙吗
Dialogue: 0,1:13:17.47,1:13:20.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鲁迪·库兰德 他在这住吗
Dialogue: 0,1:13:20.81,1:13:23.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 是的 - 我能跟他聊聊吗
Dialogue: 0,1:13:24.15,1:13:26.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 他还在睡觉 - 哦
Dialogue: 0,1:13:26.69,1:13:30.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 我能在这等他...醒来吗
Dialogue: 0,1:13:31.99,1:13:33.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是要紧事
Dialogue: 0,1:13:34.53,1:13:35.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事啊
Dialogue: 0,1:13:35.78,1:13:37.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 是私事
Dialogue: 0,1:13:37.99,1:13:39.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且他认得我 他认得我
Dialogue: 0,1:13:39.49,1:13:41.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很久以前就认识他了
Dialogue: 0,1:13:43.75,1:13:46.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 进来吧 - 哦 谢谢你 谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,1:13:49.13,1:13:52.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 需要来杯咖啡吗 您叫... - 古特曼
Dialogue: 0,1:13:53.47,1:13:55.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行 咖啡挺好 谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,1:13:55.64,1:13:59.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 呃 黑咖啡就好 - 在客厅坐会儿
Dialogue: 0,1:13:59.56,1:14:00.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去煮咖啡
Dialogue: 0,1:14:15.20,1:14:17.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我们家几年前重聚的时候照的
Dialogue: 0,1:14:18.87,1:14:20.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢
Dialogue: 0,1:14:20.45,1:14:22.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个大家庭
Dialogue: 0,1:14:22.91,1:14:25.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我父亲总爱说他生了一支足球队
Dialogue: 0,1:14:25.54,1:14:26.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是老小
Dialogue: 0,1:14:27.88,1:14:29.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你母亲有多大
Dialogue: 0,1:14:29.71,1:14:31.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她年轻多了 父亲是二婚
Dialogue: 0,1:14:33.80,1:14:36.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 谢谢你 - 古特曼先生 我能问您个问题么
Dialogue: 0,1:14:38.05,1:14:40.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您的事跟奥斯维辛有关么
Dialogue: 0,1:14:42.10,1:14:43.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,1:14:44.64,1:14:46.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我父亲可不愿谈论那事
Dialogue: 0,1:14:46.94,1:14:48.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦
Dialogue: 0,1:14:49.56,1:14:51.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我理解
Dialogue: 0,1:14:53.48,1:14:55.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您愿意跟我们共进早餐吗 古特曼先生
Dialogue: 0,1:14:55.86,1:14:57.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做了些烤苹果饼
Dialogue: 0,1:14:57.24,1:14:59.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不太饿 真是感谢你
Dialogue: 0,1:15:00.16,1:15:02.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会打扰你太久的
Dialogue: 0,1:15:02.79,1:15:04.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确定? 这可是家传秘制
Dialogue: 0,1:15:04.95,1:15:08.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 是的 我确定 可还是谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,1:15:08.88,1:15:11.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您等我下 我去告诉父亲您来了
Dialogue: 0,1:15:12.09,1:15:13.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 好的
Dialogue: 0,1:15:34.61,1:15:35.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 你是谁
Dialogue: 0,1:15:36.28,1:15:38.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 我是泽夫
Dialogue: 0,1:15:38.61,1:15:39.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 嗨 泽夫 - 英格
Dialogue: 0,1:15:45.29,1:15:46.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是谁
Dialogue: 0,1:15:47.29,1:15:51.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是你外公的老朋友
Dialogue: 0,1:16:46.72,1:16:47.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你喜欢瓦格纳?
Dialogue: 0,1:16:50.85,1:16:54.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 我一直都喜爱瓦格纳
Dialogue: 0,1:16:55.90,1:17:00.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我女儿说来了个我认识的奥斯维辛人
Dialogue: 0,1:17:02.07,1:17:04.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但作为一个幸存者不应该喜欢瓦格纳的 不是吗 (瓦格纳 德国作曲家 种族主义者 反犹太主义者)
Dialogue: 0,1:17:04.82,1:17:07.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,音乐又不可恨
Dialogue: 0,1:17:10.71,1:17:14.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我 呃 没能在那些照片中认出你
Dialogue: 0,1:17:15.71,1:17:16.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是...
Dialogue: 0,1:17:22.97,1:17:23.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的声音...
Dialogue: 0,1:17:28.14,1:17:29.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没变
Dialogue: 0,1:17:34.40,1:17:37.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道有一天你会来找我
Dialogue: 0,1:17:39.11,1:17:40.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外公 泽夫是你朋友吗
Dialogue: 0,1:17:41.03,1:17:43.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,英格 请你回厨房去
Dialogue: 0,1:17:44.24,1:17:47.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得跟我朋友探讨些事
Dialogue: 0,1:17:50.12,1:17:52.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没忘记你
Dialogue: 0,1:17:53.41,1:17:56.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧...我们到外面去
Dialogue: 0,1:17:57.38,1:18:01.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想让我的家人听见...我们要说的事
Dialogue: 0,1:18:07.26,1:18:08.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经有很久...
Dialogue: 0,1:18:10.39,1:18:12.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人认出从前的我了
Dialogue: 0,1:18:15.14,1:18:17.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我甚至记不清有多久
Dialogue: 0,1:18:20.44,1:18:24.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些年来 人们盯着我看
Dialogue: 0,1:18:25.11,1:18:29.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就以为他们认出我了 其实他们从来没有
Dialogue: 0,1:18:32.12,1:18:36.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许他们只是太害怕 所以什么都不敢说
Dialogue: 0,1:18:39.96,1:18:45.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时候 我会到这来 说出自己的名字
Dialogue: 0,1:18:48.30,1:18:50.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我自言自语
Dialogue: 0,1:18:51.47,1:18:54.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重新回忆起以前的那个我
Dialogue: 0,1:18:57.35,1:19:01.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是唯一一种让我知道自己存在过的方式
Dialogue: 0,1:19:03.03,1:19:05.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我变成现在这个人之前的那个自我
Dialogue: 0,1:19:07.28,1:19:13.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 靠谎言过活算什么人生
Dialogue: 0,1:19:16.00,1:19:18.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直都知道你会找到我
Dialogue: 0,1:19:24.84,1:19:26.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经过了太久
Dialogue: 0,1:19:27.26,1:19:28.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我们都是老人了
Dialogue: 0,1:19:30.34,1:19:35.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把你的手拿开 奥托
Dialogue: 0,1:19:37.85,1:19:38.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,1:19:38.94,1:19:42.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 "把你的手拿开"
Dialogue: 0,1:19:43.94,1:19:47.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你叫我奥托?
Dialogue: 0,1:19:48.03,1:19:49.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想你弄糊涂了
Dialogue: 0,1:19:49.24,1:19:53.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有 你的名字叫奥托·瓦利施
Dialogue: 0,1:19:53.37,1:19:57.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是奥斯维辛的一个狱长 You were a Blockfuhrer at Auschwitz.
Dialogue: 0,1:19:57.50,1:20:01.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你杀了我的家人
Dialogue: 0,1:20:03.17,1:20:04.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你疯了吗
Dialogue: 0,1:20:07.01,1:20:08.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你自欺欺人这么久
Dialogue: 0,1:20:08.94,1:20:12.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你自己都信以为真了
Dialogue: 0,1:20:13.97,1:20:14.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...
Dialogue: 0,1:20:17.56,1:20:19.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不明白
Dialogue: 0,1:20:19.23,1:20:20.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我来帮你
Dialogue: 0,1:20:22.40,1:20:24.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弄明白
Dialogue: 0,1:20:34.28,1:20:36.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉像我们开了家旅馆
Dialogue: 0,1:20:37.95,1:20:40.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去告诉外公早饭好了
Dialogue: 0,1:20:43.88,1:20:45.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 是谁啊 - 我叫查尔斯·古特曼
Dialogue: 0,1:20:45.84,1:20:47.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我父亲在这
Dialogue: 0,1:20:48.09,1:20:50.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨 真抱歉打扰您
Dialogue: 0,1:20:50.59,1:20:54.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是我听说不久前有辆出租车载我爸爸到这
Dialogue: 0,1:20:54.93,1:20:56.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 他跟我父亲在外面
Dialogue: 0,1:20:58.43,1:20:59.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感谢上帝
Dialogue: 0,1:21:00.56,1:21:03.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他已经失踪一周了
Dialogue: 0,1:21:03.94,1:21:05.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失踪?
Dialogue: 0,1:21:06.32,1:21:09.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 难以置信 跟我来 - 谢谢
Dialogue: 0,1:21:22.25,1:21:24.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 爸? - 哦 上帝啊
Dialogue: 0,1:21:24.29,1:21:27.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 妈妈 - 请别紧张
Dialogue: 0,1:21:27.21,1:21:28.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别害怕
Dialogue: 0,1:21:28.55,1:21:32.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸 你为什么不 呃 把枪放低些
Dialogue: 0,1:21:33.63,1:21:35.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 查尔斯? - 啊
Dialogue: 0,1:21:36.14,1:21:38.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你在这干嘛 - 呃...
Dialogue: 0,1:21:39.14,1:21:40.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸 把枪放下
Dialogue: 0,1:21:41.31,1:21:44.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 把枪放下 爸 - 不 不
Dialogue: 0,1:21:45.15,1:21:47.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除非他说出真相
Dialogue: 0,1:21:50.28,1:21:51.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你要这样做
Dialogue: 0,1:21:52.36,1:21:54.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉她们你是谁
Dialogue: 0,1:21:54.36,1:21:57.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请你别发疯了
Dialogue: 0,1:21:57.16,1:21:59.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉她们你做了什么
Dialogue: 0,1:21:59.91,1:22:02.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 放过她们 拜托了 - 说英语
Dialogue: 0,1:22:02.50,1:22:03.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我求你了
Dialogue: 0,1:22:04.04,1:22:06.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要让她们听懂你说的
Dialogue: 0,1:22:06.67,1:22:08.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸 他在说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,1:22:08.92,1:22:11.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别听他的 他疯了
Dialogue: 0,1:22:12.67,1:22:13.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,1:22:16.64,1:22:18.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的选择很简单
Dialogue: 0,1:22:19.10,1:22:21.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以说出真相让她活下来
Dialogue: 0,1:22:21.39,1:22:24.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也可以撒谎 然后看着她倒下
Dialogue: 0,1:22:24.18,1:22:25.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你三秒钟
Dialogue: 0,1:22:25.27,1:22:26.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 一 - 拜托 别这样
Dialogue: 0,1:22:26.35,1:22:28.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 二 - 求你了 朝我开枪吧
Dialogue: 0,1:22:28.27,1:22:29.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 爸 停下 - 三
Dialogue: 0,1:22:29.36,1:22:30.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 好吧
Dialogue: 0,1:22:31.69,1:22:33.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧
Dialogue: 0,1:22:42.37,1:22:44.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在战争期间
Dialogue: 0,1:22:46.42,1:22:48.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是囚犯
Dialogue: 0,1:22:48.71,1:22:49.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大点声
Dialogue: 0,1:22:52.38,1:22:54.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 在战争期间我不是囚犯 - 再大点!
Dialogue: 0,1:22:56.05,1:22:58.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在战争期间我不是囚犯!
Dialogue: 0,1:23:09.06,1:23:10.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是个纳粹
Dialogue: 0,1:23:14.11,1:23:15.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是个党卫军
Dialogue: 0,1:23:16.99,1:23:19.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是奥斯维辛集中营的一个狱长 I was a Blockfuhrer at Auschwitz.
Dialogue: 0,1:23:20.74,1:23:22.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你杀过人吗
Dialogue: 0,1:23:23.58,1:23:24.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,1:23:25.45,1:23:30.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 爷爷 你杀过人? - 你杀了多少人
Dialogue: 0,1:23:31.29,1:23:32.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不清楚
Dialogue: 0,1:23:33.46,1:23:34.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很多人
Dialogue: 0,1:23:37.34,1:23:40.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在告诉她们你的真名
Dialogue: 0,1:23:47.64,1:23:49.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的名字叫...
Dialogue: 0,1:23:52.31,1:23:53.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,库尼伯特·斯德姆
Dialogue: 0,1:23:54.73,1:23:55.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对
Dialogue: 0,1:23:56.61,1:23:58.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的名字叫瓦利施!
Dialogue: 0,1:23:59.03,1:24:01.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 就是库尼伯特·斯德姆
Dialogue: 0,1:24:01.49,1:24:03.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你叫奥托·瓦利施!
Dialogue: 0,1:24:04.12,1:24:05.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,1:24:06.62,1:24:10.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你 你叫奥托·瓦利施
Dialogue: 0,1:24:14.13,1:24:16.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在撒谎
Dialogue: 0,1:24:17.26,1:24:18.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有
Dialogue: 0,1:24:21.09,1:24:24.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是70年来我第一次说真话
Dialogue: 0,1:24:26.18,1:24:28.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你才是奥托·瓦利施
Dialogue: 0,1:24:30.23,1:24:34.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是库尼伯特·斯德姆 我们都是奥斯维辛的狱长
Dialogue: 0,1:24:35.52,1:24:38.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不...
Dialogue: 0,1:24:38.15,1:24:39.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是个囚犯
Dialogue: 0,1:24:40.15,1:24:41.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看你的胳膊
Dialogue: 0,1:24:42.45,1:24:47.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是98814号 我是98813号
Dialogue: 0,1:24:49.12,1:24:54.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我们互相纹的 这是我们唯一的逃生办法
Dialogue: 0,1:25:10.73,1:25:11.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸?
Dialogue: 0,1:25:13.69,1:25:14.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是真的吗
Dialogue: 0,1:25:15.56,1:25:19.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 都是谎言 都是谎言
Dialogue: 0,1:25:19.74,1:25:21.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是真的
Dialogue: 0,1:25:21.78,1:25:23.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谎言?
Dialogue: 0,1:25:26.53,1:25:28.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么能忘记呢
Dialogue: 0,1:25:29.33,1:25:32.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你给自己取名叫泽夫 因为它是狼的意思
Dialogue: 0,1:25:34.17,1:25:36.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说我俩都是狼
Dialogue: 0,1:25:47.55,1:25:49.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 我的上帝
Dialogue: 0,1:26:03.15,1:26:04.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我记得
Dialogue: 0,1:26:08.37,1:26:09.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸?
Dialogue: 0,1:26:12.33,1:26:13.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸
Dialogue: 0,1:26:17.17,1:26:18.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在 我们还在等待
Dialogue: 0,1:26:18.50,1:26:20.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来自塔霍湖警察局的消息
Dialogue: 0,1:26:20.38,1:26:23.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们仍未向记者透露或发布官方声明
Dialogue: 0,1:26:23.67,1:26:24.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他们向我们保证
Dialogue: 0,1:26:24.74,1:26:27.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不出一小时我们将悉数获知
Dialogue: 0,1:26:27.93,1:26:31.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居民们 如你所想的那样 十分震惊
Dialogue: 0,1:26:31.64,1:26:35.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我同一些不愿在摄像机前发表言论的人谈了谈
Dialogue: 0,1:26:35.35,1:26:38.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其中一位告诉我...
Dialogue: 0,1:26:38.27,1:26:42.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 可怜的泽夫 - 悲剧 真正的悲剧
Dialogue: 0,1:26:42.73,1:26:45.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他一定不知道他在做什么
Dialogue: 0,1:26:49.49,1:26:52.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他很清楚他在做什么
Dialogue: 0,1:26:54.37,1:26:56.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么 你是什么意思 马克斯
Dialogue: 0,1:27:00.88,1:27:03.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他杀掉的那个人
Dialogue: 0,1:27:04.42,1:27:08.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫做库尼伯特·斯德姆
Dialogue: 0,1:27:11.81,1:27:13.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而泽夫的真名
Dialogue: 0,1:27:16.31,1:27:19.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫做奥托·瓦利施
Dialogue: 0,1:27:23.32,1:27:25.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是他们两个...
Dialogue: 0,1:27:27.24,1:27:30.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀害了我的家人
