Selamat MENONTON "Hong Kong: Skull Island" by the Guavaberry
LF We can use this incredible machine ...
Victory for peace
We are entering a period of human history, the greatest.
Satellite progress Hamu progress can not be equated
Our progress in the ballistic missiles with.
And expansion of this time, the scene ...
This is the first time we put the camera see the Earth in the sky.
We found places where we have never seen before.
The smartest tenant is a person or a machine monkeys.
We are in this new sea because knowledge in the tank.
We are looking for peace, or cause fear a new war.
Overcoming human cruelty, and make it in this world is safe.
We are committed to it.
The Committee of the Congress rally stalled citizens ...
The next few days in a certain density.
Mark my words. Currently in Washington has never been so bad.
Do not interfere.
This is not a good time to ask.
There will be shut down, Brooks. We're out of money!
After the end of this war, our adventure will not be approved.
We will not do with our presentation.
And in the form of a stack of paper. One day, I can compile it, membundelnya.
Today we agreed to end the war and bring peace to Vietnam.
The entire US troops will be withdrawn.
We do not have a day. Hello there.
- Miranda met with Senator Phil Willis. - Of course, Mr. relics.
L to leave a message in the morning to reschedule appointments.
In a few weeks spare time.
- Jesus. I do not accept the message, Randa? - You're happy.
mobile? Five?
They will be ignored. Only for a moment.
You have five minutes. L appointment late ...
This time to find what imaginary monster?
These photos are not mapped in the South Pacific region. Not found.
Many speak of civilization.
Skull Island.
There, the Lord did not finish the creation.
It is understood that many ships and aircraft disappeared there.
Bermuda Triangle?
Aluminum or paper hat liters weekend?
Compared to the triangular hat, but I think more than that.
Castle Bravo nuclear test in 1954?
It is not a trial. They are trying to kill something.
I'm sure there are ecosystems do not know.
Its place is on this island.
Myth and science meet.
Randa, this fairy tale.
Harry Truman did not expect that, when the financial monarchy in 1946.
This is a waste ...... monarch ranked at the top to search for extraterrestrial life.
Well, they're crazy.
We should put you off.
This is an opportunity for our country.
Senator Landsat send a delegation to the island.
We took action.
If you agree, of course.
You expect to find it?
Resources, cure cancer, geological discovery.
Perhaps the alternative fuels. senator...
...... I honestly do not know what happened there.
This is what we know:
Tomorrow night, Novosat Russia will melewati this area.
And three days, they will have the same image. Whether it is...
You want to find him.
correct?
I can not believe you said, it's almost ridiculous.
Best regards.
So you can menunpang.
Listen, this is the last time. very long.
You promise? Finally, help?
senator?
another.
We need military escort.
- Hey, Mills. - Yes?
How many can believe it?
- He told us how? - I do not know, three, four.
Your mother sucks.
- It was explained that the Cole. - Later, I ordered, when they met him.
I'm sure your mother sucks.
correct?
- Mr? - Chapman.
- There is something, sir? - number
OK
What are your plans when you return to the world, Chapman?
In the eastern routes ajob waiting.
The reason Billy moved to Atlanta ...
They are waiting for me. How about you?
All this for what?
So what?
Go, Chapman. have fun.
is everything okay?
great.
Colonel HP!
You have your phone.
- It's HP. - HP, this is the general ward.
You and your soldiers are ready to the surgery last?
I do not mind, sir.
Sidangmu process. I do not want to rest?
Here pass command, sir.
Do not get too excited.
A group of scientists is called the Landsat discovered new islands from their satellites.
They need helikpter research.
Understood.
Also, the master? - Yes?
Best regards.
Randa, I'm confused. You get a military escort.
Why do I need a tracker? SAS Why? !
Former SAS. It's ok.
He helped Danang 12 pilot crashed in '72.
But your sources, he spent some time at the bar expensive.
Your degree at Yale to lead us in the forest, Brooks?
My father said that when he held his drink the way to judge.
You know each other?
- OK. Although he needs to know? - What is agreed upon.
Who else worth talking to people.
Uncharted Island? I will tell you the following things that can kill you.
Rain, heat, mud, flies and mosquitoes,
You can use Atabrine malaria, how many other bacteria?
Let alone eat your animals.
- We double your winnings. - Do you know how dangerous this is.
I think five times.
Bonus if we survived.
Pay him. I think Mr. Conrad will get fair pay.
- There is a separate weight gain. - one question.
You are here looking for clues.
Who or what KuLacak?
The information we get. No card. Only satellite imagery.
We need people like you, their particular expertise in the jungle ...
Our land-based adventure.
We only scientists and researchers. We need experienced people.
Next thing you know there's a problem.
Now find something, TN. Conrad.
Jika must have found it ...... you home.
- Weaver. Hey, Jerry. Tell you? - This is Jerry.
- Landsat? You can. - is that true?
Anchored in Bangkok. Pier 14 tomorrow 18:00.
Tomorrow
Thank you. I owe you.
I do not understand. Why do you want to join the mapping
Task, they are covered at the scheduled time?
LF three sources who said the same thing, you know you're lying.
Here are some things. Keeping things confidential.
I can not believe he did. really?
Another day 7454300
a new day!
Now, we have to go to another island ...
Another forest.
Vietnam is not an island, stupid.
West Island, and then ...
I'd better go there.
- Drinking. - This is not an island, it is the key.
This is not funny, Cole.
- Mason Weaver, a photographer. - Mason Weaver's wife?
Final inspection liters.
what should I do?
Here two years. You anywhere?
Together with the MACV-SOG.
You've come to a dangerous place.
I respect that.
Because men like losing support in the United States.
You will not hold it against unarmed people have lost the war, right?
The camera is more dangerous than guns.
We did not lose the war ...... we left it.
correct.
welcome. Site supervisors of Landsat liters 维克多涅韦斯.
This is my partner, Steve Woodward, part of the data.
The expedition took us to the best place to avoid hundreds of years.
According storm surrounding the endlessly satellite islands ...
The island hide hidden from the outside world.
Helicopter Colonel Packard was the first on the island.
You'll join us for the first time up bodies ...
Accompanied by Mr. Miranda, Miss St. biologists, geologists, TN leadership. Brooks.
We focused on the surface of the island ...
Below.
- Mr. Brooks. - Easy.
We used dynamite to create mmetakan island vibration on the surface.
You are flying from the south, down explosives
Earthquake, understand the density of the soil.
He dropped the bomb?
Scientific equipment.
Did you hear that? Now, our scientists!
You're not a scientist.
We went down, led by Mr. Conrad land expedition made camp.
Mayor Jack Chapman.
Once the storm will reach the island ...... radio interference boat.
This means that we will be alone.
After three days, the team will meet here to complement our island.
Seemingly chance to return from an unknown time.
all...
Do not miss.
What are you doing here?
what are you doing?
Why wear an explosive geological mapping mission?
You're listening to class.
- Explosion geology earthquake. - Do you believe?
I'm not saying.
Have you seen Colonel Packard?
- Yes. - They are very nervous.
War hero. where are we.
What about you?
This portrait photographers mapping mission.
Correct image to form an opinion.
And conquered the Pulitzer Prize. - Well, Colonel Conrad.
How about you? Why British special forces involved in?
Call Conrad. Microliters relieved.
They gave me the money.
I do not like mercenaries.
You do not like a war photographer.
Anti-war photographer.
You write chapter?
For my son.
Billy expensive. Tata promises a home for her birthday, but my father was lying.
I'm a bad father.
I hope this letter amend father.
Storm looks worse people.
We should postpone this task.
- This is how the island? - 50 miles maybe more.
- US lebh close. - You're floating. You get out of here.
- I can break, Colonel? - This is our chance.
Through this hole. It is a low-pressure air.
I appreciate your enthusiasm, but as an institution
Randa controller canceled the task.
AWIS decision. Landsat tour is undoubtedly inspire courage.
I hope you are inspired by my fears.
This is the only map study.
Until the last pristine areas on Earth. You are not because of the rain?
Stay on board, if you like.
Here many years before it can be like this.
You can overcome bad weather, Colonel.
HP decided to let the colonel.
I can not ride a helicopter.
- Helicopter participation. Do you know why? - Why?
Do they care?
As a precaution, Brooks.
We do?
There is nothing he can not face.
- He is in charge. - He missed the bed? L miss my bed.
Do you miss your bed?
It has a bed, Cole?
It has a bed, right?
See you at the meeting.
Yes, sir.
-Aki? A.
- Generator? A.
- Machine? - I checked three times.
Leaders in Fox Fox Group. Time Griffin and ants.
As always, do not forget ...... grip!
Maintenance of vision.
Fox five let you know when it closer.
Location Fox Lima.
been accepted.
The Fox Group with me. living together!
let's start!
Maintenance direction.
We have already done so.
Benny expensive.
Seen a hurricane decision ...
Maybe fly?
This is what happens.
Sebaikanya grip.
The Fox Group is the group leader. Change to inertial navigation.
Remember lcarus story ...
His father gave wax wings ...
He warned not to fly close to the sun.
Akselarasinya drag ... so then flew more ...
Although his wings melted from the sun ...
And fell into the sea.
The US military is not responsible.
So they gave the material that we have made ...
Baja Pennsylvania.
melt.
Come flying low.
Leader Fox Group. Split, check your area.
Fox Seven, lower Landsat team.
So, head of Lima. Fox three to six fields.
Let us there.
Other people keep up with the squad leader.
To bring the device to three hours. Come on, act now!
Prepare earthquake explosives.
Understood.
Fox II scapegoat.
It is understood that Fox three. According to 0-9-0.
You see what I see?
Earthquake response is excellent.
You will not believe it.
Good luck!.
Beware!
Shenhu Lima! Eight fall! Four autumn!
LN response, Fox three!
- This is a monkey? - what is this?
There are also some yes.
Three Fox Fox Group. The aim low.
Prepare weapons.
Leaders in Fox Fox Group. Oh shit!
- what is this? - Entahlahlah!
- Get out of here! - I am your master!
- Take us out of here! - Fox nine trap!
Minimum check.
We will fall.
Fox five, LT Leader Fox, Fox nine traps ... 1 kilomoeter north of the river.
- Send Rescue. - Good.
We drift.
From the door!
Help
"Fuck ! ! ! "
kill him.
Oh shit! I know.
We die, you idiot.
- deal with! - Beware!
adhere to!
- Fox trap! - I'll take!
- We look at it! - Tell Colonel Packard our way!
Survival, Briggs. L come.
Countryside. L repeat.
We will fall!
Listen, I want you to tell me now.
- Do you love your mother? - Yes!
- how much is it? - I'm like my mother!
Contact each unit! It aired?
L repeat, do not launch?
All will understand.
We in the south of the island.
A river a few kilometers away.
We follow the flow of water to the North Coast where prostitutes.
What are you waiting for? All helicopter crash.
We must find a way to send a signal to the board, they will send search
We just need to choose the right path.
He should sit alone at the table.
Wait a minute, we are not talking about it?
Our best people spread over 8 kilometers.
We must go to the north and join the others.
- Are you ok? - I can not claim to answer this question.
- I do not know. - who are you?
- I hope it was worth it. - I do not want to talk about it?
l is not normal, this will not happen.
Fox Fox Group in charge!
- They heard a low frequency response. change. - Fox.
- Chapman. - I Chapman.
- Inform the latest coordinates. - On the west side.
- Alpha peak coordinates, 3,0,0 change.
Well, Chapman.
In the highest mountain in the west. change.
mongkonfirmasi our Sea Stallion.
Chapman, preserve jobs.
We pick you up, but do not have enough ammunition
The Sea Stallion biocides.
Voting perimetermu. Find ambush. change.
(SOUND STATlC)
- Chapman. - (STATlC)
Reles. Take a break, or you like to go?
- I'm ready, sir. - Fast.
Chapman in the chart cells. Look around you.
Cole, what's wrong with you? Even now, I do not want to eat.
Eating life.
We just won the Apes building!
Yes sir.
It is not unusual.
This is the brain?
No tactic Therefore, we do our best in this case.
Cooperation
Thank God, you're right.
- Nice to meet you, sir. - Good.
- How many survived? - Seven survivors.
Seven died in the mission.
Raf and Hodges.
The rest were missing.
Where Landa in?
How are you?
- Okay thank you. - Good.
I am glad to hear this news, I'm worried about you.
You want to tell me everything, I do not know ......
Or I'll shoot you in the head.
Monster there.
Of course !!
No one believes.
LN Israel thought I was crazy.
But today ...
So it is not geological tasks.
He dropped a bomb to lure something.
- who are you? - Have you heard USS Lawton?
The public did not.
Thousands of young people on board survived lake
They will be updated in the war ship sank family,
But I know what I see, there is no conscience creatures.
There is no common sense, but devastating.
I spent the last 30 years,
Trying to prove anything, I learned the truth that day.
The planet is not ours.
Ancient species to rule the Earth
Long before the people.
If we do not care, they will not take it back.
The agency is called the monarch, we love
Unknown giant.
You know that thing in here?
I am very sad man, Colonel. Really.
Take us home, and evidence.
Therefore, we can send troops.
L soldiers.
This is called the hollow Earth theory. Randa hire ...
Because I write papers.
It is considered crazy.
That there is a large room in the basement ...
- Close on the surface. - aisle.
Rand believed Island may be one of them.
I would like to point out that no matter what below Yes.
As we have just seen the ancient species.
I thought he was crazy.
LT Slivka. Did you hear that? Others?
We headed north town prostitutes.
It all seemed too quiet.
- There is a hearing? anyone. - We're out of range, Slivka.
"Fuck ! ! ! "
In addition, the approaches the group.
It can not be moved.
Low noise
- Slivka. - what?
Dalmatian.
They did not die in vain.
I swear!.
Their deaths ...
You will be rewarded.
Chapman back to make ammunition.
Have you heard of mice, lions, and thorns of the story?
- Yes. - That's him.
Who would have thought that we would meet again primates.
You know the story of the mice become friends
After the lions mouse thorn out of their hands, right?
Item
The rats were killed thorn lion.
Who told me, Cole?
my mother.
- Damn! - Beware!
- what? - Behind you!
- Beware! - LN tree!
gun!
I'll help you!
I can not shoot!
Cut the legs!
Beware!
clam down! We moved!
Maintain close contact.
What is this?
Wow, behind you!
Low noise
go back!
- come back! - Friends.
- Shoot. - take it easy.
Do not shoot.
Everything is calm.
"What?"
I do not believe it when they told me to come.
I have not slept all night, I think
And Gunpei how I dreamed this moment.
Now, this is happening. 28 years and 11 months.
8 test does not return to the world ......
The world come to me?
It's OK, is not it?
They never laugh.
- are you here? - Oh, I'm sorry, miss.
Hank Captain Marlow, from 45 lnfantry.
I fight for you.
You are so beautiful......
From hot dogs and beer.
On opening day at Wrigley Field.
But you are real.
correct?
I tell you. I told you, right?
I protested.
'' It's OK. ''
Nice.
- It is there. - There are many things out there.
Come on, we need to go home.
You do not want it here in the evening.
You probably already know that in this island there are many strange things.
As long as we are here to accompany them, we'll be fine.
The walls were ...
This is an animal, do not make?
No it does not enter blocked.
"What?"
They live in trees, under us.
Some of them immature.
There is no crime. No private property.
They do not care about all this.
Best regards.
So, good news.
You say you can sleep here.
You can not hear you speak.
They rarely speak.
If you're here, you'll understand.
- let us wait and see. - Wait.
We could not stay. We have to leave here,
our life.
- Life? - Yes, not now, okay?
Who landed here, stays here.
As far as I know, burn washed ashore about 10 years, he has done before l.
You are here from '44?
Yes. What happened during the war? We win?
"What?"
This makes sense.
This is their refuge. If damage your hands, do not touch anything.
check it out.
According to their story, thousands of years,
Islanders live in fear.
This fear is a very long time.
Then one day, the most surprising thing.
They are afraid,
Start protecting them from consuming them.
But I think nothing is eternal.
Here they respect their last city.
Yes sir.
This area.
He's here.
For them, he was a god.
King Kong well.
He is a lonely man.
This is his home. We were the only guests.
Someone you do not come home ...
Unless you ask war dropping bombs.
Wasnt Hong Kong who killed your friend?
Item
one of them.
Keep Hong Kong Island.
But the devil live in our feet.
What are they called it?
lwis not want to mention his name.
But I put it prostrate skull.
- Why? - Because it sounds cool.
- Ok. - To name.
- I want to scare you. - Do not bother with this name.
- Do you mind? I liked the name - yes, that's good.
Do not say that, it sounds silly names.
LT- you want to give him a call.
Big lizard. Malignant.
He is from the ground, which is why Hong Kong angry.
They wake up the bomb.
I want to tell you, you are happy to come here,
Otherwise you will not get in here.
Cunning, very difficult.
Hong Kong can play them when they are very young.
You do not want to wake up super.
- how many. - Over.
He killed his family to Hong Kong.
Kong is the last, but it continues to grow.
You better hope he grows up, because lwis said Hong Kong dead ...
Great will increase.
Then, everything was destroyed.
This is not to say that the three-day North Island feed.
- You must come with us. - Northern part of the island?
- We should get out of here. --3 Days within?
Yes sir.
You can reach the northern end of three days.
Among them, it is impossible.
Do not go.
This is an ugly bird.
Damn. This place is hell.
Monster there.
We paid for it.
- bring it on. - Looks like maybe he would kill
Monkey we are not out of here? Yes.
- what should we do? - Yes, where is it?
Evacuation point. We should arrive within three days.
We will. Better get up.
- How to Chapman ... - If the colonel says he came,
He will come.
We almost do its job.
Gunpai want to go back to the sea.
So they killed him.
Yes.
this is very good.
This is real.
Where I can float?
I Gunpei set them for six years.
His name is gray fox.
It floats.
From aircraft engines M-51 mines,
Its zero.
I found on the beach B-29. This is great.
You must be joking. To tetanus.
I know it's bad. But it can, if it helps increase.
Unless you have a better idea, I suggest you start working.
Good!
wake up!
All right.
Wow.
check it out.
This is bloody!
Those of us who do.
We are looking for Chapman, there are plenty of ammunition in the Sea Stallion crashed,
Do not kill him.
unbelievable.
What I would do, instead of F-16?
l Vietnamese People's Army fought farmer who came from.
After he gave up, we destroyed the village.
He was 60 years old, he was wearing when we arrived.
sometimes...
Enemy no.
When you're looking for it.
What happens when they appear?
I have a gun.
Good luck, soldier.
Okay, so we have the north coast 48 hours.
- Do you know what you're doing? - Yes.
My father was a mechanic. If they can not fix my father will not be happy.
LF I saw on again.
Wait. Russia is our ally.
- We are at war with them? - It is cold.
Do you think the Cold War ...
After the summer?
Cubs win the World Cup?
- Bear? - number
- Are they good? - They are my favorite. where are you from?
- Detroit. - Ok.
So Tiger win?
- I do not know. - I doubt it.
LTTE cubs.
Who do you think wins, tiger or bear children?
Absolute tiger.
Yes, because the bear was a baby.
Adult tiger can eat Baby Bear.
You need to think twice.
I also put a man on the moon.
is it serious? I left him a man?
- What is to eat what? - Kang.
spam.
Come on, this evening.
Fox, Chapman replaced.
Billy dear ...
Sometimes it is difficult for you.
What kind of music?
What happened to swing? Barry Goodman.
You're like a time traveler.
This is modern music.
I do not know what they thought, I have to face behind a beard.
I really hope we can take the boat for 36 hours at upstream.
Because if we're late ...
He graduated from our history.
When he wrote l timeshare around the earth empty ...
Laughing entire board.
Miranda is not.
I take seriously the only person who.
feel good.
Then I thought he was crazy, he told me that there is full of monsters.
I do not know when I'm talking,
- I still do not speak. - Are you saying that.
- right? - Yes. - I said?
- Yes. - His mouth moving.
- what? - I'll stab you tonight.
- is that true? - just joking.
If the ship is not working properly, take the train.
Strange, is not it?
The most dangerous place is always the most beautiful places.
I hope to have a long-exposure photograph, but ...
Fault light.
Oh, ah ...
- Try this. - thank you.
- British Airways? - my father.
He took me from the car when it goes against the Nazis.
For me, he is like John Wayne.
Like a fairy tale hero.
- When does he come back? - Airplane crash in Hamburg.
They looked for him for months, but ......
I do not think this was a general feeling.
thorough.
Hey, do not waste time, check the perimeter.
Packard Colonel ...
Mission in the fall ...
This is a great idea.
I know you are looking for your boy.
Or rest.
It is beyond our means.
I do not like the way liters of leadership?
Please go.
When do you put this place on the map you how to do it.
I will not stop.
I know where the enemy, when I see it.
His name Gunpei lkari.
If we get rid of uniforms ...
And war ...
He became my brother.
He promised not to leave each other.
Let us leave this island.
- Wait! - Set the hose. - Yes.
Fast, come on!
Continue
Three definitely a success! Come on!
Come on!
Yes sir.
Great!
I think this is goodbye.
Best regards.
If you are in Chicago, looking for me.
Let me help you.
Men should do.
Are you ok? - Yes.
Let me go.
You see me in the library.
I have a wife.
But I have a wife?
I couldn’t tell.
There, he served as the Lake
From his telegram, the day before he fell lake
He told me to get the boy.
I have a son there.
Men do not recognize.
She thought you were dead.
I'm fine.
What Naoko, etc.?
I just want a chance to meet them.
This is enough.
We'll send you home.
Fox pet answer. Is anyone here?
Yes, Fox five, we can hear.
Yes, we are on the boat.
- To the north of the river. - ferry?
I can get it where? We encountered a crazy Santa Claus
Over time, you'll meet him.
What ship?
More like an airplane weighing boat.
Called 'Boats'
We boarded the boat.
Keeping an eye on them, Slivka.
Fired flares. We can find you.
Fox pet.
Remove the lens!
Ay.
We've seen two kilometers north.
Fox five, Fox is one of them.
Meet for an hour.
get ready!
You can enter?
Ay.
We go home!
Get off the truck
What is hell?
He was killed.
Put your device, we must continue.
HP station encountered.
No, wait!
Nobody wants to talk about ...... this.
He will not come back. There's nothing to talk about.
Oh!
They have only two kilometers north.
Soon they arrive.
Unless you eat something bigger than us.
Oh my!
Slivko!
I never thought to see you again.
- I think they're crazy. - I hope I'm crazy.
How many people left? look...
This is my stuff.
A person's loss.
glad to meet you.
Who is it?
A passenger.
Hank will Marlow Kuadron Hunter 15 45
You are here since the Second World War?
Yes, I miss the parade?
Oh!
Sincerely, Lieutenant.
We'll take you home, sir.
We follow the river ...
Our ship will arrive on the North Shore.
this is very good.
But we did not go.
Nothing is left here, Conrad.
It still?
Parkman.
He's here at sea species Marcy.
West? We can not go west!
The residence is the place of the skull.
There's an old saying: " 'East, west difference!' '
This is what we say!
Southwest
We can consider it.
We have a lot of weapons, if you want to go west.
You must listen to Mallory.
This is crazy.
He he.
Yourjob find those who are missing, right?
Good morning sir.
But if he is not in that position ...
No search party, we returned in the evening, you know?
Within 24 hours should not be next to the house.
Good. I know.
You heard him. We leave for 10 minutes.
Nice Group.
You want to die here together.
You are a good team, die together.
You should not come here.
It is a bad idea.
Do you smell it?
It was the smell of death.
What is this place?
Among them, the remaining parent concessions.
I often pictures of mass graves, is one of them.
And this hollow valley.
We will go to the highest point of the west.
Item
This place is not good, sir.
We need to go north.
Please friends.
Alone.
I do not want to leave Jack. Who am I?
We can succeed.
of course can.
be careful.
I'm new here 28 years I know what?
Cole ...
We do not have time. Close your cigarettes.
Gas Note!
This is stupid.
We must go!
Run!
where to!
Complete silence.
let us go.
follow me.
let's go together!
Continue on civilians eyes. Come on!
"Fuck ! ! ! "
Relic!
50 caliber rifle!
I will lose more than honor and death.
Come on!
Tim flamethrower! Carry out your duty!
Slivko!
Gas
Toxic gases.
Mallory! sword!
Slivka, survive!
Let's fast!
Listen, Colonel.
The higher your rank ...
However, I am no longer here.
I will tell you..
This animal is only the first.
We are in his territory ...
We should soon!
No, as long as Chapman still there.
I'm sorry, Colonel Packard.
Chapman was dead.
It does not change anything.
We have not lowered position.
- What are you doing here? - Weapon!
Enough to kill him.
LT kill Chapman.
Well, it's killing them!
my people!
You can not kill the gang.
Port on the island of God.
Only those who hold the animals underground lizard.
He was right, Colonel. We can not kill the gang.
Other beings?
This is a threat to their numbers.
If you kill an opponent ...... he can not control.
We killed them too!
After that, we kill this.
I can not let Colonel.
Wait! Do not shoot!
- We will not lose the war. - Crazy!
Did you hear that? This is crazy!
You should listen to us!
We are not at war, Colonel. you are wrong!
Your soldiers are dying because they are lying!
- Do you want us to die. - It's not our job.
- Whose side are you on, sir? - Oh, Colonel.
You are looking for a stallion on the rocks three kilometers.
I put this civil Wara back to the ship.
We are waiting for you there.
Do you agree?
Let's go!
Let's kill this guy!
Steve ...
You want to get into action or silence?
I will not say anything.
Marlowe, are you okay?
We must stop him.
They convince him? This is consistent determination.
He was so furious.
follow me......
We'll go live.
I want to go home for you and your mother.
Courage.
I love you.
Ensure families get it.
Billy dear ...
We are the best fighters.
It was close.
What have you lost? By what?
There are many similar questions and so on.
Wait here.
I have to go to the river.
Hey. I'm coming along.
I'll wait here.
Take care and 9600880
Also note the trees.
What accounts for that?
ant.
Large ants.
This is one.
It sounds like a bird, but it is ants.
Collect as many as you can, including earthquakes bomb.
Mommy.
Mills, Cole ...
Setting explosives.
Give him a special gift napalm.
They have certainly been an explosion.
We have to go. just now.
Do not shoot!
Commander, we are in what direction?
The three of you back to the ship. Through here.
Wait until morning.
LF will not go back ......
Where..
There is no need to be told twice.
Where are you headed?
We want to save Hong Kong.
Without me, man.
soldiers!
Prepare peledakmu.
Now is the time to show the Congo ...
The man is king!
Interject. Turn two.
Atifkan three.
HP!
Failure to do so.
This feeling pretty good at the beginning.
We do not want war, Hewlett-Packard.
The creature we disappointed! He killed my man!
Hong Kong to protect the territory.
We are soldiers!
We do the dirty work ...
Thus, families and our people should not be afraid!
They may not know of the existence of creatures like!
He was furious.
Blowing trigger.
Stop!
Greater than this world.
serious!
Slivka, destroy it!
What did you do wrong, son.
Down, sir.
HP!
Come on!
There.
There are greater.
return
Quick!
Colonel.
Sir!
You're dead, asshole!
Do not lose. Come on!
They told me to go at dawn.
- I know. - This is the dawn.
I got it
So how?
The end of the island.
Weaver, climb rocks and launching rockets.
If you are lucky, you will see it.
Do not delay.
By this way.
Come on, every minute counts.
Cole! We had to retreat.
End your life.
Get out.
- Cole, do not! - Cole!
- Cole, do not! - stop!
- Cole! - Cole! Cole!
Do not! Do not!
Cole!
Come on, asshole.
Go for it! Cheers!
Cole! fast!
Come on!
- Marlowe, help me! - He is hot, be careful!
- of course! - of course!
Come on, motherfucker!
Weaver!
He he.
You are wrong.
So how do you see?
West main road?
I think, my friend.
This place will change.
This message will spread.
Constantly.
What is clearly not one of us.
We'll meet again.
I do not know where it is.
I do not know when.
But I know we'll meet again.